Chapter 1243: Silver Lining

All of a sudden, Weeping Soul noticed something, and she exclaimed through voice transmission, "Master, your aura..."

"I've noticed it as well. Right now, my aura is very unstable. Not only has the Corpse Severance Talisman forcibly separated the wicked corpse soul from my soul, in a way, it's also accelerated the progression of my cultivation base. I'm currently in a very strange state. In addition to the four hundred and sixty immortal acupoints that I've already opened, there are three hundred and eighty more that are in a half-open, half-closed state," Han Li replied.

Indeed, it was a very peculiar situation that he was in. Essentially, the power of the Corpse Severance Talisman had forcibly elevated him to a pseudo mid-Great Encompassment Stage.

Opening eight hundred and forty immortal acupoints was the prerequisite to reaching the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, yet in his current state, he had one foot in the door, while the other was still stuck firmly outside, putting him in a very awkward position.

"The silver lining here is that your cultivation base seems to have been significantly elevated," Weeping Soul said.

After a brief hesitation, Weeping Soul continued, "What do we do from here, Master? Qu Lin seems to be targeting Jin Tong as well. Do we go after him or..."

Han Li was also rather hesitant, unsure of what to do.

Right at this moment, Xiaobai's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Let me out, Master! I can sense Boss's aura!"

An elated look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he immediately raised a hand to release Xiaobai.

As soon as he appeared, he immediately took on his Pixiu form and began vigorously sniffing at the air.

"That way!" he yelled as he rushed deeper into the collapsed underground space, and they quickly arrived at the stone gate at the very back of the hall.

Half of the stone gate had already collapsed, and Xiaobai rushed through the collapsed half of the gate in a flash, while Han Li's trio hurriedly followed along.

Beyond the stone gate was another rather short passageway, at the end of which was another closed stone gate that was giving off a metallic, black gleam, and there were also countless squiggly, worm-like runes etched onto its surface, forming a complex array.

Xiaobai opened his mouth to release a burst of white light with countless runes churning within it, and the ball of white light struck the stone gate before exploding violently.

The stone gate shuddered as the black array on its surface was thrown into a state of disarray, but it was able to withstand the blow.

Xiaobai's brows furrowed slightly as he prepared to try again, but Han Li had already caught up to him, and he flicked his fingers through the air in rapid succession, releasing seven or eight streaks of golden sword qi that struck the stone gate with tremendous force.

A string of resounding thumps rang out as the array on the stone gate was torn apart with ease, and the gate itself was also reduced to a pile of rubble, much to Han Li's elation.

At the moment, with over three hundred of his immortal acupoints in a half-opened state, he was able to take in the world's origin qi at a far faster rate than before, thereby significantly enhancing the power of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

"Let's go," he called out to the others, and they rushed through the destroyed gate into another black stone hall.

This one was a little smaller than the underground space from before, and at its center was a giant array, at the center of which, in turn, was a black, crystalline coffin with an unclear purpose.

Spread out around the stone hall were seven or eight smaller rooms, giving it the appearance of a cave abode.

Could this be Gui Lingzi's cave abode? Han Li speculated as he swept his gaze over his surroundings, while Weeping Soul's gaze had locked onto black, crystalline coffin with her eyes glowing with intrigue.

"Boss's scent is coming from in there!" Xiaobai declared as he pressed a paw against the door of one of the rooms, and there were no restrictions on it, so he was able to push it open with ease.

Han Li and Lan Yan hurriedly rushed into the room to discover a giant, white cage that seemed to have been crafted from some type of special jade situated at its center.

The cage was riddled with spirit patterns and talismans, and it had clearly been used to hold something captive, but there was a large hole in one of its corners, seemingly having been inflicted by a bite.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he crouched down beside the hole in the cage, then wiped a finger over its jagged edge and pressed it against his own glabella momentarily, following which he concluded, "The residual aura here belongs to Jin Tong, so she must've been held captive here this entire time. However, it seems like she bit through the cage to escape. Judging from how fresh the bite mark appears, this must've happened not long ago."

"What do we do? She's already gone, and we have no way to track her," Lan Yan said in a concerned manner.

"We may not be able to track Jin Tong, but we can track Qu Lin," Han Li said.

"That's right! He only left recently, so his trail is still fresh! Let's go after him!" Xiaobai exclaimed with an excited expression before turning to leave.

"Hold on a second," Han Li said as he reached out to stop Xiaobai with a smile on his face. "This appears to be Gui Lingzi's cave abode, so I'm sure there are many valuable spoils to be reaped here."

"You're right, Master! That bastard dared to capture Boss, so let's take everything he has to teach him a lesson!" Xiaobai chuckled in a sly manner, then flew over to one of the rooms before giving its door a vicious kick.

There was a restriction on the stone door, but it wasn't very powerful. Clearly, Gui Lingzi hadn't anticipated that someone would dare to blatantly wreak havoc in his cave abode, so Xiaobai was able to kick the door open with ease.

Lan Yan also flew over to another room before blasting through its door, while Han Li did the same.

The room that Han Li had chosen was two hundred to three hundred feet in size, and it was filled with wooden shelves that were laden with all types of precious ore and materials, all of which were of exceptional quality, superior even to the items in his collection.

On top of that, there was also a huge number of them, and this was the perfect find, considering he was currently in need of large sums of Immortal Origin Stones.

With a sweep of his sleeves, Han Li released two bursts of azure light that swept up the materials along with their shelves before stowing them away into his Flower Branch domain.

Given the urgency of the situation, he acted very quickly, taking everything in the room in the blink of an eye before moving onto the next room.

Inside this room was an octagonal, golden cauldron that was even taller than he was, and even in its resting state, it was giving off a burst of tremendous spiritual qi fluctuations.

There was nothing else in the room aside from the cauldron, so this had to have been Gui Lingzi's pill refinement chamber.

Han Li wasted no time in taking the cauldron, which he could use for himself or sell for a considerable sum of Immortal Origin Stones, then arrived at a third room.

It was a small room with only a stone table inside, enshrouded within a black light barrier.

There were around a dozen fist-sized, black crystal balls on the table, all of which were filled with flickering, black flames, and even through the light barrier, one could sense astonishing soul power fluctuations emanating from them.

"Those are balls of Profound Yin Divine Lightning!" Lan Yan exclaimed from behind Han Li upon catching a glimpse of the crystal balls.

"What's that?" Han Li asked.

"Profound Yin Divine Lightning is a special type of yin lightning refined by Gui Lingzi. It's extremely powerful, posing a threat even to early-Great Encompassment cultivators. Thank heavens Gui Lingzi wasn't carrying these balls of lightning with him. Otherwise, we would've been in some trouble during our battle," Lan Yan explained with a hint of lingering fear in her eyes.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this, and he flicked a finger through the air, releasing a bolt of golden lightning that destroyed the black protective barrier around the stone table with ease.

However, right at this moment, the black crystal balls on the table suddenly began to radiate dazzling, black light, and the black flames within them were also displaying signs of erupting.

Han Li was rather alarmed by this, but before he had a chance to do anything, a burst of black light raced through the air from behind him to envelop the crystal balls.

The black flames in the crystal balls were stabilized by the law powers imbued within the burst of black light, and Weeping Soul approached Han Li as she explained, "These balls of yin lightning are still yet to be fully refined, so they're still a little volatile, and your Cardinal Heavenly Lightning is the bane of all yin-attribute powers, so you could easily trigger this yin lightning into exploding."

"In that case, you can have them," Han Li said.

Weeping Soul shuddered slightly upon hearing this, following which a look of excitement and gratitude appeared on her face as she thanked Han Li for his generosity.

The burst of black light that she had released carried the balls of Profound Yin Divine Lightning to her at her behest, and she cast a string of incantation seals onto them.

A layer of black light instantly appeared around the crystal balls, as if a thick layer of paint had been applied onto them, and only then were the black flames inside completely stabilized.

Meanwhile, Xiaobai had also returned to Han Li's side, having reverted back to his human form, and there was a wide grin on his face.

The doors of the other rooms in the cave abode had all been destroyed, and it was clear that everything inside had been pillaged.

Chapter 1244: Following the Trail

"Did you two manage to find much?" Han Li asked, directing the question to Xiaobai and Lan Yan.

"You bet I did! I never imagined there would be so many treasures in Gui Lingzi's cave abode!" Xiaobai replied in an excited manner.

A hint of excitement also flashed through Lan Yan's eyes, but she quickly suppressed it as she offered a storage tool to Han Li with both hands and said, "This contains what I gathered from the three rooms that I went through."

"You can take a tenth of what's inside as your compensation," Han Li said in a calm manner.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Han," Lan Yan replied with a look of genuine gratitude.

The storage tool contained a priceless collection of treasures, so even just a tenth of it was a massive amount of wealth for her, something that she wouldn't even have dared to imagine in the past.

Han Li then turned to Xiaobai, who immediately grabbed onto a storage bracelet around his wrist as he protested, "I found everything in here, so it's all mine!"

"I understand, but I'm in need of Immortal Origin Stones, so I'll only take half of what's inside, while you can keep the rest," Han Li said with a wry smile.

Xiaobai let loose a loud cheer, then flipped a hand over to produce another storage tool and began transferring items into it.

"I have a request for you, Master," Weeping Soul suddenly said.

"What is it?" Han Li asked.

"Come with me, Master," Weeping Soul said as she strode over to the black crystal coffin at the center of the array in the stone chamber.

Only then did he recall the crystal coffin's existence, and he followed Weeping Soul to it.

As he peered into the coffin, his expression changed slightly as he discovered a set of white remains inside. The remains were riddled with black runes, and it was very peculiar in appearance, particularly the two crimson flames flashing within its inky-black eye sockets.

The entire set of remains was giving off an extremely sinister aura, as if it were the amalgamation of all things evil in the world.

Han Li felt as if just the mere sight of the set of remains was causing his wicked corpse soul to stir in his consciousness, and he hurriedly averted his eyes as he asked, "What a peculiar set of remains. Do you know what it is?"

"If I'm not mistaken, this should be a set of Absolute Heinous Remains, a set of remains created by collecting ten thousand sets of bodies and souls of people who've committed heinous atrocities during their lifetimes before being refined using a secret technique, and it's very helpful for severing wicked corpse souls," Weeping Soul replied in an excited manner.

"How intriguing," Han Li mused as he raised an eyebrow.

"This thing is very useful for all of us, Master. With these Absolute Heinous Remains, wicked corpse soul severances will be made far easier for you, me, Xiaobai, and Jin Tong. The problem is that this crystal coffin has been rooted to this spot, and in order to take it away without harming the Absolute Heinous Remains inside, we'll have to break the surrounding array first, and that's where I need your help, Master," Weeping Soul said.

"Alright, that's not a problem. You focus on taking the coffin, I'll help you break the array," Han Li replied with a nod.

"I'll be counting on you then, Master. With your Cardinal Heavenly Lightning, breaking this array should be a simple task," Weeping Soul said, then immediately sprang into action, and bursts of dense, black qi erupted out of her body before fusing into the array on the ground.

The array instantly lit up, and eight black chains that were giving off an astonishingly formidable glacial aura emerged near the coffin, connecting it to the array below.

Weeping Soul opened her mouth to release a ball of white light, which split up into eight parts and fused into the eight black chains, instantly turning them a half-black, half white color.

At the same time, the glacial aura emanating from them subsided significantly, and a barrier of separation appeared between the coffin and the eight chains.

"Sever the chains now, Master!" Weeping Soul yelled, and Han Li immediately flicked his fingers through the air in rapid succession, releasing eight Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords to strike the eight chains.

The chains exploded violently, and a burst of radiant, black light erupted out of the crystal coffin as it began rising up into the air.

An ecstatic look appeared on Weeping Soul's face upon seeing this, and she made a grabbing motion to summon a giant, black hand projection that caught the coffin in its grasp.

At the same time, she swept her other sleeve through the air to summon the Yama Cauldron that Han Li had given to her, and a burst of dark red light surged out of it to encompass the crystal coffin.

In the next instant, the coffin abruptly vanished, having been sucked into the cauldron's internal space.

"Thank you, Master!" Weeping Soul said in a grateful manner.

Shortly thereafter, Lan Yan and Xiaobai flew over to him as well before handing him a pair of storage tools.

Han Li accepted the storage tools, then inspected their contents with his spiritual sense, upon which an elated look appeared on his face.

The two storage tools contained mostly spirit medicines, demon beast materials, and other treasures of that nature, but unfortunately, there were no Immortal Origin Stones inside.

This was only to be expected, considering Immortal Origin Stones were generally carried on one's body. They were mostly never used in one's cave abode, and they took up a great deal of storage space, so it didn't make sense to leave them lying around.

The most valuable treasures in Gui Lingzi's collection were most likely in his storage tool.

Having said that, this was still a massive haul that could be sold for around seventy to eighty million Immortal Origin Stones.

"Let's go after Qu Lin. We've already wasted enough time here," Han Li said as he returned the same way that he had come from, with Weeping Soul and the others following close behind, and they quickly arrived back at the collapsed stone hall from before.

The path back was completely blocked by fallen rocks, but that didn't pose much of an obstacle for Han Li's group, who were able to clear away the rocks as they went, and they quickly arrived at a crossroads.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes to inspect the residual spiritual power traces left behind in this place, only to discover that the traces were very scant, and all of them had been left behind when he, Lan Yan, and Qu Lin had passed through this area together.

Somehow, Qu Lin had managed to completely cover his tracks and erase the spiritual power traces left behind from when he passed back through this point.

On top of that, the fact that Weeping Soul hadn't been able to detect his sinister intent earlier as he was leading them into that trap was a clear indication of just how thoroughly he had concealed his intentions.

Han Li harrumphed coldly as he channeled his Infernal Devilish Eyes with all his might, hoping that his ocular abilities would be superior to Qu Lin's concealment techniques.

A pair of dark purple vortexes took shape within his pupils as he cast his gaze into the crossroad up ahead, and an elated look appeared on his face as caught a glimpse of an extremely faint glimmer of golden light that extended into one of the paths of the crossroads.

The golden light was spread out in a very chaotic fashion, and they were extremely faint, virtually impossible to detect if he wasn't close to full mastery over his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

"Have you found a trail, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"Indeed, I have. Come with me," Han Li replied with a nod, then led Weeping Soul and the others down the path.

Close to a day flew by in a flash, and they were still racing through the network of underground passageways.

At this point, the underground area that they were in was completely devoid of ghostly qi, indicating that they were already far away from the Ghost Valley, yet there was still no end in sight up ahead.

They had encountered some restrictions and obstacles along the way, but none of them had been all that formidable, and many of them had already been destroyed, presumably by Qu Lin, so they didn't pose much of a hindrance.

"Do you know what the purpose of this huge underground network is, Fellow Daoist Lan?" Han Li aksed.

"Given my lowly status in the Nine Origins Temple, I've only ever been in the inner temple a handful of times, and I didn't even know that this network of underground tunnels existed," Lan Yan replied with a wry smile.

Han Li nodded in response, unsurprised by this answer as he continued onward.

After flying for a short while longer, he spotted a faint glimmer of golden light up ahead, right at the extreme limit of his vision.

Han Li immediately stopped in his tracks, as did everyone else, and Weeping Soul asked, "Have we finally reached the end?"

"I don't know about that, but there's definitely something up ahead. As a safety precaution, I'll get all of you to return to the Flower Branch domain. Rest assured, I'll project what's happening outside into the domain," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light.

"Alright, make sure to be careful, Master," Weeping Soul said, then flew into the Flower Branch domain, followed by Lan Yan and Xiaobai, the latter of whom did so with clear reluctance.

After the three of them entered the domain, Han Li concealed himself using his black Reincarnation Palace mask, then quickly made his way to the end of the passageway.

At the end of the passageway was a golden wall forged from some type of golden ore, and that was the source of the golden light that Han Li had spotted earlier.

At close proximity, he could also sense extremely potent metal law power fluctuations emanating from the wall, and his eyes instantly lit up at the sight of it.

This is Heavenend Gold Rock!

Heavenend Gold Rock was an extremely precious type of metal-attribute law material. It was inferior in value to Heavenly Vajra Diamond, but such a large quantity of it could still be sold for a very good price.

Han Li shook his head in amusement at this thought. He had become so obsessed with earning Immortal Origin Stones of late that he was constantly assessing the monetary value of everything that he came across.

All of a sudden, Han Li's gaze fell upon a corner of the golden stone wall, where a hole appeared to have chewed through it.

Faint glimmers of light could be seen through the hole, clearly indicating that there was something of interest on the other side.

There was a restriction in the wall that repelled Han Li's spiritual sense, making it impossible for him to detect what was on the other side.

Chapter 1245: Battle Between Gold Devouring Immortals

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li gently stroked a finger over the hole in the wall before pressing it against his own glabella, upon which his eyes instantly lit up.

The residual aura in the hole belonged to none other than Jin Tong.

Sure enough, she had come here after escaping from the Ghost Valley, but it was unclear why she had come here.

Of course, Qu Lin's aura was also present in the hole, indicating that he had gone after her.

Han Li chanted a quick incantation, then flew into the hole like a slithering snake, quickly passing through to the other side.

On the other side of the wall was a palace with a square base that was several thousand feet in size. The entirety of the palace was constructed from Heavenend Gold Rock, including even the ground, and there were extremely formidable metal law power fluctuations sweeping through the area.

The interior of the palace was completely empty, but it was still a majestic sight to behold, given that the entire structure was constructed from Heavenend Gold Rock.

"How extravagant," Han Li remarked.

Right at this moment, Lan Yan's voice rang out in his mind.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I just recalled that there's rumored to be a Nine Origins Palace in the Nine Origins Temple. It's said to have been constructed from a gargantuan piece of metal-attribute material by the Nine Origins Dao Ancestor, and this is most likely it!"

"What is the purpose of this Nine Origins Palace?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know the answer to that. All that I know is that it's a sacred place in the Nine Origins Temple. Perhaps it's a cultivation venue. After all, this place is extremely abundant with metal-attribute law powers, and there are many cultivators of metal law powers in the temple. In any case, make sure to be extra careful and vigilant here," Lan Yan cautioned.

Han Li nodded in response, then continued to search for spiritual power traces left behind by Qu Lin with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

However, the excessive abundance of metal-attribute law powers in this place proved to be very disruptive, and only after activating his Infernal Devilish Eyes to their full power was he finally able to catch a glimpse of a trail that led to the very back of the palace, where there was a side door.

Han Li opened the door to discover a garden outside, and the ground here was also Heavenend Gold Rock, but the pots in the garden were filled with all types of spirit soil, planted within which were many types of exotic spirit plants, most of which were of the metal attribute.

Han Li paid no heed to the spirit plants in the garden as he continued to follow the trail of spiritual power.

This was an enormous area, but there were many things here that acted as visual hindrances, and spiritual sense was also severely restricted, making it rather difficult to get a good sense of one's surroundings.

Han Li passed through two gardens and several palaces in succession, but there was still no end in sight, nor had he found any traces of Jin Tong.

Stumbling blindly through this place was very likely to lead to danger, and he was beginning to grow a little concerned.

After passing through yet another palace, Han Li finally spotted something, and his eyes lit up as he forged ahead with renewed vigor.

He could sense two auras clashing violently upon ahead amid a thunderous commotion, clearly indicating that a fierce battle was taking place, and the two auras belonged to none other than Jin Tong and Qu Lin.

After flying through a walkway, he arrived at an enormous plaza that was forty to fifty acres in size.

The plaza was surrounded by numerous massive, golden stone pillars with array patterns etched upon them, seemingly forming an array, but it was currently in an inactive state.

Two massive, golden beetles were currently locked in a fierce battle against one another in the air above the plaza, and they were none other than Jin Tong and Qu Lin.

As their battle raged on, bursts of golden light were occasionally sent crashing down onto the ground, and even though the plaza had also been constructed from Heavenend Gold Rock, Jin Tong and Qu Lin's attacks were so formidable that they still left many huge craters in the ground, while several of the golden pillars around the plaza had also been snapped.

The golden light radiating from Jin Tong and Qu Lin's bodies resembled a pair of giant mouths that were tearing at one another, and since parting ways with Han Li, Jin Tong had reached the early-Great Encompassment Stage.

However, Qu Lin had already reached the pinnacle of the early-Great Encompassment Stage, and his aura clearly dwarfed hers.

"Once I devour you, I'll be able to reach the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, perhaps even the late-Great Encompassment Stage! Just surrender yourself to me!" Qu Lin guffawed, but Jin Tong continued to put up spirited resistance, although it was clear that she was feeling the strain.

Qu Lin chuckled coldly as a golden spirit domain that was around twenty to thirty acres in size erupted out of his body to encompass close to half of the entire plaza, and countless massive golden blades appeared within the spirit domain.

Encompassed within the spirit domain, Jin Tong found herself trapped in a cage of giant blades, and they raked against her body to raise flurries of golden sparks.

The bodies of Gold Devouring Immortals were extremely resilient, so the golden blades were unable to harm her, but she was slowed down significantly by these pesky obstacles.

In response, she released her spirit domain as well, and countless golden beetle projections appeared within it.

The projections were very similar to Gold Devouring Immortals in appearance, except they had enormous mouths that took up most of their heads, and their mouths were filled with countless small yet sharp teeth.

The golden beetle projections pounced onto the golden blades before sinking their teeth into them, and they were particularly concentrated around Jin Tong.

The cage of golden blades around Jin Tong was quickly eradicated, yet right as she was about to be freed, Qu Lin abruptly appeared above her before sweeping his two front legs through the air.

All of the golden blades within his spirit domain instantly converged toward a single spot, forming two massive, golden swords that were each over a thousand feet in size.

The swords had three faces each, forming a prismatic structure, and they were giving off a burst of bone-chilling killing intent, as if they were capable of stripping away all life energy.

The pair of giant swords swept through the air toward Jin Tong at his behest, and an alarmed look appeared in Jin Tong's eyes as she let loose a loud shriek.

The golden beetle projections around her immediately pounced on the pair of giant swords, but they weren't even able to make contact with the sword before they were completely eradicated by the tremendous sword qi emanating from it.

The two swords appeared no more than three feet above Jin Tong's head in the blink of an eye before descending upon her, and a look of finality surfaced in Jin Tong's as she prepared to unleash some type of last resort ability.

However, right at this moment, yet another golden spirit domain suddenly emerged, this one encompassing both Jin Tong and Qu Lin's spirit domains, and it was filled with immense time law powers.

Enshrouded within the time spirit domain, the speed of descent of the pair of giant swords was instantly slowed down to a crawl.

Immediately thereafter, a mountainous, golden hand with countless golden runes flashing over its surface appeared out of thin air before grabbing onto the two swords.

Qu Lin's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he immediately attempted to make a string of hand seals, but his movements had also become extremely slow and sluggish.

The golden hand closed its fingers around the pair of giant swords with immense power, and a burst of tremendous spiritual pressure erupted out of it as the two golden swords were crushed into pieces with a resounding thump.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li appeared directly above Jin Tong, and an ecstatic look appeared on her face as she exclaimed, "Uncle!"

"What?! How did you manage to escape from Gui Lingzi?!" Qu Lin exclaimed in an incredulous manner.

A furious look flashed through Han Li's eyes at the mention of Gui Lingzi, and he abruptly vanished from the spot in a flash.

Qu Lin took a resentful glance at Jin Tong, then shrank down drastically before speeding away as a streak of golden light, fleeing the scene without any hesitation.

It was quite apparent that Jin Tong and Han Li were allies, and there was no way that he could hope to hold his own against both of them.

However, he wasn't able to get very far before Han Li appeared directly in his path in a wraith-like manner, displaying far superior speed to him.

An alarmed look appeared on Qu Lin's face as he lashed out with his two front legs with a fierce roar.

In response, Han Li vanished from the spot once again, only to reappear beside Qu Lin an instant later before throwing an almighty right punch into his side.

A resounding boom rang out as Qu Lin was sent flying back through the air long before his front legs were able to reach Han Li.

His movements were drastically slowed by Han Li's time law powers, while Han Li's speed was being enhanced by his Reversal True Axis ability, so there was simply no comparison against the two.

Under Patriarch Miro's advice, he had been cultivating his Reversal True Axis ability whenever he had some spare time, and he was now able to enhance his own speed by close to thirtyfold. In conjunction with his time spirit domain, he could dominate all enemies when it came to speed.

His punch had left a deep fist indentation in Qu Lin's side, but his golden exoskeleton hadn't been broken.

However, Han Li remained undeterred as he vanished from the spot once again, then reappeared beside Qu Lin before sending him flying back the same way he had come from with another punch.

All of a sudden, it was as if there were over a hundred Han Lis whizzing back and forth in his spirit domain, raining down heavy blows upon Qu Lin without respite.

Qu Lin was sent flying through the air over and over again without being able to put up any resistance, and a stunned look had appeared on his face, while blood was already trickling down from the corner of his mouth.

Even the body of a Gold Devouring Immortal had its limits, and Han Li's punches were incredibly heavy, so if things were to continue like this, then something was sure to give.

Chapter 1246: Reminiscence

All of a sudden, Qu Lin let loose a high-pitched screech, and countless specks of golden light appeared over the exoskeleton on his back.

A string of dull thuds then rang out as all of the specks of golden light transformed into sharp, golden spikes, much like the spikes of a porcupine, serving as a defense mechanism against Han Li's relentless barrage.

In response, Han Li stopped in his tracks, then made a grabbing motion with one hand to summon nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, all of which fused as one in mid-air to form a giant, golden sword that was over a thousand feet in length.

With an almighty swing, the sword came crashing down onto Qu Lin's back, sending him flying while also shattering most of the golden spikes on his back.

Blood came gushing uncontrollably out of his mouth, while his spirit domain collapsed violently.

On the surface, he appeared unharmed, and it seemed like he had been able to withstand the blow, but the Cardinal Heavenly Lightning in Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords was not to be underestimated.

Gold Devouring Immortals were renowned for their near-indestructible bodies, but they were particularly vulnerable once their physical defenses were breached.

Qu Lin was already carrying some internal injuries, and those injuries were instantly exacerbated by the influx of Cardinal Heavenly Lightning, throwing his immortal spiritual power circulation into a state of disarray, and that was why he was no longer able to maintain his spirit domain.

A sense of despair began to well up in his heart, but he wasn't going to give up so easily, and he fought to stabilize the chaotic immortal spiritual power in his body as he prepared for a counterattack.

However, right at this moment, a ball of golden light came descending from the sky, falling upon him before he had a chance to take any evasive measures.

Enshrouded within the golden light, he was instantly immobilized, as if he had fallen into a pit of quicksand.

In the next instant, two long streaks of translucent light swept through the interior of the ball of light, slicing Qu Lin's body into three parts as golden blood splattered everywhere.

Countless Gold Devouring Beetles then emerged within the ball of golden light, while Jin Tong was nowhere to be seen.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

The Gold Devouring Beetles began to devour the three parts of Qu Lin's body in a frenzy, but his body then also split apart into countless Gold Devouring Beetles before fleeing in all directions.

Han Li raised both hands upon seeing this, and the golden light within his spirit domain began to swirl around his body, forming a massive, golden vortex.

The Gold Devouring Beetles formed by Qu Lin were powerless to resist the might of Han Li's spirit domain, and they were all sucked into the vortex, unable to escape.

In contrast, the Gold Devouring Beetles formed by Jin Tong remained completely unaffected, and they continued their feeding frenzy.

Unable to get away, the Gold Devouring Beetles formed by Qu Lin could only engage Jin Tong in battle again.

The two swarms of Gold Devouring Beetles clashed like a pair of golden waves, tearing at one another amid a chorus of high-pitched screeching sounds.

An indescribable feeling welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this. He felt as if he had been taken back to what seemed like an eternity ago, back when he had just obtained his first batch of Gold Devouring Beetles and discovered that they could evolve through devouring one another.

Even though Qu Lin was superior to Jin Tong in power, the latter had gained the upper hand over him in light of the injuries that had been inflicted upon him by Han Li.

However, even so, Jin Tong was still struggling to overcome her more powerful opponent.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh as he was snapped out of his reminiscence, then made a hand seal to send a burst of time law powers sweeping through his spirit domain, and the Gold Devouring Beetles formed by Qu Lin were slowed down even further.

"Thanks, Uncle!"

Jin Tong's grateful voice rang out from the swarm of Gold Devouring Beetles, and with Han Li's help, Jin Tong was able to enjoy a dominant advantage.

Before long, almost all of the Gold Devouring Beetles formed by Qu Lin had been devoured.

Right at this moment, what remained of those Gold Devouring Beetles suddenly converged toward a single spot, as if they were trying to fuse back into one.

"Just as you said, you were all one to begin with, so why struggle against your destiny?" Han Li murmured to himself as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a thick arc of golden lightning to strike the spot where the Gold Devouring Beetles had converged.

A loud thunderclap rang out as all of the beetles were scattered before instantly being overwhelmed by the swarm of Gold Devouring Beetles formed by Jin Tong.

Shortly thereafter, all of the commotion died down as the remaining Gold Devouring Beetles recombined to form Jin Tong.

At this moment, she was looking far more mature in appearance, and she had also become even more beautiful, but the cold look on her face made her appear very unapproachable.

As soon as she reverted back to her human form, she immediately sat down with her legs crossed, and over six hundred immortal acupoints lit up over her body.

Han Li knew that Jin Tong was trying to digest the power that she had attained from devouring Qu Lin, and he swept both sleeves through the air to release a flurry of azure array flags, which landed around the two of them before conjuring up several layers of azure light barriers.

More and more immortal acupoints lit up over Jin Tong's body in rapid succession, exceeding seven hundred in the blink of an eye, while her aura was also rapidly elevating, much to Han Li's elation.

Given their current, perilous circumstances, they were going to need all of the power that they could muster.

As time passed, more and more immortal acupoints lit up over Jin Tong's body, quickly exceeding eight hundred, bringing her ever closer to the pinnacle of the early-Great Encompassment Stage.

Han Li couldn't help but wonder if she was going to make a breakthrough to the mid-Great Encompassment Stage in one fell swoop.

However, after opening her eight hundred and thirty-ninth immortal acupoint, the golden light shimmering over Jin Tong's body slowly faded away.

Han Li could sense that there was still a great deal of excess power in her body that was left unused, but it was clear that she was still not ready for her wicked corpse soul severance, so she had decided to delay her breakthrough.

Before Long, Jin Tong reopened her eyes and rose to her feet.

"I'm glad to see you again, Jin Tong," Han Li said as he removed the surrounding restrictions.

"Long time no see, Uncle! What are you doing here?" Jin Tong asked.

"I'm here to rescue you, of course. I'm not the only one, Xiaobai came as well," Han Li replied as he swept a sleeve through the air, and Xiaobai appeared beside him in his Pixiu form amid a flash of white light.

"Boss! I missed you so much!" Xiaobai wailed as he pounced at Jin Tong with tears and snot flowing down his face.

"Stop!" Jin Tong yelled as she kept Xiaobai's head away with her foot so that he couldn't rub any of his tears and snot onto her.

In spite of this rather cold reception, it was clear that she was still very touched, and she said in a quiet voice, "I'm sorry for causing you trouble, Uncle."

"There's no need to apologize. We've been companions for so many years, it's only right that we help one another in our times of need," Han Li said with a wave of his hand.

"I suppose you're right," Jin Tong said with a vibrant smile, and Han Li's eyes lit up slightly at her stunning beauty.

Out of all of the female cultivators that he knew, perhaps only Violet Spirit could compete with the current Jin Tong in the looks department.

"I'm so glad you're safe, Boss!" Xiaobai whimpered as he rubbed his head affectionately against Jin Tong.

"Jin Tong, I was told that you were being held captive in the Ghost Valley. How did you end up here?" Han Li asked.

"Gui Lingzi locked me up in that jade cage of his, and he was planning to offer me up to the Heavenly Court during the Bodhi Banquet. However, he suddenly left a few days ago, and I was able to bite my way out of the cage. It wasn't easy, but I managed to do it. After that, I stumbled through a bunch of underground passageways and somehow ended up here," Jin Tong explained.

"I see. We may be safe for now, but it still won't be an easy task for us to leave the Nine Origins Temple," Han Li said.

......

The Nine Origins Palace was the most important area in the entire Nine Origins Temple, and the heart of the sect, the ancestral hall, was situated behind the palace.

At this point, this area was also under attack from the Reincarnation Palace's forces.

The spatial restrictions around the Nine Origins Palace had already been opened, and the entire area was enshrouded under a golden light barrier, around which was stationed several thousand core elders and disciples of the temple.

It seemed like this location was quite high on the Reincarnation Palace's list of priorities as well, and the Nine Origins Temple's forces were outnumbered by severalfold by the Reincarnation Palace cultivators here.

Initially, the Nine Origin Temple cultivators were still able to hold their own against the Reincarnation Palace's forces thanks to the restrictions present, but before long, the casualties became too severe, and they were forced to retreat within the golden light barrier, continuing to hold down the fort while awaiting further reinforcements.

However, it was clear that the Reincarnation Palace had been planning this attack for a very long time, and prior to attacking the Nine Origins Palace, it had already ensured that all of the other powerful Nine Origins Temple cultivators were occupied, while ambushes had also been set up on the routes that had to be taken by reinforcements.

As a result, the Nine Origins Palace was currently completely isolated on a helpless island of its own.

Chapter 1247: Ulterior Motive

Right at this moment, a thunderous voice suddenly rang out from above.

"Let's break through this final layer of defense! Time is of the essence, and victory is within our grasp!"

As soon as the voice trailed off, Immortal Lord Heavenly Star appeared out of thin air, looking completely different from his usual lethargic self.

He was holding a silver spear with hundreds of crimson crystals encrusted into its surface, and as he pointed it up at the heavens, all of the crystals began to glow with dazzling, red light.

The clouds up above instantly began to churn violently while taking on a crimson coloration, and immediately thereafter, a burst of dull rumbling that resembled the sound of a distant thunderstorm rang out from deep within the clouds.

Countless fiery, millstone-sized meteorites then came crashing down from above in a blazing storm, bombarding the golden light barrier before exploding into countless bursts of crimson fire, causing the nearby space to tremble violently.

Even though the golden light barrier appeared to be struggling to withstand the assault, it was able to hold itself intact as a series of golden ripples surged incessantly over its surface.

"Traitorous scum!" a Nine Origins Temple elder berated, while the other elders and disciples were also looking up at Immortal Lord Heavenly Star with furious expressions.

However, Immortal Lord Heavenly Star paid no heed to them as he continued to attack the golden light barrier below.

......

In stark contrast with the ongoing commotion outside, the interior of the Nine Origins Palace was very peaceful, with only the fake mountains, stone trees, and other structures inside occasionally trembling slightly from the explosions outside.

Right at this moment, a silver array that was around thirty feet in diameter suddenly appeared on the ground in an intricately laid out garden in the palace, and five figures emerged within it.

Three of them were wearing black Reincarnation Palace masks, namely in the form of a wyrm, an ape, and a rabbit.

The figure wearing the ape mask was an extremely tall and imposing man, and he said, "It's just as you predicted, the deepest part of the lion's den turns out to be the most peaceful place."

"The Nine Origins Palace is the most important location in the Nine Origins Temple, and it's only accessible to very few people. Hence, anyone that can appear here is sure to be a formidable opponent, so we have to be even more vigilant and avoid battle as much as possible," the woman in the wyrm mask said, then took a slightly uneasy glance at her rabbit-mask-wearing companion.

The figure in the rabbit mask wasn't particularly tall, and he was also rather thin. His hair spilled down behind his mask in an unkempt fashion, and he was constantly mumbling something to himself.

"Spiritual sense is virtually useless here, so we'll be counting on you to guide us, Fellow Daoist Lu," Wu Yang said as he turned to someone standing behind him.

The man was none other than Lu Chuanfeng, and he replied in an uncertain manner, "I haven't been here many times before, so I'll only be able to narrow it down to an approximate. From there, we'll have to count on Fellow Daoist Gong."

A gentle, female voice rang out in response from beside him.

"Rest assured, everyone, I'll definitely be able to track that thing down once it's within my sensory range."

Wyrm 3's brows furrowed slightly as she cast her gaze toward the woman.

She was wearing a long, black dress that perfectly enveloped her elegant figure, and there was a veiled hat on her head, concealing her entire face, revealing only a section of her fair, swan-like neck.

Wyrm 3 didn't know who this woman was. All she could recall was that she had caught a glimpse of the woman's side profile under the stone arch bridge back when she had met with the master of the Reincarnation Palace in that strange space.

"Time is of the essence, so let's get going," Wu Yang said, and Lu Chuanfeng nodded in response before leading the way forward, followed by everyone else.

Not long after their departure, two more figures emerged from behind a nearby thicket of spirit plants, and one of them was none other than Mountain Master Huo Yuan of the Hundred Creations Mountain, while the one accompanying him was Chi Meng.

"What exactly is it that these Reincarnation Palace scoundrels want? Have they gone insane? Are they actually planning to conquer the Nine Origins Temple?" Chi Meng asked as she took a glance in the direction that Wyrm 3 and the others had departed in.

"If the Nine Origins Temple really were that vulnerable, then it wouldn't have held a firm advantage over our Hundred Creations Mountain for all these years. I'm afraid their objective for coming here is most likely identical to our own," Huo Yuan replied.

"You're saying they're here for that thing as well?" Chi Meng exclaimed.

"I can't think of any other reason why they would've taken such a huge risk to come here. At the moment, it appears that the distraction tactics that they've employed have worked perfectly," Huo Yuan mused.

"Mountain Master Huo, didn't you say that that thing was said to have been refined by your Hundred Creations Mountain? Do you really not know what it does?" Chi Meng asked.

"That thing was refined by my predecessor, the previous mountain master. It's said that the patriarch of Nine Origins Temple himself had personally requested its refinement for a very steep price, and it had taken tens of thousands of years to complete but it seems to be nothing more than an inanimate container with no apparent purpose," Huo Yuan sighed.

"I see. If this thing was refined hundreds of thousands of years ago, then why is it that you've only now suddenly expressed a desire to the Heavenly Court to investigate the object?" Chi Meng asked in a perplexed manner.

The reason why the Bodhi Token distribution process was made so complex on this occasion was precisely so that they could have an excuse to remain in the Nine Origins Temple for a while longer, thereby giving them the opportunity to uncover some answers.

"Back when the previous mountain master refined this item, he had also wanted to figure out its true purpose, but not only was he unable to uncover the answer, his obsession with the subject led to the emergence of inner demons in his heart and..."

Huo Yuan's voice abruptly trailed off here as a hint of resentment flashed through his eyes.

The previous mountain master had also been his master, and he had failed in his final corpse soul severance due to the hindrance posed by his inner demons. Otherwise, the Hundred Creations Mountain would've also had a Dao Ancestor at its helm, and its status in the True Immortal Realm would've been significantly elevated.

"Back then, the previous mountain master told me that the Nine Origins Temple has very big plans for this item, and he instructed me to keep a close eye on things. If the Nine Origins Temple ever decides to further refine the item into an immortal treasure, then I must find a way to uncover its purpose," Huo Yuan continued.

"What do you mean by further refinement?" Chi Meng asked.

"Back on our Hundred Creations Mountain, the item was only half refined. Essentially, it was a container filled with infinite possibilities. The Nine Origins Temple has been carrying out the rest of the refinement process in secret this entire time, and according to our estimates, the process should've been completed a few days ago," Huo Yuan replied.

"So you're saying that the Nine Origins Temple has been refining this item for hundreds of thousands of years?" Chi Meng exclaimed.

"On the cusp of the completion of the refinement process, some natural phenomena had been triggered, but they were quickly concealed by the Nine Origins Temple. However, the Heavenly Court also detected the phenomena, and that's why I immediately received a response when I proposed an investigation.

“I was supposed to have investigated this matter together with Immortal Envoy Feng Tian, but the Reincarnation Palace has spoiled those plans. Having said that, it's not exactly a bad thing to have them muddy the waters," Huo Yuan continued.

Chi Meng nodded in response, then turned to the direction that Wyrm 3 and the others had departed in as she asked, "Are we not going after them," Mountain Master Huo?

"Let's wait for a while longer. Spiritual sense is completely restricted here, but the woman wearing the veiled hat is giving off some very strange aura fluctuations, and she's most likely going to detect us if we get too close," Huo Yuan replied with a shake of his head.

Only after close to twenty more seconds had passed did Huo Yuan finally set off, with Chi Meng following along close behind.

......

All of a sudden, a dull thump suddenly rang out from beneath a fake mountain in another garden in the Nine Origins Palace.

The entire mountain was uprooted along with a large section of the ground around it, and several figures emerged from down below.

They were none other than Han Li, Lan Yan, Xiaobai, and Jin Tong, while Weeping Soul had returned to the Flower Branch domain to rest and recuperate, having severely exerted herself in the wake of the ordeal concerning the wicked corpse soul.

"Where are we right now? It feels like we're still in the Nine Origins Palace," Xiaobai mused with a concerned expression.

"Too much of the system of underground passageways has caved in, so there's no way for us to return the same way we came from. Hence, we have no choice but to return to the surface to look for a way out. Fellow Daoist Lan, do you know how we can leave this place?" Han Li asked.

"I've never been allowed entry into the Nine Origins Palace, so I'm afraid I don't know any more about this place than all of you do," Lan Yan sighed.

At this point, the transgressions she had committed against the sect were already punishable by death several times over.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he began scouring his gaze over his surroundings to try and find a way out.

"What are all of you looking so glum for? I can get us out of here!" Jin Tong declared in a confident manner.

Chapter 1248: Mad Dash

"You know the way out, Jin Tong?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I sure do! Back when I was being held captive in the Ghost Valley, I was taken here one time to see an old man," Jin Tong replied.

"Who is this old man?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know, but he seems to be very important in the Nine Origins Temple. Even Gui Lingzi had to bow in his presence. However, he was very nice and friendly, and he instructed Gui Lingzi to treat me well. Right after that, he went into seclusion, and I never saw him again," Jin Tong replied.

"Do you really know the way out?" Han Li asked in a skeptical manner.

"If you don't even trust me, then who can you trust?" Jin Tong protested in a displeased manner.

Before Han Li had a chance to respond, Xiaobai interjected in a distrusting manner, "Are you sure you know the way out, Boss? We were only intercepted by Gui Lingzi because you took us down the wrong path, leading to your capture. And before that, there was that time when..."

"What was that?" Jin Tong snapped in a threatening manner as she gave Xiaobai a firm slap to the head.

"Ouch! Nothing, I didn't say anything. Let's all do as you say, Boss," Xiaobai hurriedly replied as he massaged his own head.

"Seeing as Fellow Daoist Lan doesn't know the way out, either, we may as well let Jin Tong lead the way. If we encounter any Nine Origins Temple cultivators along the way, make sure to avoid battle as much as possible," Han Li said.

"You can all count on me!" Jin Tong said with a confident smile, then looked around momentarily before pointing in a certain direction.

"That way!"

With that, Han Li's group set off toward a dense forest with Jin Tong leading the way.

There weren't many buildings in the Nine Origins Palace, and the buildings that were present in the area weren't particularly grand or majestic, but they were laid out in a very meticulous fashion, connected by elegant walkways and separated by beautiful gardens.

Han Li's group passed through three gardens in a row without encountering so much as a single Nine Origins Temple cultivator.

As they emerged from the third garden, they spotted a lake that was teeming with mist and spiritual qi up ahead.

It was impossible to see through the mist to the other side of the lake, but the sounds of an intense battle could be heard ringing out on the opposite shore.

Han Li took a glance up at the sky to discover a golden light barrier overhead, which was trembling incessantly from repeated explosions.

"Is there something wrong, Fellow Daoist Han?" Lan Yan asked in an anxious manner.

"Boss led us the wrong way, didn't she?" Xiaobai asked in a despairing voice.

"You're really pushing your luck!" Jin Tong snapped as she gave Xiaobai another slap to the head, and the latter hurriedly lowered his head.

"No, this is the right way. The sounds of battle coming from the opposite shore indicate that there are Reincarnation Palace and Nine Origins Temple cultivators fighting on the other side, so we should be getting further and further away from the heart of the Nine Origins Palace," Han Li analyzed.

"See? I told you I was right!" Jin Tong said with a pleased smile.

"That doesn't necessarily mean we're going the right way, Master. What if the Reincarnation Palace cultivators have already stormed into the core region of the Nine Origins Palace? In that case, wouldn't we be heading directly into the fray right now?" Xiaobai countered.

"I think you really have a death wish today!" Jin Tong snapped in a furious manner, and Xiaobai hurriedly began begging for mercy.

"There's no way that the Reincarnation Palace forces could've gotten that so quickly. Besides, the restriction up above still hasn't been breached yet, so it's very unlikely that the battle is taking place in the core region of the Nine Origins Palace," Han Li said.

"You're right, Fellow Daoist Han. The Nine Origins Palace is the most important location in our temple, so if its defenses really have been breached, then the battle raging on the other side of the lake would be far more ferocious," Lan Yan chimed in in agreement.

"Let's go. We'll fly over this lake, then find a place outside the fray and try to leave the area encompassed under the light barrier from there. Once we've managed to do that, I'll be able to get us out of here with my lightning teleportation array," Han Li said.

With a plan established, the group immediately sprang into action, flying toward the other side of the lake.

In order to avoid attracting attention to themselves, all of them had concealed their aura and were flying along just above the surface of the lake, where they could use the mist hanging over the lake as cover.

The world's origin qi above the lake was so abundant that it resembled a high-grade spirit gathering array, and the mist was entirely formed by spiritual power that had crystallized into the form of tiny water droplets.

As Han Li and the others flew over the lake, the spiritual power droplets surged into their bodies without requiring any active effort from them to absorb them.

It was a blissful feeling akin to basking in a warm spring, and the fatigue that Han Li had accumulated from the previous string of battles was somewhat alleviated.

Right at this moment, a familiar voice rang out up ahead.

"Who are you?"

Immediately thereafter, a green figure appeared within the mist, and the entire surface of the lake was rapidly frozen solid, forming a thick sheet of ice.

The frozen mist up ahead receded to reveal a woman in a green dress, and Lan Yan hurriedly lowered her head in fear and guilt at the sight of her.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa's gaze roamed over Han Li's group, and a stunned and furious look appeared on her face as she exclaimed, "Han Li! How dare you hold Lan Yan hostage and trespass on our sacred Nine Origins Palace! And you've gone and released the Gold Devouring Immortal as well!"

Lan Yan was left in a state of exasperation upon hearing this. It seemed like Immortal Lord Miao Fa had automatically assumed that she had once again been taken against her will by Han Li.

"This Gold Devouring Immortal is my spirit pet to begin with, so I'm only taking back what belongs to me, and I'm leaving right now. How about you let us through, Fellow Daoist Miao Fa? That way, you'll be able to get back to dealing with those Reincarnation Palace cultivators. From the looks of it, they're about to break through the restriction soon," Han Li said.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa reflexively took a glance at the light barrier above upon hearing this, and a grim look appeared on her face, but in the next instant, she suddenly lashed out at Han Li, extending a palm toward him.

In the blink of an eye, six familiar rays of translucent light appeared around him, while something also seemed to have been in the process of settling above him.

Han Li instantly channeled his Reversal True Axis ability while grabbing onto Jin Tong, Xiaobai, and Lan Yan before shooting back in retreat, covering a distance of over a thousand feet in the blink of an eye.

A giant, hexagonal ice crystal had appeared directly above the spot where they had been standing just a moment ago, and it was giving off six rays of dazzling, blue light.

Those six rays of light formed six familiar, white, mirrored walls, but Han Li was already gone from between them.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa was clearly taken aback by the speed that Han Li had displayed, and only then did she notice the strides that Han Li had made in his cultivation base since their previous encounter.

"I'm not falling for the same trick again. We both have things that we're busy with, so I'll be taking my leave now."

Han Li had no intention of engaging in battle against Immortal Lord Miao Fa, so he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability again, vanishing from the spot in the blink of an eye.

However, just like during their first encounter, Immortal Lord Miao Fa had already encircled the entire lake in all directions with massive walls of ice.

Hence, Han Li had only flown less than two thousand feet when he was faced with one such wall of ice.

"Leave that to me!" Jin Tong yelled as she flew forward ahead of the rest of the group, and a layer of bright, golden light appeared over her body as she crashed straight into the wall of ice.

A resounding boom rang out as the entire wall of ice shuddered violently, and its center caved in significantly, while ring-shaped cracks instantly spread over the entire wall from the point where it had been struck by Jin Tong.

Immediately thereafter, the entire wall collapsed violently, and Han Li's group emerged from the other side before flying away in another direction.

"Get back here!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa yelled as she set off after Han Li.

A massive sheet of hexagonal ice had appeared beneath her feet, and it was gliding through the air at an extraordinary speed, carrying her in pursuit of Han Li's group.

Han Li had already released his time spirit domain, but he limited its size so that it only encompassed an area that was less than two hundred feet in diameter around him, just enough to encompass everyone so that he could use his time law powers to enhance their speed.

"Why are we running? Let's just turn around and take her out!" Jin Tong suggested.

"A mid-Great Encompassment cultivator is not so easy to kill, and if we’re caught up in a battle with her, we'll be sure to attract a lot of unwanted attention," Han Li said.

"Then what do we do now? We can't just keep running like this," Jin Tong said with tightly furrowed brows.

"Let's shake her off our trail first. Get ready!" Han Li said, and Jin Tong and Xiaobai immediately gave a collective, affirmative response, while Lan Yan was rather perplexed, unsure of what she was expected to get ready for.

In the next instant, countless arcs of silver lightning suddenly appeared around them, then became interwoven with one another to form a lightning array.

A resounding thunderclap rang out as Han Li and the others vanished from within the lightning array.

Chapter 1249: Someone Dearest to My Heart

Immortal Lord Miao Fa sped onto the scene, only to discover that Han Li and the others were nowhere to be seen, leaving behind only a scorched odor in the air.

A dark look flashed through her eyes as she continued in her pursuit.

Meanwhile, a silver lightning array appeared out of thin air above an octagonal pavilion deep within a dense forest close to a hundred kilometers away, and Han Li's group emerged from within it.

After taking a moment to steady themselves, they descended to the edge of the pavilion, where Han Li looked around momentarily to discover that there was only a small path leading to the point in the forest, and there were no auras of other people around.

"Jin Tong, can you tell where we are right now?" Han Li asked.

"Of course not! I didn't get to go on a scenic tour of this place, I was taken here as a prisoner! How am I supposed to know where we are right now?" Jin Tong grumbled.

"Perhaps we've already been teleported out of the Nine Origins Palace," Xiaobai said in a hopeful manner, and for his optimism, he received another slap to the head from Jin Tong.

"Take a look at what's above our heads!" Jin Tong snapped as she pointed up at the sky, where it could be clearly seen that they were still encompassed within the golden light barrier.

"This light barrier has isolated the entire area under it into an independent small world. Not only is my lightning teleportation array unable to teleport through it, my teleportation range has also been severely reduced."

"You see? We should've just taken out that wench and been done with it!" Jin Tong grumbled in an indignant manner.

"The ancestral hall of the Nine Origins Temple is in the Nine Origins Palace, and according to what we heard earlier, there's a very good chance that Daoist Master Chun Jun is stationed there. If we cause too much of a commotion and attract him to the scene, then we would be in dire trouble," Han Li said, and Jin Tong's indignation instantly died down upon hearing this.

"There's no point in arguing over something like this now, let's try to orient ourselves and continue looking for a way out. If the Reincarnation Palace forces are driven back, then it'll become next to impossible for us to escape," Han Li sighed.

"Indeed, time is of the essence," Lan Yan hurriedly agreed.

Given the multiple major transgressions that she had committed, she could no longer remain in the Nine Origins Temple. At this point, all she could do was flee the sect, then find a way to go into hiding in a secluded lower realm with Lan Yuanzi.

"How are we supposed to find a way out if we don't even know where we are right now?" Jin Tong asked.

"It's fine. I made sure that we were teleported westward by the array, so all we have to do is make our way back eastward, and we should be able to get back to familiar territory," Han Li said.

"As expected of Master's brilliant foresight," Xiaobai praised.

"Why does it feel like you've become more of a sycophant since I last saw you?" Jin Tong asked as she approached Xiaobai with a threatening aura.

Xiaobai immediately backed away in a wary manner as he denied, "Not at all, Boss!"

With Han Li leading the way, the group traveled eastward, and after a few minutes, he suddenly raised a hand, gesturing for everyone to stop.

After that, he began listening intently for something.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Han?" Lan Yan asked in an anxious manner.

Han Li remained silent as he continued listening for a moment longer, then explained, "It sounds like there's a large-scale battle taking place in the far distance up ahead, so we'll have to take a longer route and skirt around them."

"Really? Why can't I hear anything?" Jin Tong asked, and Lan Yan and Xiaobai immediately chimed in in agreement.

Han Li was rather perplexed to see this, but it then quickly dawned on him that this had to have been a result of the peculiar changes that had taken place in his body following his wicked corpse soul ordeal.

"In any case, let's go southeastward for now to make sure that we give them a wide berth," Han Li said, and with that, the group set off again.

However, they soon encountered several streaks of light flying through the forest in the opposite direction, followed by a group of around a dozen pursuers.

Han Li and the others completely concealed their auras as they carefully cast their eyes toward the streaks of light, upon which they discovered that it was a group of Reincarnation Palace cultivators being pursued by a collection of core elders and disciples of the Nine Origins Temple.

Han Li was surprised to discover that the two figures at the forefront of the Reincarnation Palace group were none other than Wyrm 3 and Wu Yang.

Trailing along right behind them was a man wearing a rabbit mask and a woman with a veiled hat on her head, both of which struck Han Li as somewhat familiar, but they were out of sight before Han Li had a chance to get a closer look at them.

As for the one that was bringing up the rear, he had made no attempt to disguise himself, and there was a casual smile on his face as he occasionally unleashed an attack or two to impede their pursuers.

It was none other than Lu Chuanfeng, and Lan Yan was stunned to see that the Reincarnation Palace cultivators had already infiltrated the Nine Origins Palace.

Han Li and the others were only able to catch a fleeting glimpse of them before they vanished out of sight.

After waiting for a moment, Han Li prepared to set off again, but right at this moment, he suddenly detected a burst of familiar aura fluctuations up ahead, and his entire body instantly stiffened as he stopped cold in his tracks.

The image of the woman wearing the veiled hat resurfaced in his mind, and his heart began to race.

Is it her? Is it really her?

He turned to the direction that the Reincarnation Palace cultivators had departed in, seemingly transfixed.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Han? We have to go!" Lan Yan urged.

Jin Tong was also very surprised. He had never seen such a complex mixture of emotions on Han Li's face, one that encompassed excitement, befuddlement, reminiscence, and many more unidentifiable emotions...

"There's something that I have to confirm, so I'm not going to leave for now," Han Li declared with a serious expression.

"What? Why?" Lan Yan exclaimed in shock.

"It's a private matter of mine, and it's a long story. If you don't wish to remain here, then this is where we part ways," Han Li replied in a concise manner.

Lan Yan hesitated momentarily in contemplation, then replied, "I was hoping to be able to repay you for everything that you've done for me and my brother, but it seems like the best way for me to repay you right now would be to leave so that I'm no longer a hindrance to you."

"Lan Yuanzi's soul has already mostly recovered. You can enter the Flower Branch domain now, and Weeping Soul will tell you what more needs to be done on your end," Han Li said, then swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light.

Lan Yan extended a grateful curtsey toward him before stepping into the Flower Branch domain.

"Why have you suddenly decided to stay, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked.

"I sensed the aura of an... acquaintance among those Reincarnation Palace cultivators. It's very different from when I last saw her, but even if it's not her, it's definitely someone with some type of connection to her," Han Li replied.

"Who is she? It must be someone very important to you for you to be willing to take such a huge risk," Xiaobai said.

"She's someone dearest to my heart," Han Li replied with a faint smile, while Jin Tong's eyes widened in shock.

Once again, Han Li was displaying an expression that she had never seen before.

"In that case, let's go after them and take a look," Jin Tong said.

Right at this moment, two more streaks of light suddenly flashed past overhead, and Han Li hurriedly looked up to discover that it was Huo Yuan and Chi Meng.

However, both of them also seemed to have had their attention focused on Wyrm 3 and the others, so they failed to notice Han Li's group down below.

"Why are they here as well?" Xiaobai asked once the two of them were far away in the distance.

"It looks like they're following Wyrm 3 and the others, but they don't appear to have any intention of helping the Nine Origins Temple cultivators. Instead, it seems like they have some type of ulterior motive," Han Li mused.

All of a sudden, he seemed to have been alerted by something, and he swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light, out of which Lan Yan emerged with an uneasy look on her face.

"Ready to go?" Han Li asked.

"Yes. Words cannot express my gratitude to you, Fellow Daoist Han," Lan Yan replied as she extended another grateful curtsey.

"It's fine," Han Li said with a wave of his hand. "Just keep going in the original direction that we were traveling toward, and you should be able to reach the edge of the Nine Origins Palace."

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Han. May we meet again," Lan Yan said in an earnest manner.

Chapter 1250: Second Battle Against Miao Fa

Following Lan Yan's departure, Han Li didn't immediately close the door of silver light.

Instead, he turned to Jin Tong and Xiaobai and said, "Now that we're no longer in a hurry to leave, you two can go into the Flower Branch domain for now. It'll be easier for me to act on my own."

Neither of them raised any objections, and two of them proceeded to enter through the door of silver light one after the other.

However, Xiaobai had only just entered the Flower Branch domain when a resounding boom rang out from behind him, and the door of silver light was closed before Jin Tong had a chance to make it inside.

"What's going on, Master?" he hurriedly asked through voice transmission, but received no response.

Meanwhile, the entire area around Han Li and Jin Tong had already been transformed into a world of snow and ice.

The two of them had sprung up on top of a pavilion, while the ground below was covered in a thick layer of ice with countless ice spikes pointing directly up at the heavens.

"She sure is stubborn!" Jin Tong grumbled.

"It looks like a battle is going to be unavoidable," Han Li sighed as he peered deep into the forest, where all of the trees up ahead had already been frozen solid and were in the process of disintegrating into icy powder.

The crumbling trees disintegrated to open up a wide path, revealing a woman in a green dress seated atop a crystalline, lotus flower throne that was racing through the air like lightning.

It was none other than Immortal Lord Miao Fa.

"I've already surrounded this entire area with my spirit domain, let's see how you get away now!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa yelled as she drew to a halt in mid-air around a thousand feet away.

"Your sect is currently under attack from the Reincarnation Palace, so why insist on coming after us when there are so many bigger fish to fry?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"Don't you worry about that. None of those Reincarnation Palace scoundrels will be allowed to get away! I'm going to capture you first so I can find out what all of you are plotting!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa replied in a cold voice.

"You sure talk big for an old hag! Who the hell do you think you are?" Jin Tong yelled as she bared her sharp teeth, while the killing intent in Immortal Lord Miao Fa's eyes only became more pronounced upon hearing this.

"Sheesh, you look even uglier when you're angry!" Jin Tong jeered. "Who gave you the courage to come out and embarrass yourself like this? My uncle's going to do you a favor by teaching you a lesson so you can take a good look at yourself!"

"To think that a pair of early-Great Encompassment Stage juniors would dare to display such insolence to me! I bet you two aren't even aware of the massive gulf that exists between early and mid-Great Encompassment cultivators," Immortal Lord Miao Fa sneered.

"Looks like she doesn't know what happened to Gui Lingzi, Uncle," Jin Tong chuckled through voice transmission.

"That's good news for us. We don't have much time, so we have to take her down as quickly as possible," Han Li replied.

He snapped his fingers as he spoke, conjuring up a golden spirit domain that encompassed the entire surrounding area in a radius of dozens of kilometers, within which the flow of time instantly slowed down.

In the next instant, he stepped forward, and the pavilion beneath his feet instantly collapsed.

Han Li vanished from the spot amid the wreckage of the pavilion, and in response, the crystalline throne beneath Immortal Lord Miao Fa began to glow radiantly at her behest, following which hundreds of flower-petal-shaped bursts of translucent light came shooting out of it in all directions.

Han Li had only just emerged behind her when he was met with a torrential barrage of translucent light, which was giving off a glacial aura that instantly froze the space around him solid.

Even though he had managed to detect that something was amiss, he was still just a split-second too late to retreat, and one of his calves was instantly frozen solid.

The pillar of ice that had taken shape around his calf was unexpectedly heavy, and it dragged him down like a dead weight, sending him plummeting toward the ice spikes below.

He twisted around in mid-air before throwing a punch downward, unleashing a burst of tremendous force that completely pulverized a large section of the ice spikes on the ground while also propelling him back up into the air.

Immediately thereafter, a silver flame erupted out of his calf, quickly melting away the pillar of ice.

However, right at this moment, a massive, hexagonal ice crystal suddenly appeared above him, and it released six rays of radiant, blue light, forming six white, mirrored walls that formed an encirclement around him.

Han Li couldn't help but throw a hand to his own forehead in dismay upon seeing this. He had just declared earlier that the same trick wasn't going to work on him twice, yet here he was, falling prey to it again.

Each of the mirrored walls displayed a reflection of Han Li, and each reflection had a different expression on their face.

As opposed to lashing out right away, Han Li summoned an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword with a flick of his wrist.

The sword wasn't reflected in the mirrors, and Han Li was very happy to see this.

It seemed that these illusory mirrors were only able to reflect him, but not his treasures.

With that in mind, he swung the sword through the air, unleashing a flurry of golden lightning, which came together to form a golden lightning dragon that circled around him once before rising up into the air.

The six reflections around him also sprang into action, but they had no swords in their hands, so each of them swung a fist at him instead.

In the same instant, Han Li took on his devilish deity form with three heads and six arms, then blocked all six oncoming attacks with his hands and claws.

Before the reflections had a chance to attack again, a resounding boom rang out as the golden lightning dragon crashed its way through the hexagonal ice crystal above.

The ice crystal instantly lost two of its six corners from the force of the collision, sending it flying back through the air, and the six mirrored walls around Han Li faded away, while Immortal Lord Miao Fa looked on with a stunned expression.

During their previous encounter, Han Li had been completely powerless against this ability of hers, yet on this occasion, it was barely able to trap him for even a second.

However, she remained unfazed as she stood up from her lotus flower throne, and she stepped out into the air, while the crystalline throne descended onto the ground below.

With a flick of her wrist, a blue longsword that was around three feet in length appeared in her grasp, and it seemed to have been an immortal treasure of quite a high caliber.

"Where's your little friend? Get her to come out as well so I don't have to hunt the two of you down separately!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa declared in a cold voice, but she received no response.

"Please don't scare Jin Tong, she's very timid and gets frightened easily," Han Li said, and Immortal Lord Miao Fa's eyelids twitched slightly upon hearing this.

Jin Tong had ventured into the Nine Origins Temple to kill a Gold Devouring Immortal, and she had constantly been causing trouble during her imprisonment. If she could be referred to as timid and fearful, then it would be a struggle to find anyone that could be referred to as courageous.

"No matter. If she doesn't want to come out, then I'll just have to make her," Immortal Lord Miao Fa said with a cold smile, and as soon as her voice trailed off, her longsword flew out of her grasp before rising up into the air.

Immediately thereafter, she made a rapid string of hand seals, and a cloud of glacial mist instantly came descending from the heavens.

As soon as the cloud of mist descended upon Han Li, a layer of white frost instantly took shape over his sword-wielding hand.

He looked up into the sky to discover blue light flashing like lightning within the glacial mist above, and in the next instant, countless streaks of blue swordlight came raining down from the heavens in a torrential barrage.

In response, a burst of immense time law powers surged out of Han Li's body, and a bright moon rose up into the air behind him, releasing countless rays of golden light that caused everything in the surrounding area to fall into a stagnant state, including the vast cloud of glacial mist.

However, the streaks of blue swordlight hadn't been slowed down at all, and it seemed as if they were impervious to the effects of Han Li's time law powers.

Han Li immediately activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes, upon which he discovered that the glacial qi released by the streaks of swordlight had frozen the space around them solid, granting them a protective barrier that kept Han Li's time law powers at bay.

In the blink of an eye, the storm of swordlight was already upon him, and Han Li had no choice but to swing his sword upward in retaliation.

A massive whip of golden lightning erupted out of the tip of his sword, and as it was swung through the air, it formed a dazzling, golden arched bridge that managed to ward off all of the descending streaks of swordlight.

A string of resounding booms rang out as the storm of blue swordlight bombarded the golden arched bridge, and finally, the assault became too much to bear as even the bridge of lightning was frozen solid before shattering into countless pieces.

Without the golden bridge standing in their path, the storm of blue swordlight came crashing down with unstoppable power, completely destroying the ground below.

As the storm of swordlight continued to fall, layers upon layers of blue ice began to accumulate over one another on the ground, reaching over a hundred feet tall.

However, Immortal Lord Miao Fa quickly noticed that Han Li was nowhere to be seen.

Chapter 1251: Chaotic Battle

Right at this moment, Immortal Lord Miao Fa shuddered as she violently threw up a mouthful of blood while stumbling forward in an involuntary manner.

The storm of blue swordlight falling from the heavens abruptly ceased, while the cloud of glacial mist also dissipated.

Before she had a chance to steady herself, a burst of silver flames suddenly erupted out of her lotus flower throne, forming a giant, fiery lotus flower that threatened to devour her whole.

Thankfully, she reacted very quickly, moving over a hundred feet to the side in the blink of an eye to just barely evade the silver flames.

The fiery lotus flower transformed into a silver fire raven that came swooping directly at her, and she hurriedly raised a hand to summon her blue immortal sword back into her grasp.

However, what came flying toward her was not just her sword, but also Jin Tong, who was grabbing tightly onto the hilt of the sword.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa was astonished to see this, and Han Li pounced on the opportunity to appear behind her in a wraith-like manner before piercing his sword through her chest.

Countless arcs of golden lightning erupted out of the chest and back, causing her to let loose an agonized howl, while her complexion also turned deathly pale.

"You thought Jin Tong was hiding underground, so you descended to the ground as well, but she was actually lurking up in the air this entire time," Han Li revealed.

"Impossible... How did she seize control of my Profound Frost Immortal Sword?" Immortal Lord Miao Fa exclaimed as blood trickled down from the corner of her lips.

"You can have this crappy sword back for all I care! It's so cold and hard and not delicious at all!" Jin Tong scoffed as she tossed the sword down by Immortal Lord Miao Fa's feet.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa looked down at the sword, and she was distraught to discover that a chunk of its blade was missing, looking as if it had just had a bite taken out of it.

"Damn, that thing is cold!" Jin Tong complained as she rubbed her frozen hands together with a disdainful expression.

"I was too complacent this time, but I'll make you pay for what you've done to me a hundred times over the next time we meet!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa spat through gritted teeth.

Immediately thereafter, her entire body turned to ice, freezing Han Li and his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword within it.

A burst of radiant, blue light then appeared at the center of the ice sculpture before erupting in all directions, sending countless particles of blue ice sweeping through the air in all directions like a fierce snowstorm.

A long while later, all of the blue ice crystals finally settled, and the entire surrounding area had already been transformed into a world of snow and ice.

Han Li and Jin Tong scoured their surroundings to discover that Immortal Lord Miao Fa had already vanished, along with her lotus flower throne and Profound Frost Immortal Sword, and a disgruntled look appeared on Jin Tong's face as she yelled, "I can't believe we let her get away!"

"It's fine, we didn't want to engage her in a prolonged battle to begin with. You did very well to drive her away so quickly," Han Li said with a smile as he reflexively reached out to pat Jin Tong's head, only to sheepishly withdraw his hand as it dawned on him that Jin Tong was no longer the little girl that she once was.

An amused grin appeared on Jin Tong's face at the sight of his embarrassed display.

"Alright, you can go rest in the Flower Branch domain as well. I'm going to focus my attention on pursuing Wyrm 3 and the others," Han Li said.

"Who knows where they could be by now?" Jin Tong groaned.

"It's fine. They were being pursued by Nine Origins Temple cultivators the entire time, so I'm sure there would've left a trail of battle behind, and all I have to do is follow that trail," Han Li said.

After sending Jin Tong into the Flower Branch domain, Han Li concealed himself using his black Reincarnation Palace mask, then set off after Wyrm 3's group.

The two groups of cultivators up ahead hadn't made any effort in concealing their tracks, so following them proved to be quite an easy task, and before long, he had arrived near a palace, within which the sounds of a fierce, ongoing battle could be heard.

Han Li was just about to approach the palace gates to take a look inside when his expression suddenly changed slightly, and he ducked behind a large rock, then cast his gaze toward the two stone pillars in front of the gates as he activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

There was a transparent, humanoid figure pressed against each of the stone pillars, and they were none other than Chi Meng and Huo Yuan.

At the moment, both of them had their attention focused on the scene unfolding inside the palace, so they failed to detect Han Li's arrival.

Of course, the concealment effect of his black mask also played a role in their failure to sense his presence.

Han Li took a glance at the two figures in hiding, then sank silently into the ground before slowly moving toward the palace, and it didn't take long before arrived at its gates.

From this position, he was able to see a fierce battle taking place in the palace between two parties, one of which consisted of Wyrm 3's group of five, while the other was comprised of Daoist Master Chun Jun and the two assistant abbots, Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun.

Daoist Master Chun Jun was locked in battle against the man wearing the rabbit mask, while Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun were seated in a giant array, within which was a golden altar with numerous golden giants that were dozens of feet tall standing around it.

These golden giants were clad in suits of armor and wielding massive, bladed weapons, with which they were unleashing long streaks of golden light while drawing upon the power of the surrounding array.

These streaks of golden light weren't all that remarkable in appearance, but they were were imbued with tremendous metal-attribute law powers, and the golden giants were able to hold their own just fine against Wu Yang, Lu Chuanfeng, Wyrm 3, and the woman in the veiled hat.

Hovering above the golden altar was a radiant, golden cloud that seemed to have been harboring some type of treasure, but the cloud was too bright for observers to catch a clear glimpse of whatever was inside.

Furthermore, the cloud was constantly moving like a living creature, giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations while also occasionally releasing bursts of golden light that were imbued with incredibly sharp metal law powers.

All of a sudden, the cloud turned an earthy yellow color, and the law power fluctuations that it was giving off also turned to that of the earth-attribute, causing the surrounding space to tremble violently, as if it couldn't bear the yellow cloud's enormous weight.

In the next instant, the cloud turned a lively green color while giving off tremendous wood law power fluctuations, instantly filling the entire palace with exuberant life energy.

From there, the cloud transitioned through two more different colors, namely crimson and blue, before restarting the cycle anew.

The five Reincarnation Palace cultivators were staring intently at the cloud above the altar, unleashing various types of attacks while converging toward the altar from all directions.

All the while, the Nine Origins Temple trio were resisting with all their might.

The battle had already reached white-hot intensity, but the palace was clearly bolstered by extremely powerful restrictions, allowing it to withstand the shockwaves from the battle.

What kind of treasure is in that cloud? It contains five different types of law powers! Han Li thought to himself with a stunned expression.

The higher the caliber of an immortal treasure, the more emphasis had to be placed on the purity of the law powers that it contained.

The treasure in the cloud was giving off extremely formidable aura fluctuations, surpassing even those of his Eon Divine Lamp, and somehow, it contained five types of law powers.

With that in mind, he projected what he was seeing into the Flower Branch domain, then asked Jin Tong, Weeping Soul, and Xiaobai if they had ever seen a treasure like this.

Jin Tong and Weeping Soul were also both stunned to see this, and they shook their heads to indicate that they had never seen anything like this, while a thoughtful look had appeared on Xiaobai's face.

"Do you know something, Xiaobai?" Han Li asked upon noticing his expression.

"While inheriting my father's bloodline power, I also inherited some of his memories, and there are memories of him and His Majesty, Bai Ze, attempting to refine an immortal treasure that was also supposed to contain multiple different types of law powers. Unfortunately, it ultimately ended in failure, and I can't find any further details on the matter in my father's memories," Xiaobai replied, and Han Li nodded in response.

He observed the cloud for a moment longer before turning his attention to the ongoing battle in the palace, focusing mostly on the woman wearing the veiled hat and the man with the rabbit mask on his face.

The woman had revealed the full extent of her early-Great Encompassment Stage cultivation base, and there was a layer of dark red light over her body, but it was split up into six layers of varying tones, like the spectrum of a rainbow.

She was wielding a dark red mirror immortal treasure as she fought against four or five of the golden giants, and the mirror was capable of releasing astonishingly powerful beams of dark red light that were able to vanquish the streaks of golden light unleashed by the golden giants with ease.

Even though there were several golden giants opposing her at once, she had still managed to gain a firm upper hand.

She's using reincarnation law powers! Han Li observed.

However, her reincarnation law powers were completely different from those wielded by Wyrm 3.

Wyrm 3's reincarnation law powers were extremely unyielding and aggressive, while this woman's reincarnation law powers were more mellow and versatile.

Wu Yang, Lu Chuanfeng, and Wyrm 3 were also all putting their abilities on display, gaining steady upper hands over the rest of the golden giants.

However, the golden array around the altar was extremely profound, and it was connected to the Nine Origins Palace, granting it a virtually limitless source of metal law powers. Hence, even though the Reincarnation Palace cultivators were all in advantageous positions, they remained unable to vanquish the golden giants.

Chapter 1252: Stalemate

All of the battles raging in the palace were spectacles to behold in their own right, but the most intense one was between the rabbit-masked man and Daoist Master Chun Jun.

Daoist Master Chun Jun wore a solemn expression, and there was a layer of golden light around her body, while countless almighty sword projections were swirling around him.

The rabbit-masked man was surrounded by black shadows that were constantly shape-shifting like a kaleidoscope as they converged toward Daoist Master Chun Jun from all directions, and all of the sword projections that came into contact with them instantly faded into nothingness.

A hint of recognition flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

"Shi Kongmo! Are you trying to start another war between the Devil Realm and our Nine Origins Temple?!" Daoist Master Chun Jun roared in a furious voice.

"I don't care about that, I'm looking for my wife and son! You're not half bad, but you still can't hold a candle to me, so hurry up and lay down!" the rabbit-masked man chortled as he swept both sleeves through the air, conjuring up a spirit domain that was around a hundred feet in size.

A surprised look appeared on Daoist Master Chun Jun's face upon hearing what Shi Kongmo had to say, but before he had a chance to respond, he was forced to deal with the oncoming spirit domain as he summoned his own golden spirit domain, but limited it to only around seventy to eighty feet in size.

Countless golden sword projections were flashing within his spirit domain, clashing against Shi Kongmo's kaleidoscope-like spirit domain, and the nearby space was shattered violently with an earth-shattering boom.

So it really is him! Han Li thought to himself.

Somehow, Wyrm 3 had managed to convince Shi Kongmo to come here as an ally of the Reincarnation Palace.

But why is it that they've kept their spirit domains so small? Han Li couldn't help but wonder to himself.

"It's been a long time since I've had such a fine opponent!" Shi Kongmo chortled as he swept both sleeves through the air, and around a dozen black claw projections appeared within his spirit domain before making a grab for Daoist Master Chun Jun.

In response, Daoist Master Chun Jun made a hand seal, and all of the golden sword projections in his spirit domain instantly began sweeping toward the oncoming claw projections.

However, the claw projections seemed to have no substantial form, able to pass right through the golden sword projections before raking over Daoist Master Chun Jun's body.

Around a dozen gashes that were deep enough to expose bone were instantly sliced into his body, causing him to stumble back in retreat.

"Is that all you've got? How disappointing," Shi Kongmo scoffed with a disappointed shake of his head.

"Abbot Chun Jun!"

Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun were both very alarmed to see this, and they were momentarily distracted.

"Wyrm 3! Now!" Wu Yang yelled as his eyes lit up, and at the same time, he began making a rapid string of hand seals.

A Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him, while a golden spirit domain also took shape around him, with countless axial projections flashing within it.

Wyrm 3 was clearly aware of why she had been called upon, and she made a rapid string of hand seals herself to release her reincarnation spirit domain.

Their two spirit domains overlapped with one another, and both of them began to tremble and buzz, as if they were resonating with one another.

All of a sudden, a dark red wheel the size of a house appeared in Wyrm 3's spirit domain. There were six black holes on the wheel, and it was revolving rapidly while giving off a terrifying aura.

Wu Yang quickly descended beside Wyrm 3, and the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him shot forward at his behest, fusing as one with the dark red wheel in a flash.

The dark red wheel instantly swelled to around twice its original size, and a series of golden patterns appeared over its surface, giving off time law powers that resonated with the reincarnation law powers emanating from the wheel.

Han Li was rather surprised to see this.

He had thought that only his time law powers could resonate with Wyrm 3's reincarnation law powers, yet Wu Yang had been able to achieve the same thing.

Having said that, Wu Yang was also cultivating the Mantra Axis Scripture, so it made sense that their law powers would also be able to resonate with one another.

However, it seemed that the law resonance between the two wasn't all that coordinated, indicating that they were still not accustomed to working together in this fashion.

"Go!"

Wyrm 3 and Wu Yang thrust their palms forward in unison, and the dark red wheel instantly began rumbling toward the golden altar like an unstoppable cannonball.

A string of loud thumps rang out as several of the golden giants standing in the path of the dark red wheel were instantly pulverized upon contact.

All of this had unfolded in the blink of an eye, and Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun hurriedly turned their attention back to the task at hand.

Both of them were already at the late-Great Encompassment Stage, so under normal circumstances, it would've been virtually impossible for them to have been so distracted, but the influence of Shi Kongmo's inner demon law powers was clearly showing here.

Wyrm 3, Wu Yang, and the others were aware of the nature of Shi Kongmo's abilities, so they were carrying treasures that specifically protected them from such influences.

Under the collective efforts of Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun, the golden array around the altar lit up as countless golden runes surged out of the ground, significantly bolstering the golden giants within the array, both in terms of size and physical constitution.

Giant streaks of swordlight swept through the air, forming a huge, radiant, golden net in the path of the dark red wheel.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the wheel crashed into the net with unrivaled power, sending ferocious gusts of wind sweeping through the air, while the surrounding space became fractured with rifts.

The dark red wheel continued to spin like a giant millstone, while the golden net was trembling violently amid a cracking sound akin to that of shattering porcelain.

Even though Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun were aided by the array, they were still unable to oppose the might of Wyrm 3 and Wu Yang's law resonance.

The dark red wheel was only stopped in its tracks momentarily before continuing onward, easily destroying the golden net and golden giants up ahead before racing toward the golden altar.

It was too late for Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun to try and stop it, but for some reason, they didn't appear all that panicked.

Right as the giant wheel was about to crash into the altar, a spherical, black light barrier abruptly took shape around it, encompassing the entire altar within it.

The dark red wheel struck the black light barrier with a resounding clang, causing it to cave in slightly.

However, that was the extent of what the giant wheel was able to do, and it wasn't able to make any further advancements.

High up in the air above, Daoist Master Chun Jun sprang back in retreat before promptly devouring a crimson pill, and his injuries began to rapidly heal as he sneered, "I'll admit that your distraction tactics were executed very well, but your plans have been thwarted by this Profound Origin Dark Light Barrier! This restriction was set up by the Profound Origin Dao Ancestor himself, and it'll easily withstand any attack you throw at it!"

Triumphant smiles also appeared on the faces of Daoist Master Lei Jun and Yang Junzi, but right at this moment, Lu Chuanfeng suddenly appeared before Daoist Master Lei Jun without any warning.

Countless bursts of blue light erupted out of his body, with every single one of them giving off a glacial aura, and they came raining down upon Daoist Master Lei Jun in a torrential barrage.

A bone-chilling aura instantly filled the entire palace, causing everyone's teeth to chatter.

At the same time, Wu Yang abruptly appeared in front of Yang Junzi, then swung both hands through the air to send a barrage of golden palm projections crashing down upon him.

At the same time, Shi Kongmo had also suddenly ramped up the pressure against Daoist Master Chun Jun, forcing the latter into retreat.

Right at this moment, Wyrm 3 appeared near the altar in a flash, then flipped a hand over to produce an object before tossing it through the air.

From outside the palace, Han Li was able to identify the item as none other than that black metal tablet that Wyrm 3 had obtained from the Tai Sui Immortal Manor.

The composed look on Daoist Master Chun Jun's face instantly turned to panic upon seeing this, and he exclaimed, "That's the Profound Origin Black Tablet! How do you have that?!"

He immediately attempted to swoop down to intercept Wyrm 3, but of course, Shi Kongmo wasn't going to allow him to get away, conjuring up countless black, ghostly claws that came converging toward him from all directions.

Daoist Master Chun Jun had no choice but to stop and defend himself, while Lu Chuanfeng and Wu Yang were also going all out to keep Daoist Master Lei Jun and Yang Junzi occupied.

All of a sudden, Wyrm 3 opened her mouth to release a globule of blood essence, which instantly vanished into the black, metal tablet.

A ball of black flames instantly lit up over the tablet, and it elongated at Wyrm 3's behest, transforming into a fiery, black sword that was around ten feet in length before crashing down upon the Profound Heavenly Dark Light Barrier below.

The light barrier that had seemed nigh indestructible just a moment ago was suddenly made to appear extremely vulnerable, and a long gash was sliced into its surface.

Wyrm 3 flew in through the opening before reaching out to make a grabbing motion, and a huge, dark red hand projection appeared above the altar before grabbing onto the cloud hovering over it.

Daoist Master Chun Jun's trio were furious to see this, but there was nothing that they could do.

Chapter 1253: Another Replica?

However, right at this moment, the cloud that the dark red hand projection had closed itself around suddenly swelled to over ten times its original size, and a burst of fiery, red light shot out of it, almost tearing the hand projection apart from the inside.

Wyrm 3's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and she opened her mouth to release a ball of dark red light, which contained close to a hundred reincarnation law threads, all of which fused into the hand projection in a flash.

The projection instantly swelled by around twofold in size, and countless wheel-shaped runes emerged over its surface, while the light emanating from it had also become several times brighter.

A burst of unfathomable spiritual pressure erupted out of the hand projection, causing the space around the altar to ripple and sway violently, and it was able to close itself firmly around the cloud above the altar again.

However, before Wyrm 3 had a chance to celebrate, the cloud suddenly took on five colors at once, and all five types of law powers contained within it began to integrate and resonate with one another.

A resounding boom rang out from within the cloud, and the five-colored light erupting out of it transformed into a miniature, five-colored sun that instantly filled the entire space encompassed within the Profound Heavenly Dark Light Barrier.

The five-colored light began to revolve like a windmill, slicing visible gashes into the surrounding space.

The dark red hand projection was sliced to shreds with ease, and Wu Yang hurriedly called out in alarm, "Get back, Jiuzhen!"

Wyrm 3's expression also changed drastically as she shot back in retreat while sweeping a sleeve through the air, and a small, black flag appeared in her grasp before transforming into a black light barrier in front of her.

At the same time, she also flipped her other hand over to summon a silver jade ruler, which released a burst of silver flames to form another layer of projection.

These two protective barriers had only just taken shape when the revolving blades of five-colored light descended upon them, and the pair of barriers were able to hold themselves intact for an instant before they were completely torn apart.

Thankfully, by then, Wyrm 3 had already escaped from the opening in the Profound Heavenly Dark Light Barrier.

However, before she had a chance to catch her breath, bursts of five-colored light came crashing into the Profound Heavenly Dark Light Barrier from the inside.

For all its external sturdiness, it appeared that the light barrier was very easy to damage from the inside, and countless cracks instantly appeared over its surface, following which it exploded violently, sending devastating waves of five-colored light flooding through the entire palace.

Shi Kongmo, Daoist Master Chun Jun, Wu Yang, and the others were all swept up by the waves of five-colored light, sending them crashing heavily into the surrounding walls of the palace.

Wyrm 3 was situated closest to the eruption of five-colored light, so she was met with the brunt of the impact, and her entire body was embedded into the wall as blood came gushing out of her mouth.

The woman in the veiled hat was standing further away from the altar, so she was less affected, and even though she had also been sent flying, she was able to quickly steady herself.

However, in the process, a corner of the veil hanging down from her hat was lifted, revealing half of her face.

Outside the palace, Han Li's entire body instantly stiffened as he stared intently at the woman.

The eruption of five-colored light didn't rage on for much longer before fading away, and peace and quiet was restored.

At this point, the entire altar had already completely vanished, leaving only a pile of rubble behind, while the five-colored cloud above the altar had also disappeared.

A loud clang rang out as a small ball of five-colored light fell onto the ground near the entrance of the palace, and it contained a fist-sized, five-colored little vial with some floral patterns etched onto its surface.

An incredulous look appeared on Han Li's face as he discovered that aside from its color, the vial was identical to his Heaven Controlling Vial.

Could it be that this is another replica?

Ma Liang had also had a Heaven Controlling Vial replica in his possession, and given the Nine Origins Temple immense power and resources, it certainly wasn't out of the question for them to create another one.

However, this vial was far more powerful than the Heaven Controlling Vial replica that had been in Ma Liang's possession, and it wasn't even inferior to the actual Heaven Controlling Vial by much.

The woman in the veiled hat just so happened to have been knocked back to near the entrance of the palace, and she immediately pounced at the vial in an ecstatic fashion.

At the same time, she swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of dark red light that shot forth toward the vial, yet right as she was about to clinch it, an arc of purple lightning and a burst of crimson flames flew in from outside the palace to strike the streak of dark red light in unison.

The woman had clearly failed to anticipate this, and the streak of dark red light that she had released was torn apart with ease.

Immediately thereafter, Huo Yuan and Chi Meng appeared.

The arc of purple lightning split up into a pair of purple lightning pythons at his behest, each of which was several dozen feet in length and around the same thickness as a human leg.

One of them pounced at the woman in the veiled hat, while the other wrapped itself around the burst of crimson flames like a constricting serpent.

At the same time, the second lightning python opened its mouth to blast forth an arc of purple lightning at the five-colored vial that had fallen onto the ground.

"How dare you!" Chi Meng yelled in an enraged manner as she opened her mouth to release a burst of crimson flames, which transformed into a fiery, crimson net that encompassed the purple lightning python within.

The purple lightning released by the lightning python was also ensnared by the fiery, crimson net, and the two clashed violently against each other.

At the same time, Chi Meng swept a sleeve through the air to release her Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome, which came descending directly down upon Huo Yuan.

A dark look appeared on Huo Yuan's face as he slapped a palm to his own forehead, and a complex, purple lightning rune instantly surfaced over his glabella.

Two small balls of purple lightning shot out of the lightning rune, then swelled rapidly to the size of wagon wheels, and as soon as they came into contact with each other, a purple lightning cloud that was hundreds of feet in diameter instantly took shape amid an earth-shattering thunderclap.

Countless arcs of purple lightning were flashing erratically within the cloud, and it was as if a lightning deity had descended.

The purple lightning cloud clashed against the Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome with a deafening boom, and a stalemate ensued between the two, with neither one able to get the better of the other.

Even though the two of them had traveled here together, it was every man for themselves now that such a precious treasure was on the line.

After evading the oncoming purple lightning python, the woman in the veiled hat summoned her antiquated, dark red mirror again, and a beam of dark red light shot out of its surface before shining down upon the head of the purple lightning python.

The lightning python instantly exploded, while the woman in the veiled hat abruptly vanished from the spot before closing in on the small vial on the ground in a stealthy fashion.

"You're not fooling anyone!" Chi Meng snapped as she made a hand seal, and two of the fiery dragons on her Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome opened their mouths in unison, releasing two plumes of fire that sped directly toward the woman in the veiled hat, incinerating all of the space in their path.

Huo Yuan also pointed a finger in the woman's direction to send a torrent of purple lightning surging toward her, clearly having also seen through her attempt at self-concealment.

In spite of the formidable attacks directed at her, the woman in the veiled hat was determined not to back, and she sped up en route to the five-colored vial while opening her mouth to release a globule of blood essence that fused into her antiquated mirror in a flash.

The instantly swelled to around twice its original size, and a series of wheel-shaped patterns appeared over its surface before rapidly revolving.

A beam of dark red light that was over ten times brighter than the previous one erupted out of the mirror, encompassing the two plumes of fire and the torrent of purple lightning within it.

The plumes of fire and the torrent of lightning were instantly stopped in their tracks before beginning to dissipate, but they did so very slowly, perhaps because the power they contained was excessively tremendous.

The woman in the veiled hat shuddered slightly, indicating that she was experiencing some type of physical toll, but she then took a deep breath to steady herself before continuing to charge onward, and in the blink of an eye, she was within three feet of the five-colored vial.

An urgent look appeared on Chi Meng's face upon seeing this, and she made a rapid string of hand seals, upon which her Nine Dragon Divine Fire Dome extricated itself from the purple lightning cloud before descending upon the woman in the veiled hat as a streak of crimson light.

The nine fiery dragons on the dome detached themselves before pouncing at the woman, releasing plumes of crimson flames from their mouths to strike the beam of dark red light that had shot out of her antiquated mirror.

The air temperature in the entire palace instantly swelled drastically like the interior of an active volcano, and Huo Yuan also directed his attention to the woman in the veiled hat as the purple lightning cloud descended from above at his behest.

Countless thick bolts of purple lightning came crashing down upon the beam of red light released by the antiquated mirror, and the beam of light quickly disintegrated, while the mirror itself also shattered into two pieces.

Chapter 1254: Face of Dreams

As the mirror shattered, an unnatural flush appeared on the woman's face, and she threw up a small mouthful of blood, following which her complexion turned deathly pale, indicating that she had sustained internal injuries from the damage to her bonded immortal treasure.

However, she didn't even bother to spare the mirror a glance as she reached out with her right hand, releasing a burst of dark red light to capture the five-colored vial and draw it into her grasp.

Chi Meng and Huo Yuan were furious to see this, and both of them made a string of hand seals to send nine fiery dragons and a vast torrent of purple lightning crashing down upon her from all directions.

Having already suffered severe internal injuries, the woman's legs involuntarily gave out from under her in the face of the immense pressure weighing down upon her, but she was still tightly clutching the five-colored vial in her right hand.

Wu Yang and Wyrm 3's expressions changed drastically at the sight of the dire situation that she was in, and they frantically flew toward the entrance of the palace to try and save her, but they were clearly too far away.

The veiled hat on her head had already been sent flying, fully exposing her face, and there was a look of despair in her eyes as she gazed up at the oncoming attacks.

Right at this moment, Han Li abruptly appeared before her amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, and with a sweep of his sleeve, a burst of golden light was released before flying through the air to settle above the woman's head.

From there, the golden light transformed into a golden cloud with countless runes dancing within it, encompassing both Han Li and the woman inside.

Everyone was very much taken aback by this turn of events, and immediately thereafter, the golden cloud was inundated by the fiery dragon and the torrent of lightning.

A deafening commotion rang out as all of the space within a radius of several hundred feet was torn apart, creating countless criss-crossing spatial rifts, while the surrounding world's origin qi also churned violently.

The entire palace swayed and quaked, while the golden light emanating from the walls and the ground flickered erratically, looking as if it could collapse at any moment.

A long while later, the storm of destruction finally subsided, and all of the spatial rifts quickly closed.

As the dust settled, it was revealed that the golden cloud had been reduced significantly in size, but it remained as intact and resolute as ever, much to the incredulity of Chi Meng and Huo Yuan.

They had gone all-out in that previous barrage of attacks, yet somehow, they hadn't even been able to breach that thin, golden cloud.

Right at this moment, two high-pitched shrieks rang out as two streaks of golden light abruptly shot forth toward Chi Meng and Huo Yuan, both of whom hurriedly sprang back in retreat in an alarmed manner.

The streaks of golden light made no effort to pursue them, immediately flying back to Wu Yang before vanishing up his sleeve, following which he descended near the golden cloud in the blink of an eye.

Wyrm 3, Lu Chuanfeng, and Shi Kongmo also arrived on the scene, forming a protective encirclement around the golden cloud.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to withdraw the golden cloud, and despite all of the people around him, his gaze was fully focused on the woman beside him.

"Wan'er..."

His usual, composed facade had completely disintegrated, leaving him looking dazed and vulnerable.

This was a face that he had seen countless times in his dreams, and it had become even more heartbreakingly beautiful than before.

In this moment, his mind was completely blank, and the only thing occupying it was the woman before him. He was overcome by the urge to reach out and cradle her in the palms of his hands, but he was also afraid that she would disappear at his touch, like a reflection in a pond of water.

An unprecedented emotion welled up in Han Li's heart, and all of a sudden, a certain bottleneck was shattered as his mental state evolved to a new level.

"Wan'er? Are you talking to me? Thank you for saving my life, but my name is Rushuang, not Wan'er," the woman said with a rather displeased expression at the sight of Han Li's blatant ogling, then rose to her feet and promptly devoured a red pill.

"Rushuang?"

Han Li was completely rooted to the spot upon hearing this.

"Thank you for saving Sister Rushuang, Fellow Daoist Han. What are you doing here?" Wyrm 3 asked, and she could also see that Han Li's behavior was rather abnormal.

Han Li took a glance at Wyrm 3, but offered no response to her question as he turned his gaze back to the self-proclaimed Rushuang.

A hint of disdain appeared on the woman's face as she ducked behind Wu Yang to avoid Han Li's gaze.

A twinge of pain spasmed through Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and he glowered at Wu Yang as his hands balled up into tight fists.

He was certain that there was no way he would mistake someone else for Nangong Wan.

He didn't know what Nangong Wan was doing here, how she had become a member of the Reincarnation Palace, or how she had already reached the Great Encompassment Stage, but he was confident that it was her.

Wu Yang's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of Han Li's hostile gaze, and he urged, "Now's not the time to be standing around, we have to go!"

However, as soon as his voice trailed off, the gates of the palace suddenly swung shut, sealing everyone inside.

Alarmed looks appeared on everyone's faces upon seeing this.

Chi Meng was situated closest to the gates, and she immediately made a hand seal, conjuring up a giant, fiery, crimson sword that struck the gates with tremendous power.

The fiery sword exploded into a crimson mushroom cloud, and the fire law powers imbued within erupted outward in a frenzy to try and blow the gates open.

A layer of golden light instantly surfaced over the gates, while the crimson mushroom cloud quickly faded away, and the gates were completely unscathed.

Chi Meng's expression instantly darkened slightly upon seeing this.

"The restrictions on those gates were personally set up by our patriarch. They take a long time to activate each time, but once they're activated, this palace may as well be an indestructible cage," Daoist Master Chun Jun declared with a cold smile as he swept an emotionless gaze over everyone present.

At this moment, Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun were standing behind him, with each of them holding a shimmering, golden tablet that was giving off waves of golden light.

The entire interior of the palace had also been enshrouded in a layer of golden light.

At this point, Han Li had already managed to compose himself, and a look of realization appeared on his face as he cast his gaze toward Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun.

No wonder the two of them had remained inside the array this entire time, their true objective had always been to activate the restrictions in the palace.

Judging from the effect that Chi Meng's attack had on the restrictions, or lack thereof, they were clearly extremely formidable.

Furthermore...

Han Li took a glance up at the ceiling with slightly furrowed brows.

As soon as he entered the palace, he had detected that the entire structure was enshrouded within a burst of invisible force, severely restricting one's ability to wield law powers.

This was most likely why Wu Yang and the others had only been able to conjure up such small spirit domains unbefitting of their Great Encompassment Stage cultivation bases.

With the restrictions in the palace activated, the restrictive force in the air had become even more potent, and this was undoubtedly going to be severely limiting on their powers.

Wu Yang and the others were looking around with grim expressions, while Shi Kongmo remained as casual and aloof as ever.

Daoist Master Chun Jun's gaze lingered on Han Li and the others for a moment, then shifted to Lu Chuanfeng as he demanded, "Lu Chuanfeng, how has the Reincarnation Palace convinced you betray the Heavenly Court and kill Immortal Envoy Feng Tian?"

"They didn't have to do any convincing, I've always been a member of the Reincarnation Palace to begin with," Lu Chuanfeng replied with a faint smile.

A surprised look appeared on Daoist Master Chun Jun's face upon hearing this, but it was then replaced by a cold sneer as he said, "I didn't think that the influence of the Reincarnation Palace would stretch so far and wide. I won't allow a single one of you to leave this place alive!"

"If you have what it takes, you're free to claim my head as you please!" Lu Chuanfeng chortled.

Daoist Master Chun Jun gave a cold harrumph, then turned to Chi Meng and Huo Yuan as he asked, "And what are you two doing here? Could it be that you also have ties with the Reincarnation Palace?"

"Of course not, Abbot Chun Jun. Mountain Master Huo and I only intervened because that vial was about to fall into the grasp of those Reincarnation Palace swine. We have not come here with any ill intentions," Chi Meng replied with a smile.

Chapter 1255: Invisible Hands

"That's right. Fellow Daoist Chi Meng and I spotted these Reincarnation Palace cultivators infiltrating the Nine Origins Temple earlier, and we knew they were up to no good, so followed them all the way here to try and uncover their objectives," Huo Yuan chimed in in support of Chi Meng.

Daoist Master Chun Jun naturally didn't believe them at all, but he didn't expose them.

Both Chi Meng and Huo Yuan were all but untouchable. Not only was Chi Meng a very important figure in the Heavenly Court herself, she also had Dao Ancestor Chi Rong as a backer, so even if she had admitted that she was also up to no good herself, Daoist Master Chun Jun wouldn't have dared to do anything to her anyway.

As for Huo Yuan, he was the master of the Hundred Creations Mountain, which may not have had a Dao Ancestor at the helm, but it had very close ties with the Heavenly Court. Over the years, anyone that had dared to make a move against the Hundred Creations Mountain had suffered very tragic fates, and at this point, it was common knowledge that the Hundred Creations Mountain was a subsidiary power to the Heavenly Court.

Given how delicate the situation was, Daoist Master Chun Jun knew that he had to proceed with caution. If he were to back these two into a corner and force them to join forces with the Reincarnation Palace, then the situation would take a drastic turn for the worse.

With that in mind, Daoist Master Chun Jun said, "Alright, in that case, please stand by and wait for now, and we'll let you go as soon as we've eradicated these Reincarnation Palace scoundrels."

Chi Meng and Huo Yuan were quite relieved to hear this, and they drifted over to a corner of the palace.

For all their status, they were still in the Nine Origins Temple at the moment, so if Daoist Master Chun Jun decided to take them down irrespective of consequences, then they would still be at his mercy.

"Mountain Master Huo Yuan, is that vial the item that was refined by the previous mountain master?" Chi Meng asked through voice transmission.

Now that the battle had temporarily died down, the animosity between them had also faded away.

"What our previous mountain master had refined was indeed a vial, but in the wake of the further refinement carried out by the Nine Origins Temple, it looks completely different from what it once did, so I was barely able to identify it," Huo Yuan replied.

"What do you think the Nine Origins Temple's intentions are for this treasure?" Chi Meng asked.

"Who knows what those sly old foxes are planning? Only by personally examining the vial will I be able to get an idea of what the Nine Origins Temple is plotting," Huo Yuan replied.

Chi Meng cast a contemplative gaze toward the Reincarnation Palace cultivators upon hearing this.

Meanwhile, Han Li's mind was racing as he tried to think of a way out of this dire situation.

He would definitely be able to save himself through transmigration, but for some reason, Nangong Wan had completely forgotten about him and was currently rather wary of him, so she most likely wouldn't be willing to go with him.

On top of that, Wu Yang, Wyrm 3 and the others clearly weren't going to allow him to abduct her, either.

With that in mind, Han Li cast his gaze toward Wu Yang, only to discover that the latter seemed to have been engaged in a conversation via voice transmission with Wyrm 3 and the others.

Han Li couldn't help but be annoyed to see this.

He was a member of the Reincarnation Palace, yet he was being blatantly excluded from the conversation, so they had clearly never truly regarded him as an ally.

Then again, he couldn't really complain, considering he had never truly considered them to be trusted allies, either, so the distrust went both ways.

The more he thought about it, the more he felt like ever since he joined the Blaze Dragon Dao, it seemed as if a pair of invisible hands had been molding his fate, pushing him in whichever direction they pleased.

This feeling had become even stronger after seeing Nangong Wan, and he felt like this was something that was worth looking into.

He was not someone who liked to be controlled, and he wanted to have a firm grasp on his own fate.

Daoist Master Chun Jun cast his gaze toward Wu Yang and the others, but before he had a chance to say anything, all of the Reincarnation Palace cultivators suddenly sprang into action at once.

Shi Kongmo and Lu Chuanfeng transformed into two streaks of light, one black and one blue, as they pounced at Daoist Master Chun Jun's trio, and Shi Kongmo flicked his fingers through the air in rapid succession to send dozens of black sword projections hurtling toward the trio.

Each sword projection was riddled with black, devilish eyes that were glowing with black light, presenting a very unsettling sight to behold.

Even as the dozens of sword projections were racing through the air, they produced no sound at all, and it was as if they possessed no substantial form.

Simultaneously, Lu Chuanfeng opened his mouth to release a ball of blue light while making a rapid string of hand seals, and a string of incantation seals flew out of his hands before vanishing into the ball of blue light.

The ball of light instantly exploded, forming countless thin needles of blue ice, and they shot forth through the air at his behest, raining down upon Daoist Master Chun Jun's trio in a torrential barrage.

Daoist Master Chun Jun remained completely unfazed by their attacks as he gave a cold sneer before raising both hands, and two bursts of golden light flew out of the palms of his hands before striking the palace walls on either side of him.

At the same time, rays of golden light also surged out of the tablets in the hands of Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun before also fusing into the surrounding walls.

The layer of golden light within the palace instantly began to ripple violently, releasing waves of obstructive golden light that swept toward Shi Kongmo and Lu Chuanfeng.

The barrage of ice needles unleashed by Lu Chuanfeng instantly vanished into thin air upon striking the waves of golden light, while Shi Kongmo's black sword projections were able to pierce through several layers of golden light in succession, but were quickly fading away in the process.

A surprised look appeared on Shi Kongmo's face upon seeing this, and he switched to a different hand seal, upon which the black sword projections transformed into thin, black threads that were able to pierce through the layers of golden light more efficiently en route to Daoist Master Chun Jun.

These black threads were also fading as they flew through the air, but at a far slower rate than the sword projections, and they reached Daoist Master Chun Jun's trio in the blink of an eye.

The three of them hurriedly sprang back in retreat, while Lu Chuanfeng swept both sleeves through the air to release huge chunks of blue ice the size of houses, all of which converged toward the trio like a barrage of meteorites.

It seemed that the golden light was far less efficient when it came devouring the spiritual power within substantial objects, and huge holes were blown into them by the chunks of blue ice, preventing them from closing in on Shi Kongmo and Lu Chuanfeng.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3, Wu Yang, and Rushuang had turned and rushed away in another direction, and at the same time, Wyrm 3's voice rang out in Han Li's mind.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I have a way to get us out of here, so please lend me your help!"

Han Li immediately followed along upon hearing this, and together, they descended in front of one of the walls of the palace.

Yang Junzi's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he pointed a finger at the wall in question from afar.

The golden light on the wall instantly brightened significantly, and countless giant, golden feelers erupted out of the wall before sweeping toward Han Li and the others.

"We need to buy some time for Jiuzhen!" Wu Yang yelled as he made a grabbing motion, and a giant, golden sword that was radiating dazzling, golden light appeared in his grasp.

With the swing of the golden sword, a streak of golden sword qi that was over a thousand feet was unleashed, striking around a dozen of the feelers at once.

Most of the feelers were instantly severed, but the streak of sword qi had also become far smaller and dimmer than before.

At the same time, the remaining, unsevered feelers quickly wrapped themselves around the streak of sword qi like a nest of spirit snakes, but the streak of sword qi was also like a living creature, darting around like a fish that had been caught in a net.

These feelers were extremely resilient, and they were also rapidly devouring the spiritual power imbued within the streak of sword qi.

As a result, the streak of golden sword qi rapidly shrank down before being completely fused into the golden feelers altogether.

"These feelers can devour immortal spiritual power and law powers, so be on your guards!" Wu Yang cautioned loudly as he swung his sword at another cluster of feelers.

Rushuang had also sprung into action, drawing a serpentine saber in the place of her broken mirror, and she slashed the saber through the air several times in succession, unleashing a barrage of dark red saber projections that instantly severed seven or eight feelers.

However, these golden feelers really did seem to be capable of devouring all things, and even these saber projections that were imbued with reincarnation law powers were no exception.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li raised his hands, and numerous profound acupoints lit up over his arms, causing them to swell drastically, while his fingers also elongated and thickened significantly.

He then flicked his fingers through the air in rapid succession, unleashing a barrage of blades of air that struck the remaining golden feelers, and they were torn apart without being able to pose any resistance.

Chapter 1256: Foiled Escape

It's just as I thought, these golden feelers can only devour energy, but are unable to effectively ward off physical attacks!

Those blades of air were essentially gusts of wind that he had conjured up with the tremendous strength of his fingers, and they contain no immortal spiritual power at all, making them the perfect counter to the golden feelers.

The other three Reincarnation Palace cultivators were quite surprised to see this, but Wyrm 3 then quickly turned her attention back to the task at hand as she swept a sleeve through the air to release a purple bead.

The purple bead swelled rapidly to the size of a millstone before striking the wall, where it then exploded into a body of viscous, purple liquid that clung to the wall and spread over an area that was around ten feet in size.

Wyrm 3 wore a focused expression as she cast a string of incantation seals into the purple liquid, and it immediately began to writhe like a living creature while giving off rays of purple light.

The golden light on the wall instantly vanished into the purple liquid, and it was clear that the latter also had the ability to devour spiritual power.

The purple liquid rapidly expanded as it devoured the spiritual power on the wall, but an exposed section of wall appeared at its center.

The exposed section of wall was completely devoid of spiritual power, having been stained a light purple color, and several cracks had also appeared on its surface.

"That's the Myriad Poison Dao Ancestor's Origin Devouring Poison Bead!" Daoist Master Chun Jun exclaimed upon seeing this.

"Did you think we'd venture so deep into the Nine Origins Temple without making any preparations?" Lu Chuanfeng chuckled.

Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun exchanged a grim look with one another, then immediately launched themselves at Wyrm 3 and the others.

"Get back here!" Lu Chuanfeng roared as a layer of bright, blue light appeared over his body, and he swept both sleeves through the air in unison to release two thick bursts of blue light.

A loud crack rang out as a massive, thick wall of blue ice appeared out of thin air, splitting the entire palace into two sections.

The Reincarnation Palace cultivators were on one side of the wall, while Daoist Master Chun Jun's trio and Chi Meng and Huo Yuan were on the other.

Lu Chuanfeng's complexion had turned deathly pale, indicating that conjuring up this wall of ice had been very taxing on him.

Yang Junzi was unable to arrest his own momentum, and he crashed heavily into the wall of blue ice with a resounding thump.

The wall didn't even shudder in the slightest, and it appeared to have been extremely sturdy.

Daoist Master Chun Jun and Daoist Master Lei Jun hurriedly manipulated the golden light in the palace to envelop the wall of ice and devour the spiritual power within, but this was clearly no ordinary wall of ice, and the golden light was only able to make very slow progress.

With the Nine Origins Temple cultivators trapped on the other side of the wall, Shi Kongmo and Lu Chuanfeng flew over to join Wyrm 3 and the others.

At this moment, Wyrm 3 was controlling the purple liquid while simultaneously sweeping a sleeve through the air, and a golden nail appeared before her.

The nail swelled rapidly to around ten feet in length and around the same thickness as a millstone at her behest, then shot forth as a golden shadow to strike the section of exposed wall at the center of the mass of purple liquid.

The nail was only able to pierce about half a foot into the wall before drawing to a halt.

This palace had also been constructed from Heavenend Gold Rock, and it was connected to the entire Nine Origins Palace. The purple liquid was only able to devour the spiritual power on the surface of the wall, but wasn't able to infiltrate any deeper than that.

Right at this moment, Wu Yang appeared behind the golden nail in a flash, then threw a bunch into its flat end with an almighty roar, while Lu Chuanfeng was keeping the surrounding golden feelers at bay.

A resounding thump rang out, and the nail was able to pierce about another half a foot into the wall, but it still wasn't able to punch through the wall.

"Impossible!" Wu Yang exclaimed as his eyes widened with incredulity.

"Get out of the way!"

Right at this moment, a burst of tremendous force swept through the air to send Wu Yang flying, following which Han Li appeared behind the golden nail.

All of his close to one thousand eight hundred profound acupoints lit up, and a burst of unfathomable power erupted out of his body, sending ferocious gusts of wind sweeping through the air in all directions.

A flash of realization appeared in the eyes of Chi Meng and Huo Yuan upon seeing this.

"Chang Qi was Han Li in disguise all along!" Chi Meng exclaimed, and Daoist Master Chun Jun immediately turned his attention to Han Li upon hearing this.

Han Li paid no heed to them as he let loose a low roar, and all of the starpower in his body was instantly condensed into his right arm as he threw an almighty punch into the flat end of the golden nail.

A deafening boom rang out as the nail punched through the wall in one fell swoop, following which Han Li unleashed another devastating punch, this one sending the golden nail flying altogether, leaving a huge hole in the wall.

However, Han Li was also knocked back by the force of the impact, only managing to steady himself after stumbling back close to twenty steps in a row.

......

Meanwhile, inside a room deep in the Nine Origins Palace.

It was a rather small room with very simple furnishings consisting only of some bamboo chairs and stools, and it appeared to have been a bedroom.

All of a sudden, a gray-robed elderly man appeared in the room.

It was a thin and short elderly man who wasn't dressed in Nine Origins Temple attire. Instead, he was wearing a coarse, linen robe, and his back was slightly hunched over, giving him the appearance of an unremarkable, old janitor.

The only thing worthy of note about him were his eyes, which were as sharp and bright as those of a hawk.

"I didn't think they would be able to breach the walls of the Bright Wheel Palace," he murmured to himself with a surprised expression.

"It's going to be nighttime soon, so it's about time this farce was put to an end," he continued as he took a glance up at the sky, then abruptly vanished from the spot.

......

Inside the palace.

"Let's go!" Wyrm 3 yelled as she immediately flew out through the hole in the wall, not even stopping to collect the purple liquid on the wall.

Wu Yang, Lu Chuanfeng, and Shi Kongmo immediately followed along close behind.

Rushuang was situated a bit further away from them, and she was just about to follow after them as well when around a dozen translucent spiritual sense chains suddenly appeared beside her before wrapping themselves around her body.

Those spiritual sense chains had come out of none other than Han Li's glabella.

"What the hell are you doing?" Rushuang roared in a furious manner, and Wyrm 3 and the others also hurriedly stopped in their tracks with alarmed expressions.

However, at this point, they had already flown too far away for them to be able to rescue Ru Shuang.

"I'm sorry, Wan'er, I don't know what happened to make you forget me, but I can't allow you to leave with those people!" Han Li said in an apologetic manner, then released several more spiritual sense chains, which vanished into Rushuang's consciousness in a flash, forming a spiritual sense cage around her soul.

Her struggles immediately ceased as a dazed look appeared in her eyes.

Han Li immediately raised a hand upon seeing this, intending to put her in his Flower Branch domain, but right at this moment, a burst of incredibly bright translucent light erupted out of her body before sweeping through the air in all directions.

The spiritual sense chains around her were instantly snapped upon contact with this burst of translucent light, and the spiritual sense cage within her mind was also broken.

Before Han Li had a chance to do anything, the waves of translucent light swept over him with tremendous force, sending him flying back through the air as blood came gushing out his mouth.

As soon as Rushuang was freed from her physical and spiritual restraints, the translucent light that had erupted out of her body instantly faded away.

"Are you alright, Rushuang?"

Wyrm 3 and Wu Yang flew back to her side and both of them were unable to contain their surprise, clearly indicating that they were also very much taken aback by what had just happened.

"I'm fine," Rushuang replied with a shake of her head.

"Alright, in that case, we have to get out of here!" Wu Yang urged as he flew away with Rushuang in tow, while Wyrm 3 took a hesitant glance back at Han Li.

However, with the golden feelers closing in yet again, she knew that there was no time to waste and promptly departed.

Daoist Master Chun Jun and the others were desperate to stop them, but powerless to do so from the other side of the wall of blue ice.

"You think you can get away that easily?"

Right at this moment, an elderly voice rang out, and it wasn't particularly loud, but it was filled with unmatched authority.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of golden light appeared in the palace without any warning, then instantly filled the entire palace, enveloping everyone within it.

Everyone was instantly rooted to the spot like flies in a piece of amber, and Han Li was no exception.

Even though he had just been sent flying, he hadn't sustained any major injuries, and at this moment, he was frantically channeling his time law powers and physical strength to resist against his restraints with all his might, but the golden light seemed to have been imbued with unfathomable power, rendering his struggles completely futile.

Wyrm 3 and the others had also been immobilized where they stood, and even Shi Kongmo was displaying a grim expression for the very first time.

Chapter 1257: Merciless

Right as Han Li and the others were immobilized by the golden light, a gray-robed elderly man appeared in the palace.

"Esteemed patriarch!"

Daoist Master Chun Jun's trio was ecstatic to see the new arrival, while Han Li and the others were far from pleased.

There was only one person that Daoist Master Chun Jun would refer to as "patriarch" in the entire Nine Origins Temple, and that was the legendary Nine Origins Dao Ancestor.

The gray-robed elderly man paid no heed to Daoist Master Chun Jun as he made a casual beckoning motion toward Rushuang, and the five-colored vial flew out of her storage ring before drifting toward him.

However, the space above the vial was abruptly torn open mid-flight, and a large, dark red hand shot out of the spatial rift to grab onto the vial.

The gray-robed elderly man's expression remained unchanged as he swept a sleeve through the air, conjuring a large, golden hand to grab down onto its dark red counterpart.

All of a sudden, the dark red hand made a hand seal, and six mysterious runes appeared around it, keeping the golden hand at bay for an instant.

The gray-robed elderly man's pupils contracted slightly at the sight of the six runes, while the dark red hand scooped up Wyrm 3's group in a flash.

A vortex then surfaced over the palm of the hand to suck in the group of five, following which the hand began to race toward Han Li in the distance.

A hint of fury finally appeared on the gray-robed elderly man's face upon seeing this, and he made a grabbing motion to summon a golden, metal whip that was giving off a boundless aura, and the whip lashed against the dark red hand with a flick of his wrist.

A dull thump rang out as the dark red hand exploded into a cloud of misty, red light, and a faint groan rang out from the space that it had previously occupied, seemingly an expression of pain.

The cloud of dark red light then instantly vanished into thin air.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and even Daoist Master Chun Jun hadn't been able to keep up with the sequence of events at all.

By the time he finally reacted to what had just happened, it was already all over.

The gray-robed elderly man observed the space where the dark red hand had emerged from in a displeased silence, but made no attempt to go after it.

Moments later, he swept a sleeve through the air, and the golden light in the palace rippled momentarily, causing the wall of blue ice to shatter into countless pieces.

The golden light then faded away, freeing everyone in the palace with the exception of Han Li, who remained completely immobilized.

Daoist Master Chun Jun's trio hurriedly flew over to the gray-robed elderly man's side before extending respectful bows, and Chi Meng and Huo Yuan did the same with uneasy looks on their faces.

"Chun Jun, I can see that you've done a fine job of looking after the temple," the gray-robed elderly man said in a clearly facetious remark, and his voice was filled with boundless authority.

"I was a fool to not have detected the Reincarnation Palace's plans earlier. I'm willing to accept any punishment handed down upon me!" Daoist Master Chun Jun said in a trembling voice as he kowtowed to the ground, and Yang Junzi and Daoist Master Lei Jun hurriedly followed suit.

"There are still outsiders present, so I'll address this matter later. The three of you can go now. Make sure to eradicate all of the remaining Reincarnation Palace cultivators in our temple," the gray-robed elderly man harrumphed coldly.

"Yes, esteemed patriarch!" Daoist Master Chun Jun's trio answered in unison before immediately departing.

"Sorry to have shown you such an incompetent sight," the gray-robed elderly man said as he turned to Chi Meng and Huo Yuan with a smile.

"Not at all, Senior. The Reincarnation Palace is a formidable entity that even our Heavenly Court must be wary of. With the exception of the Middle Earth Immortal Region, no other immortal region can hope to contend with it.

“It's clear that they've been plotting this invasion for a very long time, so it's already quite impressive that Fellow Daoist Chun Jun was able to organize such a spirited resistance on such short notice," Chi Meng said as he forced a smile onto her face, while Huo Yuan didn't even dare to speak.

"Is that right? In that case, perhaps I should reward him rather than punish him," the gray-robed elderly man chortled, and as his laughter reverberated throughout the palace, it grew louder and louder, resembling booming thunderclaps that caused the entire space to tremble violently.

Chi Meng and Huo Yuan began to tremble involuntarily, as did the souls in their bodies, and they hurriedly conjured up layers of protective spiritual light over their bodies to try and protect themselves, but it was completely futile.

Their souls continued to tremble more and more violently, resembling flickering flames in the wind that could be snuffed out at any moment.

Han Li's body and soul were also trembling violently, and his woes were further compounded by the fact that he was still completely immobilized and unable to adopt any protective measures.

Thankfully, his body and soul were both extremely formidable, so he was in no life-threatening danger for now.

Right at this moment, a burst of red light emerged over Chi Meng's body, instantly enveloping her and Huo Yuan.

The pained looks on their faces were instantly eased, and they began gasping for air with horrified looks in their eyes.

A projection of a red-robed elderly woman emerged from the red light.

"What's gotten you so worked up, Fellow Daoist Nine Origins?"

The elderly woman had a head of red hair that was no less vibrant than Chi Meng's, and despite her wizened, elderly appearance, it was clear that she commanded unfathomable power.

The gray-robed elderly man's laughter slowly subsided at the sight of the red-haired elderly woman.

This came as quite a relief, but at the same time, he was stunned to see the red-haired elderly woman.

Could she be another Dao Ancestor? She does bear a resemblance to Chi Meng... Could it be that she's Dao Ancestor Chi Rong?

"Chi Rong, may I ask who it was that instructed this granddaughter of yours to infiltrate my territory and steal from my Nine Origins Temple?" the gray-robed elderly man asked in a cold voice, confirming Han Li's suspicions on the woman's identity.

"It's all a misunderstanding, Fellow Daoist Nine Origins. Little Meng'er was instructed by the Heavenly Court to capture Han Li and a Gold Devouring Immortal, and she inadvertently stumbled into this place in the process. She had no intention of stealing that vial, she was merely curious about it. Surely you wouldn't be so petty as to get angry at a junior like her," the red-haired elderly woman replied with a faint smile.

"You think you can talk your way out of this? What do you take my Nine Origins Temple for?" the gray-robed elderly man snapped in a cold voice.

The red-haired elderly woman bristled slightly at the gray-robed elderly man's cold and unyielding demeanor, and she conceded, "I'll admit that Little Meng'er is at fault here. How do you want to settle this, Fellow Daoist Nine Origins?"

The gray-robed elderly man offered no response as he cast his gaze toward Chi Meng and Huo Yuan, and two beams of golden light suddenly shot out of his pupils toward the pair without any warning.

The red-haired elderly woman was furious, and she raised her cane to strike the beam of golden light that was hurtling toward Chi Meng.

The beam of golden light pierced through the cane in a flash, but it was whittled down significantly in the process, then vanished into Chi Meng's glabella.

Chi Meng immediately began howling in agony as she threw hands over her head, while the other beam of golden light shot into Huo Yuan's glabella before he had a chance to react at all.

His entire body shuddered violently, following which his head exploded like an overripe watermelon, and his headless body slumped to the ground.

The red-haired elderly woman hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of red light to envelop Chi Meng, and her agonized cries quickly died down.

The red-haired elderly woman was quite relieved to see this, following which she turned to the gray-robed elderly man with a furious expression.

"I'll spare her this time, but if she dares to try and cause trouble in my Nine Origins Temple again, then she won't get away with it so easily," the gray-robed elderly man sneered, then swept a sleeve through the air, and Chi Meng and Huo Yuan's headless body were instantly evicted from the palace, vanishing out of sight.

All the while, Han Li was looking on in complete astonishment.

The gray-robed elderly man appeared very easygoing and benevolent, yet his actions certainly belied that kindly appearance. Not only had he killed the master of the Hundred Creations Mountain, he had even taught Chi Meng a stern lesson in the presence of Dao Ancestor Chi Rong.

It quickly dawned on him that he was most likely going to follow in Huo Yuan's footsteps if he couldn't get away, and with that in mind, he began frantically thinking of ways to escape, but it seemed that his situation was simply hopeless.

Right at this moment, the Nine Origins Dao Ancestor slowly strode over to him with his hands clasped behind his back, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

Looking into his eyes, Han Li felt as if he were peering into a pair of bottomless wells.

The elderly man was in no hurry to speak, and he walked a lap around Han Li, seemingly sizing him up.

Han Li was feeling very uneasy under his probing gaze, and he felt as if the elderly man could easily glean all of his secrets if he so pleased.

Thankfully, the elderly man quickly averted his gaze, then casually swept a sleeve through the air, conjuring up a golden light barrier that encompassed the entire palace.

Han Li had seen many spirit domains in the past, but never had he witnessed one that had given him such a tremendous sense of pressure.

He was no longer able to see the surrounding wreckage as the entire space had transformed into a giant, opaque, golden ball that completely isolated the surrounding area.

Han Li quickly discovered that his connection to the outside world had been completely severed, and what was even more surprising to him was that even his connection with Jin Tong, Weeping Soul, Xiaobai, and even his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had also been severed by this spirit domain.

As for the unreliable vial spirit, it had gone mute once again, so Han Li's hopes of escaping this place via transmigration were completely dashed.

Chapter 1258: Severing Karmic Ties

After a long silence, Han Li was unable to suppress the mounting unease in his heart any longer, and he began, "Senior..."

However, as soon as he opened his mouth to speak, the elderly man reached out like lightning, making a grabbing motion toward his chest.

A strand of golden light appeared in the space in front of Han Li, then plucked out the Heaven Controlling Vial from beneath his robe before carrying it into the elderly man's grasp.

Han Li shuddered upon seeing this.

No one knew just what the Heaven Controlling Vial meant to him.

The Heaven Controlling Vial had left its mark on the entirety of his cultivation journey, from his time in the Seven Mysteries Sect in the mortal realm all the way until the present day. It was no exaggeration to say that without the Heaven Controlling Vial, he wouldn't be who he was today.

However, in the face of this elderly man, Han Li was like a child up against a mountain, and it was impossible for him to put up even the slightest resistance.

Given his physical prowess, time law powers, and tremendous spiritual sense, he was confident in his ability to oppose mid-Great Encompassment cultivators at only the early-Great Encompassment Stage, but Dao Ancestors were still simply way too far beyond his reach.

Han Li could only watch helplessly as the elderly man examined the Heaven Controlling Vial, stroking the patterns on its surface while his gaze roamed over it affectionately, as if he had just recovered a long-lost, treasured possession.

Some time later, there was suddenly a change in the look in the elderly man's eyes, but it then quickly returned to normal.

Han Li naturally didn't fail to notice this near-imperceptible change in his expression, and he couldn't help but wonder if the elderly man had been communicating with the vial spirit.

A short while later, the elderly man suddenly heaved a faint sigh before turning his gaze back to Han Li.

With nothing more than a blink of his eye, the restrictions weighing down upon Han Li were unraveled on their own.

Even though he had just been freed, Han Li remained tense and apprehensive as he stared at the elderly man in a cautious manner.

However, the elderly man then made a very surprising gesture.

With a casual toss, he threw the Heaven Controlling Vial back to Han Li, who caught the vial before looking back at him with a perplexed expression.

"From now on, the Heaven Controlling Vial will only become more and more intensely sought after. Losing it back then may not have been a curse, and recovering it today may not be a blessing. This treasure is too much for our Nine Origins Temple to bear, so if you wish to keep it, then go ahead," the elderly man said.

A peculiar look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this, but he strung the Heaven Controlling Vial back around his own neck without any hesitation before carefully tucking it down the front of his robe.

He had countless questions that he wanted to ask the elderly man, and he decided to ask the most pressing one: "Does this mean you're not going to kill me, Senior?"

"You may leave my Nine Origins Temple safely today. In fact, you will not be pursued by any cultivators of my Nine Origins Temple in the near future. However, after that, you'll still be a wanted fugitive, and if you dare to set foot in the Golden Origin Immortal Region again, then you will be hunted down," the elderly man replied.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li said, "I understand that I shouldn't ask too many questions at a time like this, but I would still like to know why you're letting me go, Senior."

"Some things were simply meant to be, and they cannot be altered, even separated by the cycle of reincarnation. Seeing as the Heavenly Dao has brought you before me today, it means that I am to repay you and sever our karmic ties," the elderly man replied as a reminiscent look appeared on his face.

Han Li was even more perplexed after hearing this, and he asked, "So what you're saying is that you owe me a favor, is that right, Senior?"

Han Li was confident that he had never met the Nine Origins Dao Ancestor before, and the disparity between their cultivation bases was night and day, so how could the elderly man possibly have been indebted to him?

"At your current cultivation base, you're still only able to see the trajectory of this lifetime, so even if I tell you about all of our karmic entanglements in the cycle of reincarnation, you wouldn't be able to understand. In any case, all you need to know is that once the favor has been repaid, our karmic ties will be completely severed," the elderly man replied, and it was as if a heavy weight had been lifted from his shoulders.

"Are you saying that someone once did something for you in a past life, and the soul of that senior went through the cycle of reincarnation to become me, so by repaying me, you're repaying that senior from that past life?" Han Li asked.

A look of surprise appeared on the elderly man's face upon hearing Han Li's deduction, but he didn't confirm nor deny this as he said, "Release that Gold Devouring Immortal. I want to speak to her."

As soon as his voice trailed off, Han Li discovered that his connection with Jin Tong had been restored.

After a brief hesitation, he did as the elderly man instructed.

Seeing as the elderly man had already spared him, he most likely wasn't going to harm Jin Tong, either.

Jin Tong appeared beside Han Li amid a flash of golden light, and as soon as she emerged, she immediately spotted the elderly man, upon which she exclaimed, "What are you doing here, old man?"

The elderly man seemed to have also been surprised by the sight of her, and he smiled as he remarked, "You've grown up so much in such a short time!"

"Uncle, this is the old man that I was telling you about," Jin Tong said as she turned to Han Li with a smile.

"Don't be so rude, Jin Tong! This man is the patriarch of the Nine Origins Temple!" Han Li hurriedly reprimanded, fearing that Jin Tong's brash words would land them in hot water.

The elderly man was completely unbothered, and he said, "Jin Tong, I've grown quite fond of you and would like to make an exception and take you under my wing as my disciple. Would you be willing to stay in my Nine Origins Temple?"

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this. He knew what it entailed to be taken under the wing of a Dao Ancestor, and he was just about to warn Jin Tong through voice transmission to consider the offer carefully when she immediately replied without any thought, "No way! I finally managed to escape from the Ghost Valley, I'm not going back there!"

"It'll be different this time. You'll become my disciple rather than a prisoner, and you'll be equal in seniority to Chun Jun. What do you say?" the elderly man offered again.

"I'm still going to have to pass," Jin Tong refused without any hesitation. "I really like you as well, old man, but I already have a master, and I don't plan to follow anyone but him."

"In that case, I won't force you. You can have this pill as a gift," the elderly man said as he flipped a hand over to produce a longan-sized, golden pill before tossing it at Jin Tong.

"Thanks, old man! You're a good person!" Jin Tong said with a wide smile as she accepted the pill, while Han Li looked on in a speechless manner.

Jin Tong was perhaps the only one in the entire True Immortal Realm who would dare to speak to the patriarch of the Nine Origins Temple like this.

"Alright, you two can go now," the elderly man said with a smile, then took a glance at Han Li before sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing a metal disk that descended to the ground before radiating bright, silver light.

A door of silver light immediately took shape over the metal disk amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, and within the door of light was a vast, blue sea.

"Let's go," Han Li said as he beckoned to Jin Tong, then began making his way toward the door of silver light.

Upon reaching the entrance, a thought suddenly occurred to Han Li, and he turned back around as he asked, "May I ask your name, Senior?"

"My name? It's been a long time since anyone has referred to me by name. My name is Li Yuanjiu," the elderly man replied, and Han Li was instantly rooted to the spot upon hearing this.

However, in the next instant, the elderly man swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a gust of wind that blew him and Jin Tong into the door of silver light.

Before Han Li had a chance to react, he was already standing on the vast sea, and the elderly man's authoritative voice rang out from behind him.

"Do not ever set foot in my Nine Origins Temple again. Farewell."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the door of silver light quickly faded away.

"What do we do now, Uncle? Where do we go?" Jin Tong asked as she scoured her gaze over her surroundings.

However, even after a long wait, she still received no answer from Han Li, and when she turned to check on him, she discovered that he remained standing rooted to the spot with a stunned look on his face, and it seemed that he hadn't heard her at all.

Indeed, at this moment, Han Li's mind was entirely occupied by the name "Li Yuanjiu".

During his first-ever bout of spiritual transmigration, he had possessed the body of an elderly daoist priest by the name of Ling Yunzi, and the name of his disciple had been none other than Li Yuanjiu.

Han Li still recalled that at the time, he had bestowed upon Li Yuanjiu the Provenance True Devil Arts and the Heavenbearing Devil Arts. Could it be that this was the favor that Li Yuanjiu had been repaying?

However, that seemed implausible to him. At his paltry cultivation base at the time, there was no way that Li Yuanjiu would've been able to see through his spiritual transmigration, so how could he possibly have made the connection between Han Li and Ling Yunzi?

However, it then occurred to Han Li that Li Yuanjiu had mentioned the cycle of reincarnation.

Chapter 1259: Counterfeit

Reincarnation was able to rank alongside space and time as one of the three paramount laws of heaven and earth, and it was the most mysterious of the three.

It was no exaggeration to say that all of the laws of heaven and earth were connected in some way to these three paramount laws.

Ever since ancient times, reincarnation had always been a very mysterious concept, and it concerned subjects such as rebirth and second lifetimes.

Of course, cultivators pursued immortality in the hope of being freed from the reincarnation, while mortals were inevitably bound to fall into the cycle upon their demise.

As for what one experienced after entering the cycle of reincarnation, it seemed that there was no consensus.

Han Li speculated that perhaps some of his residual aura had been left behind in the two cultivation arts that he had planted into Li Yuanjiu's consciousness all those years ago, and that had convinced him into thinking that he was the current incarnation of Ling Yunzi.

At the moment, Li Yuanjiu was a Dao Ancestor that even the Heavenly Court had to treat with respect, but it was clear that he still had a soft spot for the master that had taken him under their wing all those years ago.

With that in mind, it seemed like he had survived thanks to the designs of fate.

"What are you spacing out for, Uncle? Where are we going next?" Jin Tong asked as she tugged on Han Li's arm and began swinging it from side to side.

Only then did Han Li snap back to his senses, and he began inspecting his surroundings, but there was nothing to see aside from boundless ocean in all directions.

He then pulled out the map of the Nine Origins Temple that Lan Yan had given him before pressing it against his own glabella to inspect its contents.

Moments later, he concluded, "It looks like we're no longer in the Nine Origins Temple, but just to be safe, let's leave the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region as soon as possible."

With that objective in mind, he raced away in a certain direction with Jin Tong.

......

Several months flew by in a flash.

Inside a strange, murky, gray space, a beautiful woman in a long, azure dress was suspended ijn mid-air, flying in the upstream direction over a dark red river.

The woman was none other than Wyrm 3.

This was the first time that she had physically entered this strange space, and she was constantly being oppressed by the Great Dao of heaven and earth as she fought her way upstream.

There were five other rivers flowing along beside this one, and all of them were different in color and turbulence, but Wyrm 3 didn't even dare to look at them, let alone fly toward any of them.

After what felt like an eternity, Wyrm 3 had traveled several hundred kilometers, and she finally caught sight of the crystal arch bridge that stood at the origin point of the six rivers in the distance.

In contrast with last time, the woman in black sitting under the arch bridge was absent, leaving only the Reincarnation Palace Master seated on the bridge in his usual conical, bamboo hat and heavy bamboo fiber cloak.

He remained in the same posture as last time with his back slightly hunched, holding that bamboo fishing pole with the white spots on its surface. A translucent, dark red line was trailing down from the end of the fishing pole, while the other end of the line was submerged in the water.

"Wyrm 3 pays her respects to the esteemed palace master," Wyrm 3 greeted with a respectful bow upon arriving on the arch bridge.

"The fact that you were able to make it all the way here without any trouble despite this being your first physical transmigration tells me that you've made further strides in your cultivation base and mental state yet again. However, I can see that there's a faint mark on your glabella, indicating an injury. Why didn't you wait until after you were recovered before coming here?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked.

"It's just a minor injury," Wyrm 3 replied.

"Surely you've heard the adage of water dripping through stone. Multiple minor injuries accumulated over time and left unattended can result in catastrophic consequences. Do not underestimate the top brass of the Nine Origins Temple," the Reincarnation Palace Master said, then casually lifted his fishing pole, and the dark red line trailing down into the water below instantly sprang up with a loud twang.

Hanging from the end of the line was a translucent, dark red fish, and it sprang up into the air before launching itself directly at Wyrm 3's glabella.

Wyrm 3 instinctively stumbled back to take evasive measures, but then immediately stood still again, allowing the red fish to vanish into her glabella.

A layer of red light instantly surfaced over her forehead, and her face took on a bright red coloration, while translucent threads of red light could be seen roaming under her skin.

Close to twenty seconds later, the layer of red light gradually subsided, and she hurriedly extended a respectful bow as he said with an elated expression, "Thank you, Palace Master!"

The faint mark on her glabella had already faded away, and not only had she recovered from all of her injuries, she had also opened around a dozen immortal acupoints in that short span of time.

"How did it go?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked.

"We managed to secure it," Wyrm 3 replied in a concise manner.

She knew that was all that the palace master cared about, and he didn't care what had been lost to accomplish the objective.

Wyrm 3 flipped a hand over as she spoke, and the five-colored vial appeared over the palm of her hand, giving off bursts of formidable spiritual power fluctuations.

Only then did the Reincarnation Palace finally withdraw his fishing pole before rising to his feet.

While seated on the bridge, he had appeared rather diminutive in stature and hunch-backed in posture, but upon rising to his feet, he was surprisingly tall and imposing. However, even as he turned around to face Wyrm 3, his facial features were still concealed under the large hood of his cloak.

With a casual beckoning motion, the five-colored vial flew out of Wyrm 3's hand before landing in his grasp, while Wyrm 3 stood by to await further instructions.

After carefully examining the vial for a moment, the Reincarnation Palace Master suddenly erupted into laughter.

"What's so funny, Palace Master?" Wyrm 3 asked in a puzzled manner.

"As expected of the founding father of the Nine Origins Temple. You've all been fooled by Li Yuanjiu," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied as he casually tossed the five-colored vial back to Wyrm 3.

Wyrm 3 caught the vial with a hesitant look on her face, while the Reincarnation Palace Master explained, "That's nothing more than a counterfeit."

"Please forgive me, Palace Master, I didn't know," Wyrm 3 hurriedly said as she fell to her knees with a panicked expression.

"It's alright, you're not to blame. After all, I wasn't even able to tell you exactly what it is that you were to search for prior to the mission. This counterfeit Heaven Controlling Vial is exceptional in both craftsmanship and materials used, and it's comparable to a second tier immortal treasure, so it's no surprise that you were fooled," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

"Please give us another chance, Palace Master. This time, I'll be sure to return with the original," Wyrm 3 implored.

"After the huge mess that we caused this time, there's no way you'll be able to infiltrate the Nine Origins Temple again anytime soon. Besides, Li Yuanjiu personally appeared to confront you, yet you were all still able to make it back unscathed, and that's already a gesture of goodwill, one that we cannot repay with ingratitude," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

"You're saying Li Yuanjiu allowed us to get away on purpose? But why would he do that?" Wyrm 3 asked with a surprised expression.

"I can think of two potential reasons, the first of which is that perhaps he wants to show us that his Nine Origins Temple doesn't wish to be a sworn enemy of our Reincarnation Palace, while the second reason would be to prove his own innocence," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

Wyrm 3 immediately understood what the Reincarnation Palace Master was implying.

"The Heavenly Court sent both Huo Yuan and Immortal Envoy Feng Tian to investigate exactly what Li Yuanjiu had been refining over all these years, yet not only was Immortal Envoy Feng Tian killed by us, the vial was also taken by us right before everyone's eyes. That way, there would indeed be no reason for the Heavenly Court to suspect them of foul play."

"Li Yuanjiu is a very smart man. The Heaven Controlling Vial that was once in their possession was a priceless treasure that had been the envy of countless top-tier powers. In the wake of its loss, it seems to make sense that they would create a replica. Unfortunately for him, the Heavenly Court is not going to be so easy to fool," the Reincarnation Palace Master said with a smile.

"Palace Master, may I be so rude as to ask exactly what the Nine Origins Temple has created to have made even the Heavenly Court so apprehensive?" Wyrm 3 asked after a long hesitation.

The Reincarnation Palace Master merely shook his head with a smile and offered no response, and Wyrm 3 knew not to pry any deeper upon seeing this.

"Make sure that no information on this vial is leaked, and cease all of our activities in the Golden Origin Immortal Region. At the same time, stir up some more trouble in the neighboring immortal regions to divert attention away from the Golden Origin Immortal Region," the Reincarnation Palace Master instructed.

A perplexed look flashed through Wyrm 3's eyes upon hearing this.

"Regardless of what the Nine Origins Temple has created, as long as no concrete information on it is revealed, the Heavenly Court will only be able to make blind guesses, and the more they're forced to guess, the more of a wedge will be driven between them and the Nine Origins Temple," the Reincarnation Palace Master explained, and an enlightened look appeared on Wyrm 3's face upon hearing this.

"All we have to do is plant the seed of doubt, and it'll grow and thrive by itself. We don't have much time left, and there are still other things that must be done," the Reincarnation Palace Master continued as he cast his gaze toward the six rivers diverging away from the arch bridge.

Chapter 1260: Raised Flagon Mountain

The Chu Yu Immortal Region was a tiny immortal region neighboring the Golden Origin Immortal Region that was only around half the size of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. However, it was quite prosperous, thanks to its close proximity to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region.

Unfortunately, its tiny size limited the amount of resources that it was home to, so even though it frequently traded with other immortal regions, there was still yet to be a truly powerful sect to emerge within its borders. The two most formidable powers of the immortal region consist of a mountain and a palace.

Needless to say, the palace was naturally the Chu Yu Immortal Palace, while the mountain was Raised Flagon Mountain, the most powerful sect in the entire immortal region.

Raised Flagon Mountain was slightly more powerful than the Blaze Dragon Dao during the latter's heyday, and its patriarch and current mountain master were both High Zenith cultivators, joined by a large supporting cast of Golden Immortal.

The sect was rather interesting in that it didn't excel in cultivation, nor did it dabble in pill or tool refinement. Instead, it focused primarily on refining all types of immortal wines.

Most of the immortal wines produced by the sect could nourish one's body and soul, and there were even some special wines that could help cultivators overcome their five decays, thereby making them very highly sought after.

If that were the extent of it, then the immortal wines produced by the sect would only have been of interest to cultivators below the High Zenith Stage, but as it turned out, they were very popular among cultivators of the High Zenith Stage and even the Great Encompassment Stage.

The reason for this was that Raised Flagon Mountain had honed the art of wine brewing to the extreme.

The natural environment of Raised Flagon Mountain was also rather special. Its main peak was called the Jade Flagon Peak, and it resembled a giant wine flagon in shape. It was said that there was a wine cellar under the mountain, containing all types of fine wines brewed by the sect over the years.

The wine cellar in question was a natural underground cave, and it was a restricted area of the sect that was accessible only to the mountain master, the founding father, and several core elders.

However, unbeknownst to all of them, a cave abode had been sneakily dug out deep in the cellar, and there was a multitude of arrays set up around it, concealing everything within.

At this moment, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on a stone bed in one of the rooms of the cave abode, and he was wearing his black Reincarnation Palace mask while muttering something to himself.

However, he wasn't chanting an incantation or anything like that. Instead, he was purely complaining to himself.

Moments later, a disappointed look appeared on his face as he removed the mask, and Xiaobai immediately approached him before asking, "How did you go, Master? Did you manage to get into contact with her?"

"No. I don't know what's going on with Wyrm 3, but I haven't been able to get into contact with her at all over the past few months," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"Could it be that she failed to get away and was captured by the Nine Origins Temple?" Xiaobai speculated.

Han Li shook his head and offered no response. He had personally seen Wyrm 3 and the others get away. Even Li Yuanjiu hadn't been able to stop them, so they definitely hadn't been captured.

He was naturally attempting to contact Wyrm 3 in order to find out more information about Nangong Wan, but for some reason, she remained impossible to get in touch with.

All of a sudden, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he scoured his surroundings, then asked, "Where has Jin Tong run off to again?"

"Boss has probably gone to steal wine to drink again. The wine here really is something else," Xiaobai replied as he began to involuntarily salivate, while Han Li massaged his own glabella in dismay.

Raised Flagon Mountain didn't have much else going for it, but when it came to brewing wine, even Daoist Hu Yan would have to concede inferiority. Not only were there hundreds of different types of immortal wines stored in this cellar, there was a particular one by the name of Martial Empress that had been designed specifically for female cultivators.

Martial Empress didn't have a strong aroma like other immortal wines, but it was very clear in color and had a sweet and delicate flavor. On top of that, the wine placed the drinker into a blissful, half-asleep state, and that was what made it so popular among female cultivators.

Jin Tong had discovered this type of wine not long after arriving here, and it had instantly become her favorite.

Right as Han Li and Xiaobai were speaking with one another, Jin Tong stumbled into the room in an unsteady manner, carrying a black jar that was even larger than her own head, wafting out of which was a special, fruity, wine aroma.

"I'm back, Uncle," Jin Tong declared as she sat down onto the ground next to him with the jar of wine sitting on her lap.

"Haven't I told you that you can't go and steal any more wine?" Han Li scolded with a stern expression.

"I didn't steal any, all of the Martial Empress in here is mine. If you don't believe me, take a look," Jin Tong protested as she held up the wine jar in front of Han Li, revealing the characters for "Jin Tong" scrawled onto it in wonky text.

"You can't keep misbehaving like this! If the Raised Flagon Mountain cultivators catch you, then we're going to be exposed!" Han Li reprimanded in a displeased manner, snapping Jin Tong out of her drunken state.

"Fine, then let them expose us! I'm about to die of boredom here!" she retaliated, starting to get a little angry herself.

Han Li's demeanor softened slightly upon hearing this, and he sighed, "I know you don't want to stay here, but you've seen what's been happening of late. After what happened in the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, all of the nearby immortal regions have suddenly begun experiencing mass unrest. We had only just arrived in the Chu Yu Immortal Region when immortal envoys from the Heavenly Court arrived hot on our tail. If we go out now, only to be surrounded, then we'll be doomed."

"If you want me to be patient and wait, then you'll have to let me drink as much wine as I like," Jin Tong harrumphed coldly.

Before Han Li had a chance to respond, his expression suddenly changed drastically as a pillar of white light came crashing through the ceiling of the cave abode up above.

The entire Jade Flagon Peak shuddered violently as a massive crater that was over ten thousand feet in size was blasted into the eastern foot of the mountain, and the crater was perfectly filled by the pillar of white light crashing down from above.

There were five figures hovering around the pillar of light, one of whom had greenish-purple skin and an authoritative appearance that struck awe and veneration into the heart of the beholder. He was also very tall and imposing and clad in a suit of golden armor, giving him the appearance of a majestic, ancient god of war.

However, what was most astonishing about him was his late-Great Encompassment Stage aura.

There was a man and a woman standing on either side of him, and the man was very elderly in appearance with a wrinkled and wizened face, but there was a glowing, golden circle in each of his pupils. The woman appeared far more youthful, but she wasn't particularly beautiful, and the grim look on her face certainly didn't help her cause in that regard.

Both of them were wearing immortal envoy attire, and it was clear from their demeanors that they regarded the armorclad man as their leader.

Standing behind the trio was a thin elderly man with a rather red nose and a golden-robed middle-aged man, both of whom possessed far inferior auras to the trio.

The thin elderly man was stealing occasional glances down at the crater beneath the pillar of white light with a pained look on his face, while the golden-robed man remained silent, looking straight ahead with an indifferent expression.

They were the patriarch of Raised Flagon Mountain and the master of the Chu Yu Immortal Palace, respectively, and they should've been the two most powerful figures in this immortal region, yet they didn't even dare to breathe too loudly in the presence of the trio standing before them.

There were also several thousand people standing a short distance behind them, most of whom were local cultivators of the Chu Yu Immortal Region and elders and disciples of Raised Flagon Mountain.

Hovering above them were ten more Heavenly Court cultivators dressed in immortal envoy attire, and at the center of the circle formed by the ten cultivators was a round, silver mirror, which was the source of the pillar of white light that had blasted its way straight through the foot of the Jade Flagon Peak.

"Master Yue Qing, if you ask me, someone who's resorted to hiding in Raised Flagon Mountain has to be some small fry that wasn't able to get very far away. It's very unlikely to be the likes of Lu Chuanfeng or Immortal Lord Heavenly Star, so there was no need for you to come here in person," the female immortal envoy said to the armorclad man.

A hint of killing intent flashed through the man's eyes as he snapped, "Not only did Lu Chuanfeng humiliate our Heavenly Court by killing Immortal Envoy Feng Tian, he also forced me to come out of seclusion early to fill in for him as the Golden Origin Immortal Palace Master! Regardless if it's one of those two hiding here, all Reincarnation Palace scum must be eradicated!"

The armorclad man by the name of Yue Qing had previously been a divine official of the Heavenly Court, but he had been sent to the Golden Origin Immortal Palace from the Middle Earth Immortal Region in the wake of the tumultuous events that had unfolded.

He had been sent there to quell the unrest in the nearby immortal regions as soon as possible, as well as to secretly monitor the Nine Origins Temple and keep it in check.

As they were speaking with one another, a ring-shaped rune suddenly appeared over the silver mirror hanging high up in the sky, and the pillar of light shining down from it began to slowly shrink.

Before long, three figures were dragged out from underground by the pillar of white light.

Within the pillar of white light, Han Li hadn't bothered to adopt any disguise. After all, with Jin Tong and Xiaobai by his side, he wouldn't have been able to hide his own identity anyway.

The Heavenly Court cultivators were ecstatic to see him.

"It's Han Li!" one of the immortal envoys proclaimed in an elated manner.

"Pofeng, Wuhui, is this the one they call Han Li?" Yue Qing asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"That's right, Master Yue Qing," the female immortal envoy by the name of Pofeng replied.

Chapter 1261: Dire Urgency

"It looks like I made the right decision to come here," Yue Qing said, and his eyes began to light up more and more as his gaze roamed over Han Li's trio.

Others were perhaps able to see through Jin Tong's identity, but couldn't identify exactly what Xiaobai was. However, the same didn't apply to Yue Qing, and in his eyes, Xiaobai was perhaps the true big fish of the three.

The pillar of white light released by the silver mirror contained bursts of formidable spatial power, and Han Li's trio was completely immobilized within it, feeling as if they were being crushed under a mountainous weight.

"This man is far too powerful for us to oppose. I'm going to find a way to break this restriction, at which point we'll split up and get away individually. He's definitely going to come after me, so the two of you should be able to escape. Return to the primordial land and wait for me on Eight Plains Mountain," Han Li said through voice transmission.

"I'm sticking together with you, Uncle! These people can't beat us!" Jin Tong replied.

"I'm not going anywhere!" Xiaobai hurriedly protested.

"Senior Bai Ze only agreed for me to take you with me if I can guarantee your safety. If something happens to you, then I'll have failed to keep my promise," Han Li said, injecting more authority into his voice as he spoke.

"But..."

Xiaobai still wanted to protest further, but Han Li cut him off as he said, "Rest assured, as long as you two manage to get away, I also have a foolproof way to escape."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he closed his eyes and began channeling his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

"Looks like you plan to go down fighting, eh? How heroic!" Yue Qing sneered, and in the next instant, the silver mirror abruptly shuddered amid a rumbling thunderclap.

The ring-shaped rune on the mirror abruptly transformed into a lightning rune, and several thick bolts of purple lightning erupted out of it before crashing down upon Han Li's trio.

Countless tiny arcs of lightning were dancing around the bolts of purple lightning, filling virtually the entire pillar of light to make it impossible for Han Li's trio to take evasive measures.

Right at this moment, Jin Tong rose up into the air before raising her arms, and two bursts of translucent light that were as thin as cicada wings appeared above the trio, formed solely by her law powers.

Most of the lightning was kept at bay by the pair of wings, while the small amount that was able to slip through the cracks no longer posed any threat.

What everyone failed to notice was that Han Li had suddenly vanished from the spot.

Yue Qing was the first to notice, and by then, Han Li had already arrived directly below the silver mirror. He was holding an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword with golden lightning flashing all over its surface, and he swung the sword at the mirror with all his might.

However, right as he did so, the rune on the silver mirror transformed again, radiating blue light that gave off tremendous water law powers.

Han Li felt as if his sword had struck a vast sea, and his sword strike was instantly robbed of most of its power.

However, the silver mirror had also begun trembling violently as massive waves erupted over its surface, and powerful shockwaves were spreading in all directions, crashing toward the surrounding ten immortal envoys.

Most of the ten immortal envoys were at the early-High Zenith Stage with very stable cultivation foundations, but even so, they had become rather unsteady on their feet from the impact.

However, they still held a significant advantage, given that it was ten of them up against Han Li, and they also had the mirror on their side, so they were ultimately able to withstand the attack, but before they even had a chance to catch their breath, a burst of radiant, golden lightning erupted out of Han Li's sword.

A barrage of balls of golden lightning that were even more formidable than the purple lightning came crashing down upon the silver mirror, and thick arcs of golden lightning were sent sweeping through the air in all directions.

The ten immortal envoys were struck by the flailing arcs of lightning before they had a chance to take evasive measures, and they stumbled back through the air amid agonized cries.

In their sudden absence, the silver mirror fell out of the sky as all of the light radiating from it faded away.

However, Han Li didn't even have time to claim the mirror as he yelled through voice transmission, "Now!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he rose up even higher into the air in preparation to flee the scene, while Jin Tong and Xiaobai sped away in a different direction.

However, before they were able to get away, a figure appeared overhead before stomping a foot down upon them from above.

"You're not getting away!"

A thunderous voice rang out as Yue Qing's boot came stomping down with almighty power, and the entire space shuddered violently amid an earth-shattering boom.

Han Li felt a mountainous weight crash down on him from above, forcing him to plummet involuntarily back down onto the Jade Flagon Peak.

Violent tremors ran through the entire mountain, as if an earthquake were taking place, and all of the surrounding local cultivators and Raised Flagon Mountain disciples also came tumbling down from the heavens.

The patriarch of Raised Flagon Mountain had already preemptively retreated to over ten thousand feet away with the Chu Yu Immortal Palace Master, so he was able to remain steady in mid-air, but there was a pained look on his face as he observed the Jade Flagon Peak below.

A palace on the summit of the Jade Flagon Peak had already been completely razed to the ground, and Han Li was standing amid the rubble. He looked up to discover that Jin Tong and Xiaobai had also been intercepted by Pofeng and Wuhui, and not a single one of the three of them had been able to get away.

Right at this moment, Yue Qing descended from the sky and landed not far away from Han Li.

He hadn't unleashed any abilities, but just the physical impact of his landing was enough to make the entire Jade Flagon Peak shudder violently once again, a detail that hadn't escaped Han Li's notice.

"I can see that you're quite an accomplished Profound Immortal," Yue Qing remarked.

"You're far too kind, Senior," Han Li replied in a modest fashion.

"I wonder if you're as sturdy as you look," Yue Qing sneered as he stomped a foot down once again, and a yellow spirit domain instantly appeared to encompass close to half of the entirety of Raised Flagon Mountain.

Situated within the spirit domain, Han Li felt himself enveloped by a burst of suffocating earth law powers, and even the dust that had fallen upon him had become incredibly heavy, causing his feet to sink into the ground.

The patriarch of Raised Flagon Mountain heaved a forlorn sigh upon seeing this, and he knew that the destruction of his sect was inevitable, so he hurriedly began evacuating his disciples with the help of the sect's elders, while the Chu Yu Immortal Palace cultivators also evacuated from Raised Flagon Mountain.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li's trio and the Golden Origin Immortal Palace cultivators were the only ones left on Raised Flagon Mountain.

However, at this point, the ten immortal envoys had already retreated into the distance, taking no further part in the battle.

Han Li quickly checked on Jin Tong and Xiaobai to discover that the former was locked in a battle against the elderly man by the name of Wuhui, and the two of them appeared to have been quite evenly matched, while Xiaobai was clearly struggling against Pofeng.

Even though he had made significant progress in his cultivation base of late, he was sorely lacking in battle experience and was still yet to acclimate himself to his newfound power.

Right at this moment, a cold sneer rang out.

"I'd advise you not to get distracted when you're up against me!"

Han Li immediately summoned his time spirit domain to encompass the entirety of the Jade Flagon Peak upon hearing this, yet before his spirit domain had a chance to fully take shape, a figure had appeared behind him in a flash as if by instantaneous teleportation, then pressed a hand down onto his shoulder.

Han Li felt as if a mountain had come crashing down onto his shoulder, and a string of cracks and pops rang out from all of the joints in his body, but he was able to remain on his feet, refusing to collapse to his knees.

However, his entire body had sunk down even further, to the point that close to his entire lower body was now lodged in the earth.

At the same time, a ring of yellow light suddenly emerged from the ground beneath him, and he felt himself being dragged down even further by a burst of tremendous suction force.

In response, he let loose a thunderous roar while channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might, and all of his profound acupoints lit up in rapid succession, sending bursts of radiant starlight erupting out of the ground.

A burst of tremendous power surged out of his body, and the surrounding earth was violently shattered as he sprang up into the air before slashing his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in Yue Qing's direction, sending a net formed by countless interwoven arcs of golden lightning descending upon him.

A derisive sneer appeared on Yue Qing's face upon seeing this, and he casually flicked a finger through the air to release a burst of yellow force, which crashed into the net of golden lightning and tore it apart with ease.

Immediately thereafter, he made a beckoning motion, and a giant sword appeared in his grasp amid a flash of azure light. The blade of the sword was riddled with golden runes, and it was giving off bursts of mountainous sword qi.

With an almighty swing of his arm, the giant sword came crashing down upon Han Li from above, and it was accompanied by a burst of suffocating spatial pressure that compressed toward Han Li from all directions, making it impossible for him to take evasive measures, so he could only withstand the attack head-on.

He immediately switched to a two-handed grip on his sword and raised it horizontally above his own head, then simultaneously channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and true spirit bloodlines in unison, yet Yue Qing's giant sword had already crashed down upon him before he had a chance to adopt his devilish deity form.

Chapter 1262: Back Against the Wall

A sharp clang rang out as a streak of yellow swordlight erupted out of the giant sword, and it split up into two streaks of sword qi, one of which rose up into the air, while the other descended toward the ground.

The clouds up above were parted amid a burst of thunderous rumbling, and they surged to either side in a frenzy to create an enormous rift that was hundreds of kilometers wide, making it appear as if the entire sky had been sliced into two.

At the same time, the other streak of sword qi crashed down from the heavens to split the entire Jade Flagon Peak into two, leaving a bottomless trench running right down its center.

Han Li was situated at the deepest point of the trench, having fallen all the way into the underground cave cellar.

Countless jars of wine that had been stored in the cellar for countless years had been smashed open, and a rich, wine aroma wafted up into the air, making it seem as if the entire Jade Flagon Peak was a massive wine flagon that had been shattered.

Han Li was laying on the ground amid the wreckage in a spreadeagled pose, and his entire body was drenched in wine.

He struggled into a seated position as a sense of powerlessness welled up in his heart. A cultivator of Yue Qing's caliber was simply far too powerful for him to contend with, and even an escape was looking completely out of reach.

He had already attempted to call out to the vial spirit, but just like before, he received no response.

Right at this moment, a burst of tremendous pressure suddenly came crashing down as a vast expanse of yellow light filled the entire heavens.

Han Li looked up into the sky from the bottom of the chasm, and all he could see was a massive vortex of yellow clouds swirling up above, with the occasional flash of lightning visible within it.

With a sweep of his sleeve, thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords came flying out to surround him.

A resounding thunderclap rang out up above, and it was as if the entire sky had been blown open.

A rift abruptly appeared in the vortex of swirling yellow clouds in the heavens, and an incredibly thick pillar of yellow light came crashing down directly upon Han Li.

Han Li gritted his teeth tightly as he made a hand seal, and his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords quickly formed a protective circle around him.

Immediately thereafter, he let loose a low roar, and countless arcs of golden lightning sprang out of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in a frenzy, then came together to form a massive, golden wyrm that rose straight up into the air.

Han Li was situated within the body of the golden wyrm, enveloped by swordlight and sword qi as he crashed directly into the pillar of yellow light.

A string of deafening booms rang out as the pillar of yellow light was progressively torn apart by the golden wyrm, and Han Li was rising up higher and higher.

Before long, he had emerged from the chasm in the Jade Flagon Peak, and he looked up to discover Yue Qing standing up in the heavens with his giant sword, looking down with the cold detachment of an almighty deity.

Meanwhile, Jin Tong had already revealed her true Gold Devouring Immortal form, but she was currently trapped in a cage formed by the countless strands of Wuhu's horsetail whisk, and it didn't appear as if she would be able to free herself anytime soon.

In contrast, Xiaobai was going from strength to strength, perhaps because he was acclimating himself to his newly attained bloodline power as the battle wore on, and he had just devoured a blade of wind released by Pofeng's immortal sword.

Immediately thereafter, he opened his mouth again to send the same blade of wind hurtling back at Pofeng.

Both of them appeared safe for the moment, whereas Han Li was in a much more dire situation.

At his current cultivation base, he was still far from being able to match a late-Great Encompassment cultivator in battle.

Han Li heaved a forlorn, internal sigh at his current situation. Even if he could summon the vial spirit to transmigrate himself out of this pickle, he couldn't just abandon Jin Tong and Xiaobai to save himself.

Hence, he had no choice but to stand and fight.

With that in mind, a resolute look appeared in his eyes as he snapped his fingers, and the time law powers in his body surged forth in a frenzy.

All of a sudden, a lush mountain range appeared over the destroyed Jade Flagon Peak, and a river was flowing through it like a jade belt.

A hint of surprise flashed through Yue Qing's eyes upon seeing this.

"Given your relatively short cultivation career, it's already quite remarkable that you've been able to reach the early-Great Encompassment Stage, yet you've managed to attain a Oneness Tier spirit domain as well?" Yue Qing exclaimed.

His astonishment was very much warranted, given that both cultivation and the refinement of spirit domains were extremely time-consuming processes, it was extremely rare to see someone like Han Li, who had been able to make such extraordinary progress in both without either one lagging behind.

Right at this moment, the Mantra Treasured Axis rose up from the clouds behind him like a bright moon, and the golden light radiating from it instantly washed over Yue Qing's entire body.

In the blink of an eye, it was as if the surrounding space had been completely frozen, and even with Yue Qing's immense cultivation base, he was struck by a sense of asphyxiation.

I was too careless!

The thought had only just arisen in his mind when he discovered that even his thoughts seemed to have slowed down.

He hurriedly channeled his cultivation arts, and a ball of earthy, yellow light emerged over his chest, while his armor also began to glow radiantly, releasing formidable law powers to clash against the surrounding rays of golden light.

Even though that wasn't enough for him to immediately break free, at the very least, his thoughts were no longer impeded.

Pouncing on this opportunity, Han Li made a string of hand seals, and countless streaks of sword qi emerged beneath his feet, forming a vast torrent that elevated him up into the sky to face Yue Qing from afar.

From there, Han Li switched to a different hand seal, and the thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords down below instantly dispersed, spreading out around him like soldiers springing into formation.

The sound of sizzling electricity rang out as all of the swords swiveled around so that their tips were pointing up the heavens, and thirty-six incredibly thick pillars of lightning erupted into the heavens.

The pillars of golden lightning surged into the clouds beneath Han Li, which immediately began to churn violently like a pot of boiling water, and lightning was flashing incessantly within them.

At the same time, countless clouds were materializing out of thin air around Han Li before converging toward him to form a massive, golden cloud, and it stood in opposition to the yellow cloud around Yue Qing, with each one taking up half of the sky.

A pair of enormous, golden pillars emerged within the golden lightning cloud, and situated between them were two gargantuan, golden gates.

Han Li was standing outside the golden gates with his entire body basked in golden lightning, giving him the appearance of a golden deity tasked with guarding the heavenly gates.

All of a sudden, he joined his palms together in front of his own chest before raising his hands high above his head, and a burst of thunderous rumbling rang out as the golden gates behind him opened inward just a sliver to reveal a boundless sea of golden lightning inside.

In contrast with the last time these heavenly gates were opened, there was no vast outpouring of lightning. Instead, numerous fist-sized balls of golden lightning had taken shape above the sea of lightning.

These balls of lightning then drifted out of the opening between the pair of heavenly gates one after another, but instead of hurtling toward Yue Qing, all of them vanished into the center of Han Li's joined palms.

Before long, seven or eight balls of lightning had flown into the palms of his hands, and an irrepressible lightning aura was beginning to seep out from within.

As more and more balls of golden lightning entered the palms of Han Li's hands, rays of golden light began to spill out, and his face became more and more twisted with pain.

This is... a rather strange Almighty Sword Array...

Yue Qing was immediately able to identify Han Li's sword array, but at the same time, a hint of befuddlement had appeared in his eyes.

In the next instant, a sense of foreboding suddenly welled up in his heart, and he let loose a thunderous roar, upon which a series of golden runes emerged over his suit of armor to force back the rays of restrictive golden light around him.

Immediately thereafter, he grabbed onto the hilt of his sword with both hands before raising it in a slightly slow and arduous fashion.

In spite of the debilitating effects of Han Li's time law powers, Yue Qing took a step forward, striding toward Han Li while dragging his giant sword along by his side.

Images of seven misty mountains appeared over the blade of his sword one after another, and they were extremely vivid and lifelike.

At the same time, his aura began to become extremely heavy, and the yellow cloud around him began to rapidly shrink, forming a projection of a misty, yellow mountain behind him.

All the while, Han Li merely looked on with a cold expression.

Right at this moment, he brought his joined palms apart, and the golden lightning that had been suppressed between them for all this time was finally freed, forming a lightning longsword that fell into his grasp.

Han Li let loose a thunderous roar as he swung the sword viciously downward with both hands, unleashing a giant sword projection that was over ten thousand feet in length before sending it crashing down upon Yue Qing.

In response, Yue Qing slashed his giant sword upward, and a series of enormous mountain projections appeared out of thin air before crashing toward the golden sword projection crashing down from above.

The first mountain projection was shattered upon impact without being able to pose any resistance, and it was quickly followed by the second one.

Immediately thereafter, the third and fourth mountains were also completely pulverized.

A massive trench was sliced down the center of the fifth mountain, splitting it into two in a scene reminiscent of the fate suffered by the Jade Flagon Peak, but the golden sword projection was only able to cleave through the peak of the sixth mountain before its momentum was completely halted, and it became lodged in the sixth mountain.

The seventh mountain continued to rise up before crashing into the underside of the sixth mountain, and the force of the impact was transmitted into the golden sword projection, causing it to shatter into countless pieces.

Chapter 1263: Pushed to the Limits

Outside the heavenly gates, Han Li let loose an agonized cry as his entire body was flung up into the air, sending him crashing into the gates before sliding down in a defeated manner.

His sword-wielding hands had been stripped of all of their skin and flesh, reducing them to a pair of bone claws in a horrific sight to behold.

Meanwhile, Yue Qing had also withdrawn his giant sword, and five of the seven mountain runes on its surface had become rather blurry and indistinct, while the remaining two remained unscathed.

"I must admit that I'm rather impressed with how much of the Almighty Sword Array's power that you've been able to unleash," Yue Qing praised, and the derision in his eyes had been replaced with a look of appreciation.

"I haven't even been able to unleash a tenth of the Almighty Sword Array's power. Otherwise, you wouldn't even be standing here right now," Han Li said as he struggled to his feet before coughing up a mouthful of blood, while the skin and flesh on his hands began to regrow.

"I don't mean to brag, but if you had been restricted by my time law powers for just a little longer and allowed me to accumulate more power, then you may not have been able to withstand that last attack," Han Li continued as he casually stowed his completely spent Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords away, and the golden lightning cloud up above vanished alongside the golden heavenly gates.

"It appears that you've allowed my praise to get to your head," Yue Qing scoffed. "That was your final trump card, was it not? In that case, I suggest you surrender now to spare yourself of further punishment."

Han Li looked down at his own hands, which had already returned to normal, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he said, "I have one more trick up my sleeve. Would you like to see it, Senior?"

Yue Qing's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he was just about to respond when his expression suddenly changed slightly.

As it turned out, Han Li's spirit domain had remained intact this entire time, and the golden moon was still hovering behind Yue Qing, giving off waves of time law powers.

"I didn't think that this half-baked Oneness Tier spirit domain of yours would be this troublesome to deal with. Unfortunately for you, even if my cultivation base has been reversed by a million years, you're still no match for me," Yue Qing said in a cold voice.

"So you noticed right away. I intended to stall for a bit more time, but it looks like that's not going to happen," Han Li sighed.

"That's enough chit-chat! If you don't surrender now, then I can't guarantee that I'll be able to capture you without taking your life."

Ideally, Yue Qing still wanted to capture Han Li alive.

"If you want me to surrender, then I'll have to ask you to withstand one more attack from me," Han Li said with a smile.

As soon as his voice trailed off, thirty-six pillars of golden lightning suddenly erupted out of the wreckage of the Jade Flagon Peak down below, and a golden lightning cloud took shape again, while the golden heavenly gates also materialized for a second time.

A hint of surprise flashed through Yue Qing's eyes upon seeing this.

Back when Han Li had been crushed to the bottom of the Jade Flagon Peak by Yue Qing's earlier sword strike, he had already left his remaining thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords down there.

His original plan was to activate the second Almighty Sword Array as soon as the first one was was dispelled, using the element of surprise to strike him down in one fell swoop, but Yue Qing had displayed incredible power, and his forceful retaliation had caused Han Li to miss that opportunity.

Only after his hand had healed was Han Li able to make the hand seals required to activate the second sword array.

Standing outside the golden heavenly gates, Han Li joined his palms before raising them above his head once again, and a rumbling thunderclap rang out as the heavenly gates behind him began to open inward.

Just like before, balls of golden light drifted out of the heavenly gates before converging into palms of Han Li's hands.

A grim look surfaced in Yue Qing's eyes upon seeing this.

Even though he had been quite dismissive of Han Li earlier, in reality, he was quite wary of Han Li's Almighty Sword Array. Just as Han Li had said, if he had been allowed to absorb power from the sea of lightning within the heavenly gates as he pleased, then he really would've been capable of unleashing an attack powerful enough to pose a threat to Yue Qing.

With that in mind, Yue Qing naturally wasn't going to allow Han Li this opportunity.

He gave a cold harrumph as he closed both hands around the hilt of his giant sword, then launched himself directly at Han Li.

All of a sudden, a barrage of golden fireballs came raining down from the heavens like a meteor shower.

Yue Qing sliced through the first oncoming fireball with a slash of his sword, but more and more of them continued to rain down upon him.

The fireballs weren't particularly powerful, but there seemed to have been no end to them, and every single one was imbued with the time law powers of the Eon Divine Lamp and the Time Severing Torch.

After slicing through several dozen fireballs in succession, Yue Qing suddenly discovered that his movements were becoming slower and slower, as if he were being restricted by Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis again.

At this point, radiant, golden light was already beginning to seep out from between Han Li's hands, and arcs of lightning were springing out of his entire body, but he knew that this was still nowhere near enough power.

The golden heavenly gates opened up a little further at his behest, and balls of golden lightning came flying out from within at around twice the rate as before, then converged toward the palms of his hands.

He let loose an agonized roar, and the skin and flesh on his face was beginning to tear open, with golden lightning erupting out of his body.

Jin Tong and Xiaobai both turned their attention to Han Li in unison upon hearing his strained cry, and Jin Tong frantically yelled, "Stop, Uncle! If you keep this up, your body is going to give out!"

As for Xiaobai, he didn't even get a chance to say anything before Pofeng's attacks were upon him again.

Wuhui had already been forced onto the back foot by Jin Tong, and he was able to take advantage of this window of respite to catch his breath before launching himself at Jin Tong with renewed vigor.

It's still not enough... I need more... Han Li thought to himself as he gritted his teeth with all his might.

Even though Yue Qing had been slowed down significantly, he was still closing in steadily on Han Li, and he had also noticed the terrifying amount of lightning power that had accumulated in Han Li's body.

"This is it!" Yue Qing roared as a hint of killing intent surfaced in his eyes, and he raised a hand up toward the heavens, upon which a giant, murky, gray mountain appeared up above to withstand the barrage of golden fireballs.

At the same time, all of the runes on his giant sword lit up as he swung it horizontally at Han LI from afar.

Wave of ripples that were visible even to the naked eye appeared in the space up ahead, then swept toward Han Li with tremendous power.

A series of massive spatial rifts appeared high up in the heavens, and they remained open for extended periods of time.

With the spatial ripples rapidly closing in, Han Li still hadn't accumulated as much lightning power as he had hoped for. A wry smile appeared on his face as he prepared to prematurely unleash his attack, but right at this moment, a golden rune suddenly shot forth from afar before crashing into the waves of spatial ripples and exploding violently.

A burst of dazzling, golden light erupted forth, coupled with an almighty, primordial aura, and the spatial ripples were completely eradicated, while devastating shockwaves were sent sweeping through the air in all directions.

Close to the entirety of Raised Flagon Mountain was razed to the ground, reducing it to a set of barren plains, while Yue Qing was also sent flying back tens of thousands of feet.

After steadying himself, he immediately turned to Xiaobai with an astonished gaze as he exclaimed, "I knew you were a primordial true spirit!"

Xiaobai offered no response, and internally, he was feeling rather dismayed.

Bai Ze had told him that the golden talisman contained roughly a third of the power of an all-out attack from him, but it hadn't wounded Yue Qing at all.

While Yue Qing remained completely unscathed, Pofeng was given a massive fright. If that golden talisman had been used on her, then she would've most definitely already met her demise.

Even though Han Li hadn't been forced to directly withstand the attack, the explosion had taken place far too close to him, so he was unable to emerge unscathed.

His entire body was trembling uncontrollably, and in addition to his face, even his arms had begun to tear open, with arcs of golden lightning flashing incessantly within his wounds.

However, his palms remained stubbornly closed as he continued to accumulate more lightning power.

His vision was beginning to blur, and even his spiritual sense had become a little muddled.

"You must be close to your limits. If you release me, I can use my power to kill him."

A sinister yet tantalizing voice rang out in Han Li's mind.

Han Li knew that it was his wicked corpse soul speaking to him, and he offered no response.

At this point, almost his entire body had already turned numb, and the lightning power that he had accumulated was so vast that it was already out of his control, making it impossible to withdraw his sword array even if he wanted to.

If things were to continue like this, it wouldn't be long before his body imploded from the excessive influx of golden lightning.

Yue Qing could see that Han Li was nearing his limits, and instead of pressing any further, he merely remained standing still on the spot with a cold sneer on his face, waiting for Han Li to self-detonate.

Chapter 1264: Return to Eight Plains Mountain

"Stop being so stubborn. At this rate, you're going to get both of us killed, so why not release me? At the very least, those two little lackeys of yours will still have a chance to survive," the wicked corpse soul goaded.

Han Li was still very hesitant, but he didn't have much time left.

His body was about to reach its limit, and finally, he gritted his teeth as a look of finality appeared on his face, following which the Origin Separation Law Chains around the wicked corpse soul began to unravel.

"Good choice!" the wicked corpse soul cackled with glee, yet its triumphant cackling abruptly cut off as it discovered that Han Li had only unraveled half of the Origin Separation Law Chains around it.

"I can borrow your power, but I don't have to borrow all of it," Han Li said with a conniving grin, and the wicked corpse soul was furious.

With half of the Origin Separation Law Chains unraveled, half of the unopened immortal acupoints in Han Li's body opened up on their own, and a burst of power also surged into his body.

With this influx of power, Han Li was able to continue accumulating more lightning between the palms of his hands.

A stunned look appeared on Yue Qing's face upon seeing this, and he had no idea how Han Li had accomplished this. All he could do was shrink his spirit domain so that it formed a protective barrier around his own body, and at the same time, slid a hand over the blade of his giant sword.

A burst of immense earth law powers surged into the sword, and the seven mountain runes reappeared on its surface.

Immediately thereafter, he swung his sword down upon Han Li with a thunderous roar, and heaven and earth were split apart by a gargantuan streak of swordlight.

Seven majestic mountains appeared within the streak of swordlight, and each one was etched with a giant rune that was giving off an unfathomably dense and heavy aura.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly brought his hands apart as if he were drawing a bow, and a bow of golden lightning appeared in his grasp, nocked upon which was a golden arrow that was aimed directly at Yue Qing.

In the blink of an eye, the arrow of heavenly lightning pierced through the first mountain, and the remaining mountains didn't fare much better, either.

The golden arrow ran through all seven mountains in rapid succession, arriving before Yue Qing in a flash.

As a late-Great Encompassment cultivator, Yue Qing's reflexes were extremely sharp, and he raised his giant sword in front of himself as a protective barrier while dodging to the side to ensure that none of his vital regions were in the arrow's path.

The arrow was so incredibly fast that only after it had struck the giant sword did a string of resounding booms ring out in rapid succession from the seven mountains that it had pierced through, and it tore straight through the giant sword before piercing into the left side of Yue Qing's chest.

Yue Qing was sent flying back like a cannonball by the force of the impact, traveling tens of thousands of feet before crashing into the ground like a meteorite.

A massive cloud of dust rose up from the ground as the surrounding earth collapsed violently, forming a giant crater that was over ten thousand feet deep.

High up in the sky, Han Li was also looking rather worse for wear. His entire body was charred black, while blood was flowing from all of his orifices, and he swayed unsteadily for a moment before falling from the heavens.

With what little remaining power they had, his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords converged to catch him before lowering him to the ground.

Wuhui and Pofeng were astonished by this turn of events. Never had they anticipated that the late-Great Encompassment Stage Yue Qing would have so much trouble against an opponent two cultivation ranks his junior, and thoughts of retreat were beginning to arise in their hearts.

Jin Tong and Xiaobai pounced on the opportunity to force back Wuhui and Pokong before flying to Han Li's side, while Wuhui and Pokong rushed to Yue Qing's aid.

"Uncle!" Jin Tong called out in a concerned manner as she helped Han Li up into a seated position.

Han Li was so feeble that even after summoning a pill, he didn't have the energy to bring his hand to his own lips.

Xiaobai hurriedly took the pill before feeding it to him, and after swallowing the pill, Han Li immediately said, "We have to get out of here."

Jin Tong hoisted Han Li onto her back without any hesitation upon hearing this, yet right as the three of them were about to depart, a furious voice rang out from afar.

"Where do you think you're going?"

Han Li cast his gaze toward the direction that the voice had come from to see Yue Qing slowly approaching them.

He was still carrying his giant sword, but a fist-sized hole had appeared on its blade, and its spiritual nature had clearly been significantly compromised.

The suit of armor that he was wearing was in an even more wretched state, and a massive, corkscrew-shaped wound could be seen on his exposed chest. Golden blood was flowing out of the wound, while the surrounding area had been charred black, presenting a horrific sight to behold.

"As expected of a late-Great Encompassment cultivator," Han Li praised with a resigned sigh.

"You are the first and only early-Great Encompassment cultivator to have inflicted such severe injuries upon me. For that, I'm going to repay you a hundredfold!" Yue Qing spat through tightly gritted teeth.

Jin Tong set Han Li down behind her with a grim expression, then positioned herself in front of him and Xiaobai.

"Do you take pride in picking on early-Great Encompassment Stage juniors like this?"

Right at this moment, a cold voice rang out without any warning, and it echoed throughout the entirety of Raised Flagon Mountain.

"Who's there?" Yue Qing yelled as he stopped in his tracks and looked up into the sky with a wary expression.

In the next instant, the bright and clear sky suddenly turned pitch black, as if night had suddenly descended.

An elated look appeared on Han Li's face as he looked up to discover an enormous figure descending from the heavens, shrinking as it did so before ultimately taking on the form of a burly man in a hooded cloak.

The man was none other than the Sky Roaming Kun Peng, Yue Mian.

"Uncle Yue! What are you doing here?" Xiaobai exclaimed in an ecstatic manner, and even Jin Tong was struck by a sense of awe and veneration at the sight of Yue Mian.

"If I didn't come, you would've lost your life here because of Han Li!" Yue Mian snapped as he took a disgruntled glance at Han Li, and the awe and veneration in Jin Tong's heart instantly faded away upon hearing this as she glowered up at Yue Mian with a furious expression.

"It's not Master's fault! I was the one who insisted on coming with him!" Xiaobai protested.

"We'll talk about this later," Yue Mian said with a dismissive wave, then turned his gaze to Yue Qing's trio.

"To think that even the elusive Sky Roaming Kun Peng has made an appearance. Looks like I really am dealing with someone quite important," Yue Qing remarked as the surprise in his eyes began to fade.

"Piss off before I change my mind!" Yue Mian replied in a concise manner.

Yue Qing had already suffered severe injuries from Han Li's previous attack, and he naturally wasn't going to throw his life away against a Dao Ancestor like Yue Mian.

"Don't forget the lesson that the primordial land had to learn the hard way," he said in a thinly veiled threat, then promptly departed with Wuhui and Pofeng.

At this point, Han Li had already recovered somewhat, and he rose to his feet as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

"Thank you, Senior."

"Take some more time to rest. With me here, no one would dare to interrupt you," Yue Mian said.

Despite what he had said, he didn't truly blame Han Li, and he had only raised a complaint out of concern for Xiaobai's safety.

Han Li did as he was told, sitting down to rest and recuperate.

Not only had he severely overexerted himself during the battle just now, he had also been forced to unravel half of the Origin Separation Law Chains around his wicked corpse soul, thereby reducing the amount of time he had to prepare for his corpse soul severance.

"The two hundred years were almost up, so I decided to come and pick you up early. On the way here, I sensed that you had used the golden talisman given to you by Bai Ze, so I immediately sped up and got here as quickly as I could," Yue Mian explained.

"You came here because you were worried that I wouldn't be willing to go back at the agreed-upon time, right, Uncle Yue?" Xiaobai asked.

Yue Mian didn't confirm or deny this.

"Don't worry, Uncle Yue. During this period of time that I spent with Master, I've come to realize just how lacking my powers are, so after I go back, I'll go into seclusion right away, and I won't come out until I've completely inherited the power passed down to me by my father," Xiaobai promised.

"It seems like you've grown and matured," Yue Mian said with a pleased nod.

Around two hours later, Han Li finally awakened from his meditative state, and Yue Mian bade him farewell before preparing to depart with Xiaobai.

"Please wait a moment, Senior Yue Mian," Han Li hurriedly said.

"What is it?" Yue Mian asked.

"If you're returning to Eight Plains Mountain, would you be able to take me with you, Senior?" Han Li requested.

"Oh? You also want to go to Eight Plains Mountain?" Yue Mian asked with a puzzled expression.

"That's right. Would that be alright?" Han Li asked.

In the wake of his Nine Origins Temple adventure, he had become even more desperate to elevate his own powers.

Given his involvement in the recent events, he was now most definitely a wanted fugitive in all of the immortal regions, leaving him with nowhere to hide. Hence, Eight Plains Mountain was perhaps the safest place for him.

"Of course," Yue Mian replied with a smile and a nod, then swept a sleeve through the air, conjuring up an azure storm that lifted Han Li involuntarily up into the air.

Han Li was slightly alarmed by this, and he was just about to channel his time law powers wot steady himself when his feet landed on a solid surface, and a burst of gentle yet irresistible power swept over him, causing him to stumble into a seated position.

He looked around to discover that he was sitting on the back of a gargantuan, azure bird that completely concealed the entire landscape down below like a boundless, azure continent.

This was Yue Mian's true form, and compared with it, Han Li was like an insignificant speck of dust.

At this moment, Xiaobai was sitting beside Han Li with a mixture of astonishment, excitement, and longing in his eyes.

Chapter 1265: Extraheavensphere

Yue Mian flapped his enormous wings to propel himself up into the air, and in the blink of an eye, he had ascended through the clouds, but he displayed no sign of stopping as he continued to elevate himself further and further.

The world's origin qi in the surrounding space was quickly becoming sparser and sparser, and Yue Mian warned, "Sit tight!"

Immediately thereafter, countless azure incantation seals surged out of his talons before swirling around him, and his speed was instantly enhanced by a hundredfold, reducing all of the surrounding scenery to a rapid blur.

Han Li was almost thrown off Yue Mian's back by the abrupt acceleration, and he hurriedly channeled his cultivation arts to stabilize himself.

Moments later, Yue Mian seemed to have broken through some type of boundary and arrived in a unique space.

It was a boundless, blue space that was incredibly pristine, with not even the faintest cloud or the slightest speck of dust to be seen.

However, at the same time, this place was also completely devoid of world's origin qi, and all other types of energy, for that matter. It was a space filled with boundless nothingness.

Never had he flown at such a lofty altitude before, so this was a stunning sight that he had never gotten to witness.

"What is this place? I don't think I've ever been here before," Jin Tong murmured as she looked around in a slightly dazed manner.

"This is the Ethersphere," Xiaobai answered.

"What's that?" Han Li asked.

"According to my father's memories, the atmosphere of the True Immortal Realm is split up into three sections, the Ethersphere, the Astralsphere, and the Extraheavensphere. This is the Ethersphere, which is closest to the ground, and beyond the Ethersphere is the Astralsphere, while beyond that is the legendary Extraheavensphere, also known as the Extraheaven Realm," Xiaobai explained.

"I see," Han Li murmured with a thoughtful expression.

"These three areas are all at extremely high altitudes and are rife with peril. For example, this Ethersphere is completely devoid of spiritual qi, so any cultivator that stays here for extended periods of time will suffer severe detrimental effects. Hence, the average cultivator would never come here, and as a result, there are very few records of this place," Xiaobai continued, and Han Li nodded in response.

With his cultivation base, visiting the Ethersphere was not a difficult task, but he had been too busy working on his cultivation and hiding from the Heavenly Court, so he had never gotten a chance to explore such areas.

Jin Tong was sitting beside Han Li with a scowl on her face, seemingly very averse to the environment here.

"Are you alright, Jin Tong?" Han Li asked.

"I'm fine. It's just that the complete lack of spiritual qi here is rather unsettling," Jin Tong replied.

"In that case, why don't you go and rest in the Flower Branch domain?" Han Li suggested.

Jin Tong nodded in agreement with this suggestion, and Han Li cast her into the Flower Branch domain, while Yue Mian continued to ascend higher and higher.

The Ethersphere was astonishingly massive, and even with Yue Mian's incredible speed, it took him close to an hour to reach the end.

All of a sudden, ferocious, black storms began to appear up ahead, and they were sweeping through the air in waves amid a thunderous howling sound.

"Is this the Astralsphere?" Han Li asked.

"It must be. The Astralsphere is filled with Heavenly Astral Wind, making it an extremely dangerous and inhospitable place, but it's quite tame compared with the Extraheavensphere," Xiaobai explained.

As soon as his voice trailed off, Yue Mian dove headfirst into the storms of Heavenly Astral Wind up ahead without any hesitation, and the howling instantly became so deafening that even Han Li was beginning to feel a throbbing pain in his eardrums.

He hurriedly channeled his time law powers to protect his own ears, while a layer of protective white light had also surfaced over Xiaobai's body.

The gusts of Heavenly Astral Wind were tearing viciously at Yue Mian, but they were kept firmly at bay by an azure light barrier that encompassed his entire body, and his speed wasn't hampered in the slightest as he continued his ascent.

Initially, Han Li was a little concerned, but his concerns were quickly assuaged upon seeing the ease with which Yue Mian was negotiating the surrounding storms.

These storms were unlike anything that Han Li had ever seen before. They were filled with incredibly violent power, and it was as if they were determined to completely annihilate anything that fell into them.

Thin, black lines could occasionally be seen within the storms, and they were able to tear open spatial rifts with ease, but these black lines were also unable to breach the azure light barrier around Yue Mian.

All of a sudden, Xiaobai's eyes lit up as he raised a hand to summon the white cloth pouch that was once his father's bonded immortal treasure.

The pouch instantly swelled to ten times its original size, and a ring of white light appeared over the mouth of the pouch, giving off a burst of tremendous suction force.

All of the Heavenly Astral Wind within a radius of hundreds of kilometers was instantly sucked into the pouch, and the same applied to the thin, black lines interspersed throughout the gusts of Heavenly Astral Wind.

After collecting all of the Heavenly Astral Wind in the nearby vicinity, the white pouch flew through the air like an all-devouring beast, sucking in all of the Heavenly Astral Wind in its path.

"Why are you collecting this Heavenly Astral Wind?" Han Li asked.

"I'm not collecting the Heavenly Astral Wind, I'm collecting those black lines, which are gusts of Black Whitewash Wind, something that only arises from millions of years of condensed Heavenly Astral Wind.

“There's a secret technique in my father's memories that can make use of Black Whitewash Wind to refine a type of extremely powerful Windbreaker Bead that poses a significant threat even to Great Encompassment cultivators. It's not every day that I get to come to the Astralsphere, so I have to take full advantage of the opportunity," Xiaobai explained with a smile.

Han Li nodded in response as he took an intrigued glance at the white pouch.

He had reflexively attempted to examine the pouch with his spiritual sense just now, yet as soon as his spiritual sense made contact with the pouch, it was instantly sucked in before being eradicated.

Despite the pouch's unremarkable appearance, it seemed to possess some very special and powerful abilities.

Before long, they had reached the end of the Astralsphere, and Yue Mian reached out with both of his talons to tear open a giant, spatial rift, which he flew directly into.

Han Li felt his vision blur momentarily, following which he found himself situated in a black space.

Countless asteroids were suspended in this black space, some of which were only the size of houses, while some were astonishingly massive, with their boundaries nowhere in sight. All of these asteroids were moving in an irregular fashion, and occasionally, some of them would clash or grate against one another to produce a deafening commotion.

Some of these asteroids were completely devoid of luster, while others were giving off light of all types of different colors to somewhat illuminate the darkness.

All of a sudden, a storm of blue ice blew over rapidly from afar, and it stretched as far as the eyes could see, resembling a gargantuan, blue ice dragon.

The smaller asteroids in its path were instantly frozen solid before being swept away by the storm, while thick layers of blue ice had materialized over the larger asteroids.

The blue storm had only just passed by when an enormous purple cloud appeared, seemingly out of nowhere. The purple cloud was filled with arcs of purple lightning, and all of the frozen asteroids instantly exploded upon contact with the cloud.

Immediately following the purple cloud emerged a giant, black vortex that was revolving rapidly, devouring everything in the nearby vicinity.

However, the black vortex was also only around for a fleeting moment before fading into nothingness.

It was clear that this was the Extraheavensphere, and Han Li felt as if he were situated in a boundless, black space, one in which neither his Infernal Devilish Eyes nor his spiritual sense were able to see very far.

Furthermore, he could sense a burst of power that was countless times more formidable than that of the revolution of the celestial bodies present in this space.

"The Extraheavensphere is fraught with peril, but there are also countless precious treasures to be found here. At your cultivation bases, you should be able to hold your own here, so I suggest you come here to explore from time to time. It'll be very beneficial for your cultivation," Yue Mian said as he continued to fly onward, but as opposed to ascending any further, he was now flying directly forward.

"There are indeed many precious treasures here," Xiaobai said as he adopted his Pixiu form and began excitedly sniffing at the air.

He then summoned his white pouch again before opening his mouth to release a ball of white light into it, and the pouch instantly swelled to several hundred kilometers in size.

At the same time, it had also become semi-transparent, and the threads that the pouch had been woven from spread apart to form a net.

Bursts of tremendous suction force surged out of the net to devour all of the nearby asteroids before crushing them to reveal chunks of ore of all types of different colors.

In the blink of an eye, the pouch had already gathered several hundred pieces of precious materials, and Han Li couldn't help but become even more curious about the pouch upon seeing this.

"Fellow Daoist Han, even though you've already reached the Great Encompassment Stage, you still only know very little about Dao Ancestors. Dao Ancestors possess powers beyond your imaginations, and there's a very good chance that we could be detected by other Dao Ancestors had we been flying at a lower altitude, so it's much safer to travel through the Extraheavensphere," Yue Mian explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a contemplative nod.

Yue Mian continued to fly directly forward as bursts of azure ripples surged out of his body.

These azure ripples didn't appear all that remarkable, but all of them were imbued with astonishing power. All of the asteroids that came into contact with the ripples were instantly vaporized, regardless of their size, allowing Yue Mian to forge ahead at full speed.

Of course, none of the natural hazards present in the Extraheavensphere posed a threat to Yue Mian, either, and they were instantly eradicated without a trace as soon as they came into contact with his body.

Han Li had witnessed the power of peak-Great Encompassment cultivators on more than one occasion, and while they were theoretically only one step away from becoming Dao Ancestors, it was quickly becoming clear to Han Li that that single step may as well have been an infinitely wide chasm.

Chapter 1266: Heavenly Devil Cloud

Han Li gently exhaled and sat down with his legs crossed before channeling his cultivation arts.

The Extraheavensphere was an extremely perilous place, but it was extremely abundant with all types of world's origin qi, making it an exceptional place for cultivation.

Meanwhile, Xiaobai continued to collect the nearby chunks of ore with his white pouch.

Close to two hours flew by in the blink of an eye, and right at this moment, the entire world up ahead suddenly turned dark, as if night had abruptly descended.

Alerted by this sudden change, Han Li awoke from his cultivation to discover that an enormous, black cloud had appeared up ahead, and it was in the process of sweeping toward them.

The black cloud was churning incessantly, and all types of shadows could be seen flashing within it, presenting an unsettling sight to behold.

"What's that?" Xiaobai asked with a surprised expression as he ceased his ore collection operation.

"That's a Heavenly Devil Cloud formed by Extrarealm Heavenly Devils. These clouds have no substance and are impossible to eradicate, making them the most threatening hazard in this Extraheavensphere. Make sure to be on your guard, especially you, Fellow Daoist Han," Yue Qing warned, then plunged headfirst into the black cloud.

Han Li instantly felt a chill sweep over him, as if he were being submerged in a vat of cold water, and the surrounding area had turned so dark that even Xiaobai was barely visible to him, despite their close proximity to one another.

Han Li hurriedly channeled his time law powers to protect his entire body, and right at this moment, a burst of invisible energy fluctuation surged out of the nearby darkness to envelop him.

Before he had a chance to react, the surrounding scenery changed drastically, and he found himself in a murky, gray space all on his own.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, and a cool and refreshing sensation instantly arose in his consciousness.

Right at this moment, a black-robed young woman came stumbling toward him, and it was none other than Nangong Wan.

Her hair was disheveled, and she was frantically rushing along as if she were being pursued by something terrifying.

"Save me, my husband! I've already recovered my memories, but the people from the Reincarnation Palace won't let me leave!" Nangong Wan yelled in a shrill and horrified voice with tears streaming down her face, giving her a very vulnerable and pitiable appearance.

"It doesn't appear as if there's anyone pursuing you," Han Li said in a calm manner.

"I'm so scared!"

Nangong Wan reached Han Li in the blink of an eye, then threw herself at him like a drowning man pouncing at a raft.

A peculiar look appeared in Han Li's eyes, and right as Nangong Wan was about to throw herself into his arms, he suddenly raised a hand to release a thick bolt of golden lightning, which pierced through Nangong Wan's chest in a flash, leaving a gaping hole in its wake.

"How could you..." Nangong Wan sputtered in an incredulous voice as blood came gushing out of her mouth.

"I'll admit that this is a very convincing illusion, but it's not going to work on me," Han Li said in a cold voice as he spread his fingers, and the bolt of golden lightning erupted in all directions to tear Nangong Wan's body into pieces.

A blood-curdling howl rang out as Nangong Wan disintegrated into a plume of black smoke, and the surrounding, gray space also vanished as Han Li reappeared on Yue Mian's back.

He heaved an internal sigh of relief, but his brows then instantly furrowed tightly again.

Even though he had just overcome that illusion just now, the wicked corpse soul in his body had suddenly begun to stir, and an intense burst of bloodlust and killing intent was beginning to arise in his heart.

He hurriedly channeled his spiritual sense and his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra in an attempt to suppress this ill intent.

So these Extrarealm Heavenly Devils are capable of affecting my wicked corpse soul. This must be why Yue Mian warned me to be careful.

Before he was able to suppress the ill intent in his heart, another burst of invisible energy fluctuations swept over him, and this time, he was transported into a purple space, where an elegant figure was standing with her back facing him.

Even though her face was turned away from him, Han Li was still able to immediately identify her as none other than Violet Spirit.

His brows furrowed slightly as he swept a sleeve through the air, and a thick bolt of lightning erupted out of the palm of his hand before crashing down upon Violet Spirit with tremendous might.

However, Violet Spirit abruptly vanished from the spot, then reappeared several hundred feet away, successfully evading Han Li's attack.

"What is the meaning of this, Brother Han?" she yelled as she turned around to face him with a stunned and infuriated look in her eyes.

Han Li continued to sweep his sleeve through the air in rapid succession, releasing more golden lightning that intertwined to form a huge, golden lightning net, which encompassed the entire surrounding area within a radius of several dozen kilometers.

The net of golden lightning descended rapidly upon Violet Spirit, displaying such incredible speed that even a Great Encompassment cultivator would struggle to react in time.

Once again, Violet Spirit was able to evade the attack, flying out of the scope of the net of golden lightning in a flash as if by instantaneous teleportation.

However, she was unable to fully evade the attack this time, and her right arm was grazed by the net of lightning, tearing her sleeve apart while also inflicting a horrific gash onto her arm.

"Looks like you really do intend to kill me. I worked so hard in my cultivation all these years so that I could ascend to the Immortal Realm and by your side, and this is what I get in return!" Violet Spirit yelled in a heartbroken voice as tears began to well up in her eyes.

Han Li was aware that this Violet Spirit was nothing more than an illusion, but he was still struck by a pang of guilt and sympathy at the sight of her heartbroken display. However, he didn't allow that to influence his decision-making as summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which released waves of golden ripples that instantly swept over Violet Spirit's body to root her to the spot.

Han Li then made a forceful grabbing motion, and the golden lightning net converged around Violet Spirit to form a ball of golden lightning.

The ball of lightning exploded with a resounding boom, and Violet Spirit had vanished without a trace.

The purple space faded away, and Han Li reappeared on Yue Mian's back once again.

His complexion was rather pale, and the ill intent in his heart had become even more potent.

Before he even had a chance to catch his breath, another wave of Heavenly Devil Fluctuations swept over him, this one far more formidable than the previous two.

This time, Han Li was transported into a shimmering, golden world.

The entire space was filled with immense metal law power fluctuations, and it didn't feel like an illusory world in the slightest.

A giant, golden figure was standing up ahead, and it was none other than the Nine Origins Dao Ancestor, Li Yuanjiu. A vast, suffocating aura was emanating from his body, making Han Li feel as if he were being crushed under the collective weight of a hundred mountains.

"Han Li, you infiltrated a restricted area of our Nine Origins Temple and wounded two of our temple's holy envoys while also assisting those Reincarnation Palace scoundrels in stealing our prized treasure.

“I was going to spare you in order to sever our karmic ties, but that decision has been met with vehement objections from everyone in our Nine Origins Temple, so I've come to take your life," Li Yuanjiu declared as he made a hand seal, and a divine, golden saber that was over ten thousand feet in length appeared out of thin air before crashing down upon Han Li with unstoppable might.

A massive rift was torn into the golden space by the divine saber, and Han Li's pupil contracted drastically upon seeing this.

He channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra and Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might, and a loud tearing sound rang out as he struggled free from the restrictive pressure that was weighing down upon him.

Immediately thereafter, he threw an almighty punch directly into the sharp blade of the golden saber, and a resounding clang rang out as the saber flew back in retreat before exploding violently into countless specks of golden light.

However, the skin and flesh on Han Li's fist had also been torn apart to expose the bones underneath, but he paid no heed to his own injuries.

A cold sneer appeared on Li Yuanjiu's face as he swept both sleeves through the air, and countless golden sword projections appeared directly above Han Li in rapid succession before falling upon him in a lethal, golden storm.

The storm of golden sword projections pierced countless holes into the space down below in a devastating, doomsday-like scene.

However, Han Li remained completely unfazed as he launched himself directly at Li Yuanjiu, allowing the golden sword projections to fall upon him, and in the blink of an eye, his body was already riddled with holes.

At the same time, a cold sneer appeared on Li Yuanjiu's face as he swatted a palm down upon Han Li, and the entire golden space came crashing down upon Han Li at his behest.

However, right at this moment, a layer of radiant, golden light erupted out of Han Li's body, and a burst of tremendous time law powers instantly encompassed the entire golden space, slowing everything down to a crawl.

At the same time, Han Li's speed was enhanced by several dozenfold, and he raced through the air like a speeding arrow that pierced through Li Yuanjiu's body in a flash.

Li Yuanjiu exploded violently, and the surrounding golden space also faded away, returning Han Li to reality.

All of his injuries had disappeared, but the ill intent in his heart had broken through a certain threshold and was now proving impossible to suppress.

Han Li was doing everything in his power to remain in control, but his efforts were proving to be futile.

Thankfully, right at this moment, Yue Mian flew out of the Heavenly Devil Cloud, and the ill intent in Han Li's heart wasn't exacerbated any further, allowing him to just barely remain in control of himself.

If they had stayed in that Heavenly Devil Cloud for even just a little longer, he would've been overwhelmed by the ill intent in his heart and driven insane.

At the same time, Xiaobai also opened his eyes with a mixture of lingering fear and relief on his face.

Chapter 1267: Nowhere is Safe

"Are you two alright?" Yue Mian asked.

"We're alright, but that was a really close call! Each successive illusion was more fearsome than the previous one, and if you hadn't flown out of the cloud when you did, I don't think I would've been able to maintain control over myself for much longer," Xiaobai said.

"This is why Heavenly Devil Clouds are the most potent hazards in the entire Extraheavensphere. That was a rather small cloud that we encountered just now. If we had run into a larger Heavenly Devil Cloud, then I wouldn't have been able to fly out of it so quickly," Yue Mian said.

"In that case, I think I'm going to stay out of the Extraheavensphere for now. Perhaps I won't be able to progress as quickly in my cultivation, but at the very least, it'll be a lot safer. How are you doing, Master?" Xiaobai asked as he turned his gaze to Han Li, who was currently seated in silence with his eyes closed and his brows slightly furrowed.

There was a burst of baleful qi swirling around his body, and as he opened his eyes in response to Xiaobai's question, it was revealed that they were glowing with faint, crimson light.

"Master, your eyes! Could it be that you've already been possessed by an Extrarealm Heavenly Devil? How dare you! Get out of my master's body!" Xiaobai yelled with a look of alarm and fury on his face.

"It's fine, I haven't been possessed, I've only been somewhat affected," Han Li reassured.

A hesitant look of skepticism appeared on Xiaobai's face upon hearing this.

"Very impressive! I thought that in your current state, there's no way you'd be able to remain impervious to the influence of the Extrarealm Heavenly Devils, but you've done very well. Having said that, I presume that you're struggling to contain the ill intent in your heart right now," Yue Mian said with a faint smile.

"That is indeed the case, Senior," Han Li confirmed with a wry smile.

No further ill intent had accumulated in his heart, but it hadn't abated, either. On top of that, the ill intent was proving impossible to suppress, despite his best efforts.

"One's three corpse souls are entities that have extremely profound connections to one's soul and psyche. I don't know how you managed to forcibly summon your wicked corpse soul without first reaching the pinnacle of the early-Great Encompassment Stage, and I can tell that you've suppressed it for now, but under the influence of the Heavenly Devil Cloud, it's only a matter of time before it breaks free, so you'll have to find a way to sever it as soon as possible.

“Otherwise, it'll inevitably take over your body in the near future," Yue Mian said.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

He was aware that he couldn't keep his wicked corpse soul restrained forever, and he also wanted to sever it as soon as possible, but given his lackluster cultivation base, his chances of a successful corpse soul severance were very slim.

Yue Mian spoke no further on the subject, and after flying for close to half a day longer, he suddenly swooped down in a gradual descent, passing through the Astralsphere and the Ethersphere again before descending upon a lush mountain range somewhere in the vast territory of the primordial land.

After flying for a while longer, the majestic Eight Plains Mountain appeared up ahead.

Han Li couldn't help but be astonished by Yue Mian's speed. It had taken him several decades to fly from Eight Plains Mountain to the greater Golden Origin Immortal Region, yet it had only taken Yue Mian less than a day to make the same return journey.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and he jumped down from Yue Mian's back, then cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "Thank you for bringing me back to the primordial land, Senior Yue. However, given my status as a human, I most likely won't be welcome on Eight Plains Mountain, so I think we should part ways here."

Yue Mian reverted back to his human form amid a flash of azure light, then took a glance at Han Li as he replied, "Suit yourself."

All of a sudden, Bai Ze appeared out of thin air with a wide smile on his face as he interjected, "I can't allow that! It would reflect terribly upon our primordial tribes if you were shut out right on our doorstep!"

"Senior Bai Ze!" Han Li hurriedly greeted with a respectful bow, and Xiaobai immediately followed suit.

"You really stirred things up in the Nine Origins Temple, Fellow Daoist Han! It's not every day that I get to see someone of Li Yuanjiu's caliber falling flat on his face!" Bai Ze chuckled in amusement.

"Of course! Master and I were completely unstoppable in the Nine Origins Temple! We beat up two of their holy envoys so badly that they were forced to run for their lives!" Xiaobai declared in a triumphant manner.

"It was the Reincarnation Palace that did the vast majority of the work, I only happened to be in the right place at the right time," Han Li said in a modest manner.

"Be that as it may, it's still very impressive that you were able to emerge unscathed from the lion's den that is the Nine Origins Temple. Back when you left, you were only at the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage, yet you're not even that far away from the mid-Great Encompassment Stage now. I don't think even I was able to make such rapid progress at the same stage of my cultivation journey!" Bai Ze praised.

"You're far too kind, Senior," Han Li said, maintaining a humble demeanor.

"You're still as modest as ever, Fellow Daoist Han. Thank you for looking after Xiaobai and ensuring his safe return," Bai Ze said as he pulled Xiaobai in for a closer examination.

"Xiaobai is my friend, so it's only right that I protect him. Besides, Xiaobai is more than capable of looking after himself, and I didn't really do anything. As for our safe return to the primordial land, that's all thanks to Senior Yue Mian," Han Li replied with a smile.

"In any case, I'm glad to see both of you safe and well. Come and take a seat on our Eight Plains Mountain," Bai Ze offered.

"Please forgive me, but I'm afraid I must turn down your kind invitation, Senior Bai. I'm currently in a rather precarious condition and would like to go into seclusion right away," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute.

Bai Ze took a quick glance at Han Li, and a hint of surprise appeared in his eyes as he said, "I can see that there are indeed some rather pressing concerns for you to address. In that case, I won't keep you any longer. Around a hundred and fifty thousand kilometers east of here is a mountain range called the Jade Cloud Mountain Range.

“It's a place that's very abundant with the world's origin qi and isn't occupied by any primordial tribes, so you can go into seclusion there."

An elated look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

"Thank you, Senior Bai."

"I'll come with you, Master. Your Majesty, seeing as the Jade Cloud Mountain Range isn't far away from here, it makes no difference whether I stay here or go there to cultivate, right?" Xiaobai implored.

"You're not going anywhere! I've already made arrangements for your cultivation from this point onward, so you have to stay on Eight Plains Mountain," Bai Ze replied in an authoritative manner.

"Fine..." Xiaobai acquiesced in a reluctant manner.

"I'll be taking my leave now, Senior Bai Ze, Senior Yue Mian," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute, then flew away toward the east as a streak of golden light.

Bai Ze's trio observed his departing figure for a moment, then descended onto Eight Plains Mountain.

It didn't long for Han Li to reach the Jade Cloud Mountain Range, and just as Bai Ze had proclaimed, the world's origin qi here was extremely abundant, yet it wasn't as wild and unrestrained as the world's origin qi elsewhere in the primordial land, so it really was an ideal location for a stint of seclusion.

Han Li dug out a simple cave abode into a cliff face, then set up some restrictions around it.

After that, he conjured up a door of silver light and stepped into the Flower Branch domain through it.

Weeping Soul and Jin Tong seemed to have already been waiting at the entrance, and they immediately approached him upon his arrival.

"Weeping Soul, you already know what happened in that Heavenly Devil Cloud earlier. Right now, I need your help to see if I can suppress the ill intent in my body," Han Li said, then sat down on the spot with his legs crossed and closed his eyes.

Weeping Soul immediately sprang into action, resting a palm down onto Han Li's head to conjure up a dark red light barrier over his entire body.

Han Li gave a muffled groan as his immortal acupoints began to flash erratically, and bursts of black baleful qi surged out from within before swirling around his body.

As soon as the baleful qi came into contact with the dark red light barrier, it would immediately fade into nothingness with a loud sizzling sound.

However, more and more baleful qi continued to surge out of Han Li's body with no end in sight.

Jin Tong could sense the perilous condition that Han Li was in, and she remained standing off to the side in silence while staring intently at Han Li with an unblinking gaze.

Even after three days and three nights, the baleful qi surging out of Han Li's body hadn't abated in the slightest.

At this point, Jin Tong was already feeling very agitated, and her gaze was constantly roaming back and forth between Han Li and Weeping Soul. On several occasions, she was almost unable to resist the urge to speak, but she held her tongue each time.

She knew that Han Li couldn't afford any distractions in his current condition, and she was very frustrated at her own inability to help him in any way.

All of a sudden, Han Li's eyes sprang open as he said, "You can stop now, Weeping Soul."

Weeping Soul withdrew her hand and backed away, then said in a hesitant manner, "Master, the ill intent in your body seems to be different from before somehow."

"So you've noticed it as well," Han Li said with a wry smile, but he didn't elaborate any further as he raised a hand cut off Jin Tong right as she was about to speak.

He had tried to avert this crisis in a peaceful fashion, but a peaceful resolution proved out of reach. At this point, he had no choice but to sever his wicked corpse soul as soon as possible and progress to the mid-Great Encompassment Stage.

However, that was certainly not going to be an easy task.

He had no master that he could turn to for guidance, and due to the time constraints during his previous stint of transmigration, Patriarch Miro hadn't provided him with any instructions on the subject of corpse soul severance, so he would have to go into this completely blind.

With that in mind, Han Li turned to Weeping Soul and Jin Tong and said, "I'm going to go into seclusion in the space of accelerated time to try and cultivate to the pinnacle of the early-Great Encompassment Stage as quickly as possible.

“There's no need for you two to worry about me, just focus on your own cultivation. We may be safe for now in the primordial land, but we'll have to return to the immortal regions eventually, and the more power the three of us can attain, the better equipped we'll be to make our return."

Immediately thereafter, he summoned his spirit domain to encompass the surrounding space in a radius of close to two hundred feet.

With his Mantra Treasured Axis working in tandem with the Celestial Time Array, the flow of time within his spirit domain was instantly accelerated by roughly ten thousandfold.

Weeping Soul and Jin Tong were still a little concerned about Han Li's current condition, but ultimately, there was nothing that they could do to help him, so they sat down on either side of him and began to focus on their own cultivation.

Chapter 1268: Corpse Soul Severance Bottleneck

At the moment, Han Li hadn't begun cultivating right away. Instead, he put up all of the precious treasures and materials that he had obtained from Gui Lingzi's cave abode for sale in the Reincarnation Palace.

He didn't have many Immortal Origin Stones left, so he had to stock up on more.

Thankfully, everything that he had gathered from Gui Lingzi's cave abode would be enough to support his Immortal Origin Stone needs for the near future.

After that, Han Li sat down with his eyes closed to channel his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra and began working on opening his remaining immortal acupoints.

However, he hadn't remained in a state of cultivation for long before his eyes suddenly sprang open.

His progress had been unexpectedly smooth, and it was a completely different experience from his past cultivation.

At this rate, it would only take a few years for him to open an immortal acupoint, and that was a virtually negligible duration of time in this space of accelerated time.

Could this have something to do with the fact that my remaining immortal acupoints are already in a half-open state from having my wicked corpse soul forcibly brought out?

He quickly banished these thoughts from his mind and refocused his attention on his cultivation.

Over ten years flew by in a flash, and right at this moment, an immortal acupoint was suddenly opened on Han Li's shoulder.

An ecstatic look appeared on his face, but it was quickly replaced by a look of concern.

By opening this immortal acupoint, he had elevated the powers of both himself and his wicked corpse soul.

The Origin Separation Law Chains around the wicked corpse soul seemed to have been forced open a little, and the baleful qi swirling around Han Li became even more potent as a result.

"Your struggles are completely futile. The more power you attain, the more powerful I become as well. Eventually, I'm going to break free from this seal, and when that time comes, your body will be mine!" the wicked corpse soul cackled with glee.

Han Li paid no heed to the wicked corpse soul's goading words as he closed his eyes and refocused his efforts once again.

Thirty thousand years flew by in the blink of an eye.

Han Li's entire body was riddled with glowing specks of golden light, amounting to a total of eight hundred and thirty-nine.

His aura had also swelled by roughly twofold, and it was now comparable even to that of mid-Great Encompassment cultivators like Immortal Lord Miao Fa and Gui Lingzi.

However, the baleful qi swirling around him also become much denser, and a strange, black rune had appeared on his glabella.

The rune resembled a sinister face that was flashing with black light, and it looked as if it could crawl out of his glabella at any moment.

The golden light radiating from his body faded away as he opened his eyes.

At this moment, around half of both of his eyes were glowing a deranged, dark red color, while the other halves of his eyes remained composed and sane and normal in coloration, presenting a very bizarre sight to behold.

A hint of elation flashed through Han Li's eyes at the sight of all of the immortal acupoints shimmering over his body.

This stint of seclusion had gone far smoother than he had imagined, and all that stood between him and the mid-Great Encompassment was a single immortal acupoint.

He still wasn't ready for a corpse soul severance, but the situation had become so urgent and dire that he couldn't afford to wait any longer.

If it wasn't for his tremendous spiritual sense and immense mental resilience, the overwhelming ill intent that had accumulated in his body would've already pushed him over the edge.

Jin Tong and Weeping Soul could sense that Han Li had awakened, and they also paused in their own cultivation to check on him.

Thirty thousand years wasn't a particularly lengthy period of cultivation for the two of them, and they couldn't help but be distracted by their concern for Han Li's condition this entire time, so neither of them had been able to make much progress.

"Are you alright, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked in a concerned manner at the sight of immense baleful qi swirling around Han Li.

"I'm still alright for now," Han Li replied.

"Are you planning to commence your corpse soul severance now, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"That's the idea, but prior to that, I still have to make some preparations," Han Li replied, then fell silent as if he were contemplating something.

Weeping Soul and Jin Tong exchanged a glance with each other, and neither of them said anything.

After a brief silence, Han Li made a hand seal to withdraw his spirit domain, then turned to Jin Tong and Weeping Soul as he said, "I'm going to start making preparations for my corpse soul severance now, so I'll get the two of you to stand on lookout duty for me outside."

The two of them nodded in response before flying out of the Flower Branch domain, and following their departure, Han Li put on his Reincarnation Palace mask before opening the trading interface.

Earlier, he had released a mission requesting methods or insights pertaining to the severance of the wicked corpse soul for early-Great Encompassment cultivators.

He had attached an extremely lofty reward to the mission, including a huge sum of Immortal Origin Stones, as well as all types of precious treasures, Time Dao Pills, and various cultivation arts and secret techniques, with even the Five Lightning True Mantra thrown into the mix.

Unfortunately, even with such a tantalizing reward on offer, there had still been no responders to date.

Han Li heaved a forlorn sigh upon seeing this, but he wasn't all that surprised.

Corpse soul severances were the key to cultivation progression fro Great Encompassment cultivators. For cultivators progressing to the Golden Immortal Stage, the High Zenith Stage, and even the Great Encompassment Stage, there had always been certain patterns that could be followed, thereby making it possible to devise certain methods to assist in those breakthroughs.

However, corpse soul severance was completely different. It concerned attachments that differed from person to person, and on top of that, Great Encompassment cultivators were extremely rare to begin with, so it was virtually impossible to devise a formula or a set of foolproof methods that could ensure a successful corpse soul severance.

However, over the countless eons that the True Immortal Realm had been in existence, some methods had been invented, and these methods were collectively known as corpse soul severance techniques.

However, such techniques were extremely precious, so it made sense that no one would be willing to offer them up for exchange.

Han Li had only released the mission under the very slim hope that it would reap dividends for him, so it was no surprise that it had failed to achieve the desired outcome.

At this point, he could only think of a single feasible solution.

He flipped a hand over to produce the Heaven Controlling Vial.

With no other alternatives, he would have to transmigrate to the past at the cost of his time law threads to seek guidance from Patriarch Miro.

Thus, Han Li channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra while simultaneously calling out to the vial spirit, but his calls remained unanswered.

What's going on?

He had already lost contact with the vial spirit last time in the Nine Origins Temple, and it was still displaying no reaction, even though so much time had already passed since then.

He continued to call upon the vial spirit for a while longer, but ultimately received no response, and his heart slowly began to sink.

Without the vial spirit's help, it would be impossible for him to transmigrate precisely back to the True Mantra Sect.

With no corpse soul severance technique at his disposal, he would have to proceed completely blind, and that would significantly reduce his chances of success.

Right at this moment, a voice transmission talisman flew in through the entrance of the Flower Branch domain, and Han Li was rather taken aback to see this, but he immediately caught the talisman before crushing it in his grasp.

The talisman transformed into a ball of white light, and Weeping Soul's voice rang out from within.

"Master, a woman by the name of Liu Le'er has come to visit, and she claims to be an acquaintance of yours. Do you know her?"

"I do. Let her in," Han Li replied.

Weeping Soul gave an affirmative response, and the ball of white light faded away.

Han Li rose to his feet and took a moment to compose himself, then flew out of the Flower Branch domain into the hall of his cave abode outside.

Waiting for him in the hall were Jin Tong and Weeping Soul, and they were joined by none other than Liu Le'er.

Han Li could sense that she had made significant strides in her cultivation base since they last parted ways, and just like him, she was closing in on the mid-Great Encompassment Stage.

Liu Le'er faltered slightly at the sight of Han Li's current appearance, but then immediately dove into his arms in an elated fashion.

"You're finally back, Brother Rock! I'm so glad to see you again!"

He immediately felt two pairs of accusing eyes lock onto him, and he could only rub his own nose in a sheepish manner.

Jin Tong and Weeping Soul exchanged a glance with one another, then left the hall in silence to give Han Li and Liu Le'er some privacy.

"What are you doing here, Le'er?" Han Li asked as he gave Liu Le'er a gentle pat on the head.

"I just so happened to have been cultivating on Eight Plains Mountain, and His Majesty, Bai Ze, told me that you were here, so I came right away," Liu Le'er replied with a smile.

A surge of warmth welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this, scattering some of the ill intent that had been plaguing him all this time.

"Now that you're back in the primordial land, you should stay for good. We have plenty of cultivation resources here, and there won't be any Heavenly Court cultivators coming after you," Liu Le'er said in a hopeful manner.

"I wish I could stay, but there are many things that I need to take care of outside of the primordial land, so I'm going to have to leave soon," Han Li sighed.

Liu Le'er's face fell slightly upon hearing this, but she then immediately put on a smile again as she said, "It's alright, I know that you're destined for great things, so I won't try to keep you. However, you have to make sure to pay me regular visits."

"Alright, I'll make sure to come and visit whenever I have some spare time," Han Li promised.

He was also quite glad to see Liu Le'er again, and in their ensuing conversation, he learned that all of the elite cultivators of the most prominent primordial tribes had gathered once again on Eight Plains Mountain to cultivate together in a mysterious space created by Bai Ze and Yue Mian.

"What's wrong with your eyes, Brother Rock? And why do I sense such intense ill intent within you?" Liu Le'er asked in a concerned manner.

"At the moment, I'm trying to sever my wicked corpse soul to progress to the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, but there's been a slight hiccup, and things have gone a little awry. Having said that, there's no need for you to worry. I'll be fine once I've completely severed my wicked corpse soul," Han Li replied, downplaying the severity of his condition to assuage Liu Le'er's concerns.

"You're already severing your wicked corpse soul? You're progressing so quickly! But I heard from His Majesty that if you progress too quickly in your cultivation, then you won't be able to accumulate sufficient insights at each cultivation rank, and that'll be detrimental to your subsequent cultivation.

“In particular, after reaching the Great Encompassment Stage, one has to carefully assess the enhancements provided by each successive immortal acupoint that's opened. Otherwise, there's no way they'll be able to ensure a smooth corpse soul severance," Liu Le'er said.

"That is indeed the case," Han Li replied with a nod.

"If I recall correctly, you've been cultivating on your own this entire time with no master to guide you, isn't that right, Brother Rock? Do you have a suitable corpse soul severance technique to use?" Liu Le'er asked.

Chapter 1269: Return to a Former Home

"I'm afraid not. I've been searching for one for a very long time, but it's been a completely fruitless endeavor thus far," Han Li sighed with a shake of his head.

"That's a really big problem! Without a corpse soul severance technique to assist you, your chances of a successful corpse soul severance will be extremely slim!" Liu Le'er said in an urgent manner.

"Even so, I have to give it a try. Otherwise, I'll have no chance at all," Han Li replied with a smile.

Liu Le'er looked around momentarily, then flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip before quickly thrusting it into Han Li's hand as she said through voice transmission, "I'm also close to reaching the pinnacle of the early-Great Encompassment Stage, so Chief Liu Qing has recently bestowed upon me a corpse soul severance technique. You can have a copy of it, Brother Rock. Perhaps it'll suit you as well."

"Le'er, you can't just go around giving out something so precious! If the Heavenly Fox Tribe finds out, who knows what type of punishment will await you?" Han Li exclaimed as he immediately offered the jade slip back to her.

"You're someone extremely important to me, so it's not like I'm just handing out the corpse soul severance technique to anyone, and as long as neither of us say anything, there's no way the Heavenly Fox Tribe will find out. Even if they do find out, I bear the true spirit bloodline of the Nine Tailed Immortal Fox, making me the future hope of the Heavenly Fox Tribe, so they wouldn't do anything to me," Liu Le'er assured with a smile.

Han Li hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then nodded as he acquiesced, "Alright, in that case, I'll take it."

"I can't leave Eight Plains Mountain for too long, so I have to go back now. I was only able to visit you this time under special permission from His Majesty. If you return to the primordial land in the future, you have to make sure to come and see me," Liu Le'er said as she took a reluctant glance outside.

Han Li nodded in response, and Liu Le'er took one final glance at him before flying out of his cave abode as a streak of gray light, quickly vanishing out of sight.

Following Liu Le'er's departure, Han Li immediately began to examine the contents of the jade slip, and the first thing that he saw was a title that read: "Avatar Corpse Soul Severance Technique".

The title gave him an idea of the contents of the corpse soul severance technique, but he didn't dwell on it for too long as he continued reading through the rest of the jade slip.

There wasn't much content in the jade slip, so he was able to read through everything quite quickly, and the more he read, the more his eyes began to glow with excitement.

In summary, the Avatar Corpse Soul Severance Technique required one to refine an avatar with which they shared a spiritual connection, and through that connection, one would sever their wicked corpse soul by transferring it into the avatar.

One's three corpse souls were inseparable from oneself, and that was why they were so difficult to sever.

The essence of this Avatar Corpse Soul Severance Technique lied in transferring the three corpse souls out of one's body before sealing them into individual avatars. Once that was achieved, the connection between host and corpse soul would be significantly weakened, thereby making a successful severance far easier to accomplish.

However, there were two prerequisites to using this corpse soul severance technique, the first of which was that the host had to possess tremendous soul power. Otherwise, they would be unable to bear the strain of transferring their wicked corpse soul out of their body.

The second prerequisite was that the avatar had to be sufficiently compatible with the host, and the longer that the avatar had been in existence, the higher the chance of success.

Han Li withdrew his spiritual sense from the jade slip as a faint smile appeared on his face.

This Avatar Corpse Soul Severance Technique was almost tailor-made for him. Due to his cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique, his soul was far more powerful than that of the average early-Great Encompassment cultivator, and he also had that Earthly Deity Avatar waiting for him in the Black Wind Sea.

Having spent so many years apart, he had almost forgotten about the Earthly Deity Avatar, and he certainly hadn't ever anticipated that it would come in useful in this type of context.

With the ill intent in his body constantly corroding his soul, he had no time to waste. Thus, he immediately called upon Jin Tong and Weeping Soul to pack up all of the array tools in the cave abode, then prepared to set off for the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

However, proir to his departure, he paid a visit to Eight Plains Mountain, stopping several hundred kilometers away before extending a respectful salute from afar.

Bai Ze appeared before him amid a flash of white light, then smiled as he asked, "Are you leaving so soon, Fellow Daoist Han?"

"I have something urgent that I must go and do right away. I've come here to bid farewell, and to thank you for your hospitality, Senior Bai Ze," Han Li said.

"Don't mention it. I can see that the ill intent in your body has grown into a rather pressing concern, so this is indeed a rather urgent matter," Bai Ze remarked.

Han Li nodded in response.

"I'm not fully confident in my ability to overcome this ordeal. If I am to fail, then I'll have to ask you to look after Xiaobai and Liu Le'er of the Heavenly Fox Tribe in my stead."

"Of course, I would be looking out for them even if you didn't ask. Where are you planning to go, Fellow Daoist Han?" Bai Ze asked, and Han Li's brows reflexively furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Han, I have no intention of prying into your future plans. It's just that Yue Mian has a sky roaming ability that can take you to your destination far faster than you can get there, as long as it's not too far away," Bai Ze explained with a smile.

An enlightened look appeared on Han Li's face, and he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute as he said, "I see. Please forgive me for misunderstanding your intentions, Senior Bai Ze. I would like to go to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region."

"The Northern Glacial Immortal Region? That's not too far from here. Yue Mian, can your take Fellow Daoist Han there with your sky roaming ability?" Bai Ze asked.

Yue Mian instantly appeared out of thin air beside him and replied, "Of course."

"In that case, I'll have to trouble you to make the trip. Right now, Fellow Daoist Han is a wanted fugitive of the Heavenly Court, so it'll be rather difficult for him to travel from place to place," Bai Ze said.

"Thank you, Senior Bai Ze, Senior Yue Mian," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

"Save your thanks! Your humans and all of your formalities annoy me to no end!" Yue Mian harrumphed as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a ball of azure light, which quickly transformed into a semi-transparent azure bird that was around a hundred feet in size.

The azure bird swooped down onto Han Li in the blink of an eye before opening its beak to devour him whole.

Immediately thereafter, it spread its wings to slice open a spatial rift, then flew into the rift in a flash.

All of this had unfolded in the blink of an eye, far too quickly for Han Li to be able to react.

By the time he finally processed what had just happened, the azure bird was already racing through a boundless expanse of spatial turbulence.

Many complex spirit patterns appeared on its body to form a series of cloud-shaped designs, and there were also streams of azure runes that were flowing over its body like water, giving off extremely formidable and aerodynamic law power fluctuations, allowing the bird to slice through the surrounding spatial turbulence without any resistance like a hot knife through butter.

At this moment, Han Li was being held firmly into place by a burst of tremendous power that was swirling around within the giant bird's belly.

He had no intention of freeing himself, and he began to observe his surroundings in an intrigued manner.

The azure bird was incredibly fast, countless times faster than him, and the surrounding scenery was rapidly receding.

Around thirty hours later, the azure bird abruptly emerged from the spatial turbulence and appeared above a lush forest.

Immediately thereafter, it disintegrated into countless streams of azure light with a dull thump, while Han Li quickly stabilized himself in mid-air.

He released his spiritual sense to examine the surrounding area, and a hint of elation immediately appeared on his face as he flew away into the distance as a streak of golden light.

Before long, he arrived at a small city by the name of Bright Hill City.

He had never visited this city before, but back when he first left the Black Wind Sea to travel to the Blaze Dragon Dao, he had heard along the way that this was a city on the Primordial Wave Continent.

In the wake of his arrival on the Primordial Wave Continent, Han Li had developed a newfound sense of awe and veneration toward the unfathomable powers of Dao Ancestors.

If he had traveled from Eight Plains Mountain to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region himself, then even a hundred years may not have been enough for him to complete the journey, yet Yue Mian had transported him here in barely over a day.

With that in mind, Han Li extended a grateful bow in the direction of Eight Plains Mountain, then set off toward the Black Wind Sea.

......

Northern Glacial Immortal Region, Black Wind Sea.

Streaks of light were racing through the air above a vast expanse of clear, blue ocean, and all of these streaks of light were converging toward a lush island.

The island itself wasn't very large, but there were numerous floating island arrays set up around the island, forming a seven-island chain that presented a spectacular sight to behold.

At the very center of the island stood a gargantuan statue with its arms spread open like a deity embracing its followers.

At this moment, there were hundreds of thousands of island residents gathered on a giant, white stone plaza at the center of the island, and they were in the process of evacuating from the plaza, having just completed their morning prayer ceremony.

Some of the people on the plaza looked up briefly at the streaks of light racing through the sky overhead before quickly losing interest, while most of the island residents didn't even bother to look up at all, clearly already accustomed to such a sight.

Among the massive crowd was an elderly man with a head of white hair that presented a stark contrast with his dark skin, and there was a proud look on his face as he held onto the hand of a little boy who also had a rather dark complexion.

"You see that, Tiger? It's all thanks to our Ancestral God that all of the dozens of nearby islands in this region have pledged their subordination to our Dark Veil Island. The chiefs of those islands have to come here to pay their respects on this day every single year. How badass is that?" the elderly man said with a wide smile.

Chapter 1270: Return

"You rattle off the same spiel to me at this time every single year! I'm about to develop calluses in my ears!" Tiger complained in a disgruntled manner.

"Don't take that tone with me! Have I told you about that time..."

"You have! There was that time when our Dark Veil Island was almost razed to the ground by outside enemies, but our Ancestral God appeared just in the nick of time to eradicate the enemies," Tiger hurriedly interjected before his grandfather had a chance to tell the same story the ninety-eighth time.

"Now that I think about it, it's already been many, many years since I last saw our Ancestral God," the elderly man sighed.

Tiger was just about to offer him some words of consolation when his expression suddenly changed drastically as he yelled, "Grandpa, look!"

Immediately thereafter, a chorus of excited voices rang out from within the crowd as everyone stopped in their tracks to look back at the enormous Ancestral God statue at the center of the island.

Tiger's grandfather hurriedly turned around as well, and he was greeted by the sight of the statue giving off a layer of dazzling, blue radiance under the light of the morning sun, giving it the appearance of a gargantuan sapphire.

Waves of tremendous water law power fluctuations were surging out of the statue before spreading over the entire island, basking everyone in a blissful sensation of comfort.

"It's the Ancestral God!"

"The Ancestral God has appeared!"

"Our Ancestral God has come to bless us!"

The plaza erupted into a frenzy as everyone fell to their knees again before kowtowing in prayer.

Right at this moment, a figure appeared atop the statue, then rose up into the air before flying away, quickly vanishing out of sight.

All of the residents of Dark Veil Island erupted into a panic upon seeing this, and they began yelling in alarm as they hurriedly rose to their feet.

The figure passed by all of the chiefs that had just flown onto the island, and they reflexively stopped in their tracks before exchanging a few bewildered glances.

It was only when a slightly rotund, azure-robed man flew up into the air from the island did they heave a collective sigh of relief before hurriedly converging around him.

"Chief Luo Feng, was that the Ancestral God of the island just now?" a gray-robed chief asked.

There was a rather solemn look on Luo Feng's face, and he nodded silently in response as he cast his gaze toward the direction that the Ancestral God had departed in.

"What's going on? Are we under attack?" a purple-robed woman asked in an anxious manner.

Luo Feng took a moment to compose himself, then said, "Please go and wait for me in the conference hall for now. I'll be with all of you shortly."

In reality, he was also unaware of why the Ancestral God had suddenly come out of seclusion to leave the island.

The chiefs of the islands naturally couldn't pry any further, and they descended onto the island.

After a brief hesitation, Luo Feng also descended onto the plaza below.

"Chief Luo Feng!"

Everyone on the plaza hurriedly gathered around him and began asking a barrage of questions.

"There's no need to panic. It is a rare opportunity to see our Ancestral God in the flesh, and as long as you are earnest in your prayers to him, you will be sure to receive his blessings," Luo Feng said.

All of the island residents were ecstatic to hear this, and they began praying in earnest once again.

Where have you suddenly gone, Ancestral God?

Luo Feng heaved an internal sigh before setting off for the conference hall.

The chiefs of the other islands weren't going to be as easy to fool as these island residents.

......

Several thousand kilometers away from the island, a blue figure was racing over the sea before descending upon a black coral island that was only around a thousand feet in size. The blue figure was identical to Han Li in appearance, and it was none other than his Earthly Deity Avatar.

At this moment, Han Li and Jin Tong were standing on the island with their back facing the Earthly Deity Avatar.

"You've finally come back," the Earthly Deity Avatar said.

Han Li turned around to face his avatar as a faint smile appeared on his face, but before he had a chance to say anything, Jin Tong exclaimed, "So this is your Earthly Deity Avatar? It really does look exactly like you!"

She strode over to the avatar as she spoke, then walked in a circle around it while inspecting it from all angles.

"You've reached the late-Golden Immortal Stage. That's a little better than I expected," Han Li remarked.

"After I lost contact with you, I no longer had access to any time law crystals to accelerate my manifestation of heavy water, but on the flip side, I no longer had to supply heavy water to you, either. On top of that, I've been receiving a constant influx of power of faith over the years, so I've been able to progress decently quickly in my cultivation, and right now, I'm already able to manifest heavy water of the third level," the Earthly Deity Avatar replied.

Han Li was silent for a moment upon hearing this, then swept a sleeve through the air to summon his Heavy Water True Axis as he said, "I no longer have any use for this thing, and it's far more compatible with you anyway, so I'll leave it to you."

The black axis shrank down into a palm-sized disk at his behest as he spoke before drifting toward the Earthly Deity Avatar, and the latter caught the disk with a nod.

They were one and the same, so there was no need for expressions of gratitude.

"Luo Feng has done quite well in managing Dark Veil Island over the years. You may not think it all that impressive, but I think you should still go back and take a look," the Earthly Deity Avatar suggested.

Han Li hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then nodded in response, following which the three of them flew back to Dark Veil Island.

On the way there, Han Li instructed Jin Tong to return to the Flower Branch domain for now, while he channeled his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique to conceal his own aura before entering the island in secret.

Upon arriving on the plaza in the island, he discovered that all of the island's residents were still praying in earnest.

The Earthly Deity Avatar performed another "divine miracle" atop the statue to assure the island's residents that their Ancestral God hadn't abandoned them, and only after that did it depart.

Inside the conference hall, Luo Feng was seated at the head of the table, calmly sipping on some tea, while the chiefs of the other islands were discussing the matter of the Dark Veil Island Ancestral God's excursion in hushed tones.

"Chief Luo, the Ancestral God has never made an appearance during any of our previous annual visits, why has he suddenly left the island this time?" one of the island chiefs asked in a careful manner.

It was very rare for an Ancestral God to leave their island, and this applied to all Ancestral Gods across the Black Wind Sea. After all, only by remaining on their own territory, where they're surrounded by their followers, could they constantly be showered with the power of faith.

On top of that, this entire region of the sea had been taken over by Dark Veil Island, so conflicts had become extremely rare, and there was really no need for the Ancestral God himself to ever address anything in person.

Hence, his sudden departure was rather alarming.

"There's no need to be alarmed, everyone. The Ancestral God has only gone out to check on something, and he's already returned to the island," Luo Feng said.

He had just received a voice transmission from the Earthly Deity Avatar, and that left him feeling far more assured.

Everyone was rather skeptical to hear this, but a burst of tremendous power suddenly swept over the entire conference hall to back up Luo Feng's claim, only to then fade away an instant later.

The meeting of island chiefs quickly concluded, and all of the chiefs paid their respects to the Ancestral God statue before returning to their own islands, while Luo Feng hurriedly made his way straight to the Ancestral God Hall, which was a restricted area on the island.

The Ancestral God Hall was situated right below the Ancestral God statue at the center of the island, and it was where the Earthly Deity Avatar normally stayed in seclusion.

By the time Luo Feng arrived at the hall, the door was already open, and he announced his own arrival before stepping aside.

The Earthly Deity Avatar was seated with its legs crossed on a cushion, and Luo Feng extended a respectful bow as he greeted, "Luo Feng pays his respects to the esteemed Ancestral God."

"How did the meeting go?" the Earthly Deity Avatar asked.

"Aside from the few islands that pledged their allegiance to us from the outset, the other islands are still not fully loyal to us, and in the wake of your sudden departure, they immediately began probing and asking questions," Luo Feng replied.

"That's fine. Your current True Immortal Stage cultivation base will be enough intimidation to keep them in check," the Earthly Deity Avatar said.

"It's all thanks to your protection that our Dark Veil Island has been able to become what it is today. At all times, you are the core of our island, and that is something that I've never forgotten," Luo Feng hurriedly said as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly appeared in the room and remarked, "I took a stroll around the island just now, and I can see that you've done a very good job managing everything."

Luo Feng hurriedly turned to Han Li in an alarmed manner, and upon catching sight of him, an incredulous look appeared on his face as he exclaimed, "Is that you, Master Liu?"

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, and only then did he recall that he had been using the alias of Liu Shi here.

"That's right," he replied.

Luo Feng hurriedly extended another deep bow upon hearing this.

"Luo Feng pays his respects to Master Liu Shi!"

"No need for formalities. I've actually come to you with a request," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of gentle force to help Luo Feng back up into a standing position.

The Earthly Deity Avatar and Luo Feng both faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which the latter hurriedly replied, "Whatever you need, the entirety of Dark Veil Island is at your service."

"I'm going to go into seclusion in the Black Wind Sea for a while, and I need you to find me a secluded and unpopulated island," Han Li said.

Chapter 1271: Convincing Oneself

"Frostless Island would be perfect for your needs! The island is surrounded by sharp coral, and the sea around it is extremely turbulent and inhospitable. On top of that, the entire island is completely devoid of life, so the island itself and a huge area around it is completely uninhabited," Luo Feng said.

"I need you to help me set up an array on this island," Han Li requested in a direct and straightforward manner.

"I'm happy to be of service," Luo Feng said.

Han Li pulled out a set of blueprints and a black storage ring that he had already prepared earlier, then handed them to Luo Feng as he said, "These are the blueprints and materials required for the array. Get started as soon as possible, and make sure the array is complete within seven days."

Luo Feng inspected the contents of the blueprints and the storage ring briefly, then immediately said, "I'll have it arranged right away."

"There's no hurry. I have here some cultivation arts and spirit medicines for Dark Veil Island. You can take them as well," Han Li said as he tossed Luo Feng a white storage ring, who caught it before immediately kowtowing to the ground in gratitude without even first inspecting its contents.

Following Luo Feng's departure, Han Li turned his gaze to the Earthly Deity Avatar, and the latter also raised its head to look back at him.

A reminiscent look appeared in Han Li's eyes at the sight of his identical avatar.

The avatar had been born from a wisp of his soul in conjunction with a Soulbirth Flower, and it was a separate, sentient being from himself. With communication between them severed for all these years, it had become even more independent, so in a sense, it was both a part of him, but also not a part of him.

As long as this avatar existed, even if he were to meet an untimely demise, his presence in this world wouldn't be completely erased.

Due to the fact that the avatar had been born from a wisp of his soul, Han Li could seize back absolute control over it at any time.

Of course, that was an option that he would only turn to as a last resort as once the avatar lost its sense of self, it would be unable to continue presiding over Dark Veil Island in his stead.

"I have a request for you," Han Li said.

"Go ahead. We are one and the same, so just speak to me as if you were speaking to yourself," the Earthly Deity Avatar said.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li gently brushed a hand over his own face, removing his disguise to reveal his true appearance.

There was a strange, black rune emblazoned onto his glabella, and his were shimmering with crimson light, while a formidable, baleful aura was emanating from his body.

A chill instantly ran down the Earthly Deity Avatar's spine at the sight of the rune on his glabella, and it felt as if it were looking at a vicious beast that could tear its way out of the skin on Han Li's forehead at any moment.

"What happened to you?"

Given that they had lost contact with one another for such an extended period of time, it had no idea about Han Li's current condition.

Immediately thereafter, an even more astonished look appeared on its face as it exclaimed, "Your cultivation base!"

Earlier, Han Li had concealed his true cultivation base, and only now had he fully revealed it.

"Right now, I'm at the pinnacle of the early-Great Encompassment Stage, and I must sever my wicked corpse soul," Han Li explained with a wry smile.

"You're already at the Great Encompassment Stage?"

Even as Han Li's Earthly Deity Avatar, it couldn't help but be completely flabbergasted to hear this.

As an Earthly Immortal, it was essentially taking a shortcut as far as cultivation was concerned, and as long as it had enough followers to supply it with the power of faith, its rate of progression should've been faster than that of the average cultivator.

Given the rapid expansion of Dark Veil Island's forces, the Earthly Deity Avatar had been gaining more and more followers at an unprecedented rate.

As a result, it had been progressing quite quickly in its cultivation, but Han Li had completely put it to shame.

"Do you need my help in your corpse soul severance?" the Earthly Deity Avatar asked.

"That's right. The three corpse souls arise from their host's attachments, and their power grows alongside that of their host, so they're extremely difficult to sever through the power of one's soul alone. I was fortunate enough to have obtained a corpse soul severance technique that can allow me to transfer my wicked corpse soul into your body as a medium, thereby significantly increasing my chances of success," Han Li explained.

"What are the risks involved?" the Earthly Deity Avatar asked.

"Corpse soul severance is an extremely perilous endeavor in itself, and in the process, my soul could easily be devoured by my wicked corpse soul, allowing it to take over my body. Even if I can successfully sever my wicked corpse soul and seal it into your body, there's a very good chance that it'll take over this body of yours," Han Li replied.

The Earthly Deity Avatar's brows furrowed slightly as it asked, "So essentially, I'm going to be used as a vessel for your corpse soul, is that right?"

"That's right," Han Li replied with a nod.

A peculiar look appeared on the Earthly Deity Avatar's face as it asked, "If you were in my place, would you agree to something like this?"

"This is not an entirely detrimental arrangement for you. Ultimately, there are only so many people residing in this region of the Black Wind Sea. I presume that the biggest reason why you haven't been able to reach the High Zenith Stage all this time is because there's only so much power of faith that you can receive from your followers, and that's not enough to bring about a breakthrough, isn't that right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right," the Earthly Deity Avatar replied with a nod.

"I have a way to help you break free from the restrictions of your Earthly Immortal body so that you'll no longer have to rely on the power of faith," Han Li said.

The Earthly Deity Avatar shook its head in a skeptical manner as it said, "I'm sure you understand the nature of the connection between this Earthly Immortal body of mine and Dark Veil Island better than anyone else, how could this connection possibly be severed?"

"I understand that over the years, the connection between your Earthly Immortal body and Dark Veil Island will only have become more and more deeply ingrained. However, you have no idea how much power my wicked corpse soul possesses. Once it enters your body, it'll be sure to make modifications to better suit itself, and with its Great Encompassment Stage power, severing your reliance on the power of faith will be an easy task," Han Li explained.

The Earthly Deity Avatar fell into deep thought upon hearing this, and only after a long silence did it ask, "Is this really feasible?"

"I would say that I'm at least 70% to 80% confident that it can be done," Han Li replied with a nod.

"What will become of the residents of Dark Veil Island then?" the Earthly Deity Avatar asked.

"Even if we set aside the fact that Luo Feng has already reached the True Immortal Stage, if you wish to protect the island, then you can remain here for as long as you please. With the resources and treasures that I left behind for them, they won't have to fear anyone in the Black Wind Sea. Also, severing their ties to their Ancestral God can be a good thing for them as well," Han Li replied.

The Earthly Deity Avatar nodded in response, seemingly swayed by Han Li's words.

"It may sound like this is going to be a simple process, but in reality, it won't be easy. Firstly, your current body may not be able to withstand the tremendous influx of power brought into it by the wicked corpse soul. Secondly, if your soul is unprotected, then it will most definitely be devoured by the wicked corpse soul," Han Li continued.

"I'm sure you already have some solutions in mind, right?" the Earthly Deity Avatar asked.

"That's right. The array that I instructed Luo Feng to set up is designed to refine your Earthly Immortal body. As for your soul, I will seal it away using a secret technique, placing you into a state of complete slumber. The wicked corpse soul won't be able to detect your existence, so it naturally won't be able to devour you," Han Li replied.

A hesitant look appeared on the Earthly Deity Avatar's face upon hearing this.

"Rest assured, prior to commencing my corpse soul severance, I will bind your body to Frostless Island. Only after taking over your body and completing the modifications on it will the wicked corpse soul be able to break free, and by then, I will have already successfully consolidated my mid-Great Encompassment Stage cultivation base, so I'll be able to capture it with ease.

“After that, all I'll have to do is extract it out of your body and seal it away again," Han Li reassured.

"So you'll have to consolidate your mid-Great Encompassment Stage cultivation base before it completely takes over my body, is that right?" the Earthly Deity Avatar asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"Compared with the rest of the process, that should be the easy part," Han Li replied in a confident manner.

"In that case, it seems like this is a feasible plan," the Earthly Deity Avatar said after some further contemplation.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon hearing this.

It had not been an easy task to convince himself, but only with the full cooperation of the Earthly Deity Avatar would he be able to use his corpse soul severance technique to the best effect.

......

Seven days flew by in a flash.

There was an inhospitable region of the Black Wind Sea that was filled with islands of sharp coral, some of which were visible above the surface, while others were lurking just below the waves.

At the center of the area was a strange, gray island, and whenever the surrounding, turbulent waves crashed into the island, they would immediately rise up to form vast walls of water over a thousand feet tall.

This was the uninhabited Frostless Island, and right at this moment, a group of four figures descended onto the island from above, and they were none other than Han Li and his Earthly Deity Avatar, as well as Luo Feng and Jin Tong.

The group descended onto the center of the island, and the mountain there had already been completely shaved away to create a flat plaza, upon which a hexagonal, blue altar that was several hundred feet tall had been constructed.

Chapter 1272: Preparations Complete

"This array and this altar were constructed according to your specifications, Master Liu. Here are all of the leftover materials," Luo Feng said as he offered up a black storage ring with both hands.

Han Li had already examined the altar to find that it had been constructed in a very sound manner, and he waved a hand as he said, "You can keep it."

"Thank you, Master Liu!" Luo Feng hurriedly replied in an ecstatic fashion.

"I've already taught you how to operate the array. I'm going to get Jin Tong to stand on lookout duty for you, so you can cultivate here in peace, but I can only give you forty-nine days," Han Li said.

"If this array really is as powerful as you say, then forty-nine days will be plenty," the Earthly Deity Avatar replied.

Luo Feng was observing the conversation between the two with a perplexed look in his eyes, but Han Li made no effort to explain anything to him as he flew down onto the altar.

He walked a lap along the edge of the altar, depositing round stones that were filled with abundant water law powers into the slots on the altar one by one.

After that, he returned to the ground as he said, "Alright, you can enter the array now."

The Earthly Deity Avatar nodded in response, then leaped onto the center of the altar before sitting down with its legs crossed.

Before long, the sound of an incantation rang out, and the entire altar began swaying violently as pillars of light rose up into the air from its surface, stirring up the clouds above to form an enormous, funnel-shaped vortex.

Tremendous bursts of water-attribute spiritual qi converged toward the vortex from all directions before being funneled down onto the altar.

The Earthly Deity Avatar was instantly basked in a layer of blue light that turned its body translucent, and it began absorbing the influx of spiritual qi.

"You stay here and keep a lookout for forty-nine days," Han Li instructed as he patted Jin Tong on the shoulder.

"You can count on me, Uncle," Jin Tong replied with a nonchalant mood.

Han Li knew that it was very unrealistic to expect her to fully focus on something unless it was devouring precious treasures.

Thankfully, this was a very secluded place far away from the Heavenly Court's forces, so it was relatively safe, and if anyone dared to try and spoil Han Li's plans, then Jin Tong would be able to easily scare them away.

"Luo Feng, come back to Dark Veil Island with me," Han Li instructed, and the two of them promptly departed.

"I know you're perplexed about what I'm doing, right?" Han Li asked as the two of them flew through the air alongside one another.

Luo Feng didn't know how to respond, so he could only nod in silence.

"I wasn't planning to keep you in the dark anyway..."

With that, Han Li revealed to Luo Feng his plans of modifying his Earthly Deity Avatar, but of course, he kept the matter regarding his corpse soul severance a secret.

Initially, Luo Feng was horrified to hear about this arrangement, but he was quickly reassured after learning about all of the preparations that Han Li had made.

"It's all thanks to you that our Dark Veil Island has been able to reach such prosperous heights, Master Liu. I'm extremely grateful for the fact that you disclosed all of this to me, even though you could've easily chosen not to. Seeing as you've already made such meticulous arrangements, I have no objections and am willing to help in any way that I can," Luo Feng said as he extended a deep bow, and Han Li gave a pleased nod upon hearing this.

From there, Han Li remained on Dark Veil Island to instruct Luo Feng to complete the rest of the preparations in secret.

This was an island that was built upon faith, and the conversion process was not going to be so easy.

Hence, Han Li had begun addressing the matter from the most foundational level, selecting some children from the island with exceptional cultivation aptitude before gathering them in the Ancestral God Hall to instruct them on the basics of cultivation.

With the seed of change planted and Luo Feng pulling some strings from behind the scenes, it was only a matter of time before Dark Veil Island was gradually transformed into a place similar to an immortal sect.

After forty-nine days, Han Li departed from Dark Veil Island and traveled to Frostless Island.

He was immediately approached by Jin Tong, who complained, "You're finally back, Uncle. That avatar of yours came out of seclusion four days ago, and it's been sitting like a statue this entire time. You should check on it to make sure that it hasn't actually turned into a statue!"

"The array must've caused quite a commotion these past forty-nine days. Did anyone come to check on what was happening?" Han Li asked.

"Some people came the day after you left, and many more groups of people came after that, but none of them dared to get too close, and I chased them away just like you instructed," Jin Tong replied.

"How did you chase them away?" Han Li asked in a skeptical manner.

"I told them what you told me to say, that the Ancestral God of Dark Veil Island was cultivating in seclusion here, and that no one was to disturb him," Jin Tong replied as she averted her eyes in a sheepish manner.

"You didn't get physical with anyone?" Han Li asked.

"Well... I did beat up that one guy. I already told him to piss off, but he still snuck back a second time, so I flicked him on the head and sent him plunging to the seabed. It took quite a while for him to float back up to the surface," Jin Tong replied with a sheepish smile.

"You didn't kill him, did you?" Han Li asked.

"No, no, I didn't even put any force into my flick, and no one else dared to come after what happened to him," Jin Tong replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then leaped onto the altar on the island.

All of the water-attribute Immortal Origin Stones that had been embedded into the altar had already turned a lifeless, gray color, clearly indicating that the immortal spiritual power that they contained had already been absorbed by the Earthly Deity Avatar.

At this moment, the Earthly Deity Avatar was seated with its legs crossed, and its body was still in a near-translucent state. As a result, all of its internal organs were visible, and immortal spiritual power and the power of faith could be seen circulating through them.

A miniature, blue figure that resembled a nascent soul could be seen in the avatar's head, but it was nowhere near as clear as a nascent soul and appeared more like a cloud of mist.

"You've already reached the desired state," Han Li said with a pleased nod.

Right at this moment, a miniature, glowing figure suddenly scattered like smoke before spreading over the avatar's entire body, restoring it to its normal, opaque state.

"I'm ready. What do I need to do next?" the Earthly Deity Avatar asked as its eyes sprang open.

Han Li offered no response as he smiled and swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light, and Weeping Soul stepped out from within.

Following such an extended period of rest and recuperation, she had already fully recovered from her injuries, and her cultivation base had also returned to its peak.

"This is Weeping Soul. She is going to seal away your soul and spiritual sense through the use of a secret technique to put you into a state of slumber," Han Li said.

The Earthly Deity Avatar took a glance at Weeping Soul before nodding in response.

After that, he closed his eyes and waited for her to begin.

Han Li gave Weeping Soul a nod, and she immediately strode over to the Earthly Deity Avatar before pressing her joined middle and index fingers against its glabella.

A speck of dark red light emerged over her fingertips, and bursts of formidable soul power fluctuations came surging out from within.

Han Li observed the proceedings for a moment before stepping down from the altar.

With a flick of his wrist, a stack of array tools appeared over the palm of his hand, and he placed them down over certain strategic locations on the island.

After around four hours, Han Li had covered virtually every single inch of the island, having planted close to two thousand array flags and array plates in the process.

By the time he returned to the altar, Weeping Soul had also finished what she was doing. The Earthly Deity Avatar had reverted back to its previous, translucent state, but the hazy figure in its head was already nowhere to be seen.

Han Li released his spiritual sense to carefully inspect the Earthly Deity Avatar, and he was rather taken aback by what he saw.

"Even with my spiritual sense and spiritual connection with my avatar, I'm no longer able to detect its soul. Could it be that you've pulled its soul out of its body?" Han Li asked.

"I wouldn't do that," Weeping Soul replied with a smile. "Didn't you tell me that the soul of an Ancestral God can't leave their body for extended periods of time?"

"In that case, this soul sealing secret technique of yours is truly impressive," Han Li praised.

Weeping Soul was quite pleased with his praise, and she pointed a finger at one of the Earthly Deity Avatar's hands, upon which an indistinct, longan-sized figure appeared momentarily within the palm of its hand before quickly fading away again.

"If even I can't detect its soul, then there's no way that my wicked corpse soul will be able to detect anything," Han Li said, then flipped a hand over to produce an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword before using it to carve an array into the ground.

This array was far more complex than any that Han Li had ever seen before, and it consisted of three layers.

Each layer was filled with countless tiny runes, and after completing the array, Han Li summoned around a dozen Immortal Origin Stones and several treasures that contained spiritual power of different attributes before placing them down onto the important points in the array.

By the time all of the preparations were complete, the sun had already set down to sea level, basking the entire sea in a warm, orange glow.

"Jin Tong has gone out to play again. Get her to come back here, and the two of you will be stationed at the northernmost and southernmost tips of the island," Han Li instructed.

Weeping Soul nodded in response before turning to depart, but Han Li raised a hand to stop her as he continued, "From this point onward, whenever the array on the altar is activated, you two will have to activate the restrictions that I've set up on the island. Regardless of what happens on the altar, do not interfere. All you have to do is focus on guarding the island to ensure that no one comes in and no one leaves. Understood?"

"Understood," Weeping Soul replied with a nod, then flew away to fetch Jin Tong.

Chapter 1273: Corpse Soul Severance

Following Weeping Soul's departure, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to transfer his Earthly Deity Avatar into the innermost layer of the array, which resembled a yin yang diagram.

He then sat down across from his avatar on the yang side of the diagram, while the avatar occupied the yin half.

After that, he began to temper his own aura, and his aura gradually completely subsided, as if he were using his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique.

Shortly thereafter, Jin Tong and Weeping Soul returned to guard the northernmost and southernmost points of the island, as instructed by Han Li.

Meanwhile, Han Li began to chant an incantation, and a burst of golden light appeared over the outermost layer of the altar, forming a hemispherical light barrier that encompassed the entire altar.

Countless runes could be seen swimming over the surface of the light barrier, giving off rays of dazzling, golden light.

After that, the middle layer of the array also lit up alongside all of the treasures that had been placed in it. Pillars of light rose up from these treasures, with their colors reflecting the different attributes of said treasures.

These pillars of light transformed into a series of translucent chains, each of which pierced into a major acupoint in the Earthly Deity Avatar's body.

All of these acupoints were going to be important obstacles for the wicked corpse soul to bypass while modifying the avatar's body, so Han Li had to seize control of these acupoints in advance as a safety precaution.

Only after countless chains had emerged from the second layer of the array before piercing into the Earthly Deity Avatar's body did the innermost layer of the array finally begin to glow with black and white light.

In contrast with the previous two layers, only a thin light barrier emerged from the third layer of the array.

Han Li cast his gaze out of the altar to discover that countless pillars of light had also arisen across the entire island, forming a radiant, golden pagoda that loomed over the entirety of Frostless Island.

With the Treasured Pagoda Demon Subduing Array already activated by Jin Tong and Weeping Soul, Han Li was able to fully focus on the task at hand, and he immersed his spiritual sense fully into his own consciousness.

At this moment, half of his consciousness was enshrouded under a suffocating blanket of dark clouds, while the other was filled by a vast sea of blood.

Ever since half of the Origin Separation Law Chains were unraveled last time, the wicked corpse soul had been gaining power at a rapid rate, and even though Han Li had already subdued it several more times since then, the outcome had been far from encouraging.

Generally speaking, once a wicked corpse soul took shape, it had to be severed as soon as possible, and it was considered a grave mistake for one to allow their wicked corpse soul to linger in their body for as long as Han Li had.

Not only was the wicked corpse soul growing rapidly in power, it had corroded Han Li's consciousness to a very concerning degree, to the point that it was now almost on equal footing with him.

If he delayed his corpse soul severance for much longer, then it would be able to struggle free from the Origin Separation Law Chains to force a showdown.

Han Li's soul flew through the air while the two halves of his consciousness clashed violently against one another.

The wicked corpse soul was suspended in mid-air by the Origin Separation Law Chains, and it looked up at Han Li with a sinister grin as it chuckled, "You sure kept me waiting..."

"It sounds like you've been waiting for me this entire time," Han Li remarked with a smile.

"You know that you can't keep me trapped here forever, so it was only ever a matter of time before you were forced to release me," the wicked corpse soul said.

"You're right. Now that you're already a separate entity from me, I'm unable to stop you from continuing to grow in power by the day. Hence, I'm going to sever you here and now," Han Li declared.

"And what makes you think you won't be the one to be severed?" the wicked corpse soul sneered.

"Right now, you do indeed possess the power to pose a significant threat to me, but a clash between us would be sure to leave this body in ruins, and that won't benefit either of us," Han Li said.

"Even if I come into possession of a ruined body, that would still put me in a far better position than the one that I'm in now, so that's only something that you have to worry about," the wicked corpse soul replied in a cold and nonchalant manner.

"In that case, what if you manage to defeat me, but I detonate this body of mine in my final moments to take you down with me?" Han Li threatened.

The wicked corpse soul's expression finally stiffened slightly upon hearing this, but it then smiled as it said, "I don't believe you'd go that far. I am you, so even if your body is taken over by me, that's still better than to suffer a fate of mutual destruction. Besides, you don't have the spine to do something like that anyway!"

"Is that right? I didn't think that my wicked corpse soul would be such a terrible judge of my character. If you don't believe me, then feel free to test me," Han Li said as he clasped his hands behind his back, and the wicked corpse soul fell silent upon hearing this.

Despite what it had just said, it knew that Han Li was indeed capable of doing what he had threatened.

"Now that you believe me, how about we discuss an alternate solution that'll benefit both of us?" Han Li suggested with a smile.

"What do you have in mind?" the wicked corpse soul asked.

"I've already prepared an avatar of an extremely high caliber for you in advance. Once you possess the avatar and refine it, you'll have a body of your own just the same," Han Li said.

The wicked corpse soul burst into laughter upon hearing this.

"Even a three-year-old wouldn't believe such a ridiculous lie! I am your wicked corpse soul, and I'll be constantly plotting your downfall! How could you possibly be willing to grant me a body and set me free?"

"Right now, I'm only focused on severing you from my soul. As for the consequences, I'll deal with those as they come. That's the solution that I propose, it's up to you whether you believe me or not," Han Li said.

"Are you really not lying to me?" the wicked corpse soul asked in a hesitant manner.

"Why don't you take a look for yourself?" Han Li said with a smile, then opened up his soul slightly to allow the wicked corpse soul to sense the Earthly Deity Avatar.

After examining the avatar for a moment, the wicked corpse soul said, "Its aura is quite compatible with mine. Looks like you really did prepare it for me. In that case, I'll trust you just this once."

A pleased smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and all of the remaining Origin Separation Law Chains unraveled on their own at his behest before dissipating into a cloud of black mist.

The wicked corpse soul slowly rose to its feet, then began stretching its body, and a string of cracks and pops rang out from all of its joints.

"I'm truly touched that you went out of your way to create an avatar for me, but I still prefer this original body of yours. If one of us has to leave, then why not let it be you?" it said with a sinister smile as it cocked its head to the side.

"I knew you would do this. Looks like I'll have to take a more forceful route," Han Li sighed, then flipped a hand over to summon a lightning longsword that was identical in style to his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

"I'd gladly oblige with your arrangements if you can defeat me," the wicked corpse soul grinned, and it also conjured up a longsword in the same style as the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, but as opposed to Han Li's sword of golden lightning, its sword was formed by crimson lightning.

Han Li sprang forward, seizing the initiative as he lashed out with his sword, but the wicked corpse soul made no effort to defend itself as it thrust its sword directly at Han Li in retaliation.

A rumbling thunderclap rang out as a bolt of crimson lightning sprang out of the tip of its sword before hurtling toward Han Li like a crimson spear.

In response, Han Li rose up higher into the air to evade the oncoming attack while simultaneously arriving directly above the wicked corpse soul.

Arcs of golden lightning sprang out of his sword before descending upon the wicked corpse soul to surround it like a lightning vortex, and before the wicked corpse soul had a chance to react, an array suddenly lit up beneath its feet.

Numerous lightning chains then sprang out of the surrounding area without any warning before linking together with the lightning descending from above, forming a golden cage around the wicked corpse soul.

A mocking sneer appeared on Han Li's face as he looked down upon the trapped wicked corpse soul.

"When did you prepare this lightning array?" the wicked corpse soul yelled with a furious expression.

"Of course it was while I was talking to you just now. Otherwise, why do you think I wasted so much time when I knew you were just going to pull off this stunt anyway?" Han Li sneered.

All of a sudden, the wicked corpse soul burst into laughter as it chortled, "As expected of you, or should I say, myself?"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and a sense of foreboding welled up in his heart at the sight of the wicked corpse soul's deranged expression.

Right at this moment, his entire consciousness began to tremble violently, and the crimson half began to bubble and churn like a pot of boiling water.

Huge bubbles appeared over the surface of the vast sea of blood, and plumes of bloody vapor rose up into the air to join the crimson clouds above.

A turbulent wave of blood rose up from down below to completely inundate the wicked corpse soul alongside the entire lightning cage around him, and by the time the wave of blood receded, it had already broken free.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face as he immediately made a hand seal, and a deafening thunderclap rang out as countless arcs of golden lightning began to intertwine within his half of his consciousness.

Chapter 1274: Let Loose

Han Li's entire consciousness was instantly filled with howling gusts of wind and deafening thunderclaps, and neither Han Li nor the wicked corpse soul uttered a single word as they charged at one another with single-minded determination.

At the same time, the two halves of Han Li's consciousness also erupted into a frenzy as they prepared for an almighty clash.

Han Li and the wicked corpse soul employed very simple attacks, with the former's fist clashing against the latter's palm, and immediately thereafter, the two halves of Han Li's consciousness also collided.

High up in the sky, crimson and golden lightning intertwined, while down below, two turbulent seas clashed with unstoppable might, with both sides itching to devour the other.

Han Li felt as if his soul were about to be torn apart, and he hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might, sending all of his spiritual sense crashing toward the wicked corpse soul.

"Do you still not get it? I am now the dominant force in your consciousness! The more enraged you get, the more powerful I become, so let the flame of your wrath burn brighter!" the wicked corpse soul sneered, then thrust both palms forward to release a burst of tremendous power.

The weight of half of Han Li's consciousness came crashing down upon him, and despite his best efforts to resist, he was still involuntarily pushed back.

As a result, the crimson half of Han Li's consciousness was able to gain the upper hand, and as it began to conquer more and more space, its crimson coloration began to slowly fade, as if it were gradually returning to normal, much to Han Li's alarm.

This indicated that the wicked corpse soul was gradually taking his place and becoming the legitimate force in this space. Once his half of his consciousness was completely overwhelmed, his spiritual sense would be rejected as a foreign infiltrator.

If that were to happen, the best outcome that he could hope for would be to be banished from his own body, but it was much more likely that he would be devoured and assimilated instead.

"You've lost! Rest assured, I'm going to take your place and elevate you to heights that you'll never be able to touch!" the wicked corpse soul cackled with elation at the sight of its crushing advantage.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly sneered, "Have you not heard that it's a bad habit to celebrate too early?"

In the next instant, a gargantuan yin yang symbol suddenly appeared beneath Han Li and the wicked corpse soul, and each of them occupied one half of the symbol.

The wicked corpse soul's expression instantly stiffened upon seeing this, and it roared in a frantic voice, "No! How could this be..."

Immediately thereafter, the yin yang symbol began to glow with black and white light, and it also spun around to completely reverse the state of the two halves of Han Li's consciousness.

Han Li let loose a thunderous roar as he thrust both palms downward with all his might, and the dominant half of his consciousness instantly crushed the other half, recombining the two into one.

At the same time, Han Li's eyes sprang open atop the altar on Frostless Island, and blood was flowing out of all of his orifices, while a ball of black shot out of his glabella.

A burst of condensed immortal spiritual power was dragging along behind the ball of black light like a disruptive veil, and in the instant that it flew out of Han Li's body, it abruptly swerved around to try and re-enter through his glabella.

However, right at this moment, a burst of radiant light suddenly erupted out of the yin dot in the yang half of the symbol to suck in the ball of black light, and in the next instant, the ball of black light re-emerged from the yang dot in the yin half of the symbol before vanishing into the Earthly Deity Avatar's glabella without a trace.

The entire altar was silent for close to twenty seconds, following which a guttural roar of boundless fury and indignation rang out.

The Earthly Deity Avatar had reopened its eyes, and they were filled with malicious rage as it threw its hands over its head with a twisted look on its face.

It immediately tried to rise to its feet, only to discover that it was unable to control this body at all, and that only further exacerbated its fury.

Han Li was sitting across from it with his aura fluctuating in an unsteady fashion, and he appeared to be in quite a sorry state, but all eight hundred and forty of his immortal acupoints had been opened, elevating him to the mid-Great Encompassment Stage.

However, the wicked corpse soul had taken part of his immortal spiritual power with it, so he would need time to rest and recuperate before he could stabilize his aura and consolidate his mid-Great Encompassment Stage cultivation base.

"It's going to take you some time and effort to be able to gain control over this body. Don't say I didn't warn you," Han Li said in a calm and composed manner, then closed his eyes to focus on his recuperation.

Only then did the wicked corpse soul notice the chains that were protruding out of its body, and it quickly realized that Han Li was trying to use this body as a cage to trap it.

It was naturally furious to the extreme, but it had no choice but to compose itself and try to refine this body.

As the wicked corpse soul's power began to circulate within the lifeless body, it began to take on rapid changes, and the Earthly Immortal body was rapidly being converted into a normal body of flesh.

Bursts of spiritual power began boring tiny tunnels into the body, forming veins and meridians to connect all of its internal organs.

The body's chest began to slowly rise and fall, and it really was beginning to give rise to renewed vitality.

Even though Han Li's eyes were closed, he was constantly keeping tabs on the wicked corpse soul with his spiritual sense, and he had no choice but to reopen his eyes upon sensing the rapid progress that it was making.

The wicked corpse soul was far more compatible with this body than he had imagined, and this current rate of modification was both alarming and concerning.

Right as he was about to activate the array on the altar to subjugate the wicked corpse soul, it sprang into action first.

All of its baleful qi had vanished without a trace, replaced by waves of immense water law power fluctuations that surged out of its body, while its aura also rapidly swelled.

Crap!

The golden light barrier overhead was especially potent in subjugating baleful qi, and it had been designed to trap the wicked corpse soul, but it seemed to have realized this and completely restrained all of its baleful qi.

A resounding boom rang out as an overpowering wave of blue light erupted out of the wicked corpse soul's body, scattering all of the surrounding chains.

Immediately thereafter, it rose up into the sky, propelled by a blue water dragon, and crashed straight into the golden light barrier up above.

A dull thud rang out, and the golden light barrier remained intact, while the water dragon erupted into a vast volume of water.

"Get back here!" Han Li roared as he made a grab for the wicked corpse soul's ankle, only for it to disintegrate into water amid a flash of blue light.

As a result, Han Li grabbed onto nothing but a fistful of water, and before he had a chance to do anything else, a resounding boom rang out up above as the wicked corpse soul burst through the golden light barrier, then fled the scene without any hesitation.

Right at this moment, a dazzling, golden, seven-story pagoda appeared out of thin air before descending rapidly upon the wicked corpse soul, while Han Li closed in on it from down below.

However, before he was able to reach it, another deafening boom rang out up above, and a massive hole was blown into the top of the pagoda.

A vast expanse of black light was gushing out of the hole, and a broken piece of a black wheel could be seen within it.

The wicked corpse soul had detonated its Heavy Water True Axis in order to break out of the Treasured Pagoda Demon Subduing Array!

"I was too careless today, but I'll be back to exact my revenge!"

A resentful roar rang out in the sky, following which a streak of black light came plunging down into the sea, raising an enormous wave in the process.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face as he hurriedly set off in pursuit.

Compared with the risks of failing to consolidate his cultivation base in a timely fashion, it was a far greater risk to allow his wicked corpse soul to run free.

Hence, he had to capture it at all costs.

All of this had unfolded in the blink of an eye, and Jin Tong and Weeping Soul still had no clue what had just happened, but they hurriedly set off after Han Li, nonetheless.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li had already flown several hundred feet, but the wicked corpse soul was nowhere to be seen, so he could only pause for the moment and channel his Spirit Refinement Technique to aid him in his search.

"What happened, Uncle?" Jin Tong hurriedly asked.

"My Earth Deity Avatar has been corroded by the power of faith of countless people, and that power of faith is imbued with all types of malicious fixations like vengeance and bloodlust. Hence, its body is extremely compatible with the wicked corpse soul, and it was able to seize control of the body far faster than I expected, allowing it to catch me off guard and get away.

“It's now fled into the sea, and in my current state, I'm unable to fully channel my Spirit Refinement Technique, so I can't detect where it is right now," Han Li explained with a grim expression.

Right at this moment, Weeping Soul flew onto the scene, and she had one finger pressed against her own glabella while pointing in a certain direction with her other hand as she yelled, "It's in that direction, and it's moving very quickly! Should we..."

"We have to go after it!" Han Li declared as he immediately set off in the direction that Weeping Soul was pointing in.

Chapter 1275: Ghost Gate

Under Weeping Soul's guidance, Han Li set off after the wicked corpse soul at full speed.

With his current mid-Great Encompassment Stage powers, he was able to cover a distance of several million kilometers in the blink of an eye.

Even though he was now able to lock onto the wicked corpse soul with his spiritual sense, the latter was somehow able to give itself a burst of acceleration whenever he got close, and as a result, it remained frustratingly out of reach.

Before long, the two of them had reached the edge of the Black Wind Sea, and up ahead was a boundless wall of black yin wind that stretched as far as the eyes could see in all directions.

It's the Soul Stirring Winds!

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he immediately channeled his Reversal True Axis ability to grant himself a significant speed boost.

However, in the same instant, the wicked corpse soul also abruptly accelerated as a burst of golden light flashed over its body, and it was able to rush headfirst into the Soul Stirring Winds ahead of Han Li.

"Good luck catching me now!" the wicked corpse soul cackled as he plunged into the Soul Stirring Winds.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly as he instantly spread his spiritual sense into the Soul Stirring Winds, but somehow, the wicked corpse soul had managed to completely vanish without a trace.

After a brief hesitation, he decided not to charge in blindly.

Even though letting the wicked corpse soul run free was going to undoubtedly create future headaches, he was still yet to consolidate his cultivation base, so rushing in blindly after it was not a wise decision.

Right at this moment, Weeping Soul's voice rang out in his mind.

"Master, let me out for a second."

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, and Weeping Soul appeared beside him.

Her eyes were glowing as she stared into the Soul Stirring Winds up ahead, Han Li was rather intrigued to see this.

"Have you discovered something, Weeping Soul?"

"I detected a very familiar aura in these winds, and on top of that..."

Weeping Soul made a hand seal as she spoke to summon the Yama Cauldron.

The cauldron immediately began to glow, and it looked as if it were itching to fly into the Soul Stirring Winds.

"Get Song Chunshan out here!" Han Li hurriedly said, and Weeping Soul faltered slightly upon hearing this, then immediately nodded in response before sweeping a sleeve through the air, upon which Sun Chongshan appeared beside her out of thin air.

As soon as Sun Chongshan was summoned, he immediately scoured his gaze over his surroundings, and a surprised look appeared on his face upon catching sight of the Soul Stirring Winds up ahead.

"Have you been here before, Fellow Daoist Sun?" Han Li asked.

"The environment here is very similar to that of the Heavenfall Immortal Region where I found this Yama Cauldron," Sun Chongshan replied in a truthful manner.

Han Li nodded in response, then turned a contemplative gaze back to the Soul Stirring Winds.

"Have you been here before as well, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"I once ventured into these yin winds a very long time ago, but I didn't dare to venture too deep. These yin winds are called Soul Stirring Winds, and not only do they contain immense glacial qi, there are also creatures that are similar to yin beasts lurking deep within them. It's said that these Soul Stirring Winds come straight from the depths of the underworld," Han Li replied.

"Perhaps that rumor is true!" Weeping Soul exclaimed in an excited manner.

"You seem to be very interested in these Soul Stirring Winds," Han Li remarked.

"I want to go inside and take a look. Can we?" Weeping Soul asked as she put on a pitiable expression.

"Seeing as this place has something to do with the Yama Cauldron, I also want to go in and take a look. However, before that, I need to rest and recuperate for some time, so you'll need to keep a lookout for me," Han Li said.

"Not a problem!" Weeping Soul replied as she immediately cast Sun Chongshan back into the Yama Cauldron.

From there, Han Li and Weeping Soul settled on a small and obscured island nearby, and Han Li created a temporary cave abode before entering the Flower Branch domain to commence a stint of seclusion.

He was in seclusion for close to twenty years, but thanks to the space of accelerated time, only less than a day had passed by in the outside world.

Once again, Han Li and Weeping Soul were standing before the Soul Stirring Winds, and Sun Chongshan was summoned a second time.

As soon as he caught sight of Han Li, his jaw immediately dropped to the ground.

Just a day ago, Han Li had been in terrible condition, yet in such a short span of time, he had managed to completely recover.

Could it be that he had taken some type of unfathomably powerful pill that was extremely effective even on Great Encompassment cultivators?

Despite all of the questions in his mind, he knew better than to articulate any of them, and he waited obediently for further instructions from Han Li and Weeping Soul.

"Let's go in. Hopefully, we can still catch him," Han Li said, then swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a golden light barrier to encompass the trio before the three of them flew collectively into the Soul Stirring Winds as a streak of golden light.

The Soul Stirring Winds were still as hostile as ever, but Han Li was countless times more powerful since he last ventured into them, so he was able to traverse through them with ease on this occasion, and it didn't take long for him to travel a considerable distance into the Soul Stirring Winds.

However, he was disappointed to discover that the wicked corpse soul remained elusive, and even Weeping Soul wasn't able to detect it at all.

Additionally, what also came as a surprise to Han Li was that they hadn't encountered any of the yin beasts residing in the Soul Stirring Winds thus far.

Right at this moment, the Yama Cauldron in Weeping Soul's hands began to tremble slightly before pointing downward, and Han Li's trio immediately embarked on a descent.

Last time, Han Li had been focused solely on flying through the Soul Stirring Winds, and he had never explored in the downward direction. As a result, only now did he discover that the sea down below had disappeared, with more gusts of yin wind taking its place.

As they continued to descend, the glacial qi in the surrounding area became more and more potent, to the point that even the golden light barrier released by Han Li wasn't able to keep it at bay.

Sun Chongshan had begun shivering uncontrollably, and he was just about to say something when a black trident that was aimed at his back suddenly shot out of the yin winds behind him.

A metallic clang rang out as the trident was repelled by the golden light barrier around the trio, and a flash of recognition appeared in Han Li's eyes at the sight of it.

He had encountered this thing during his previous crossing of the Soul Stirring Winds.

At his lowly cultivation base at the time, he had only been able to force the creature into retreat, and he wasn't expecting to encounter another one here.

However, this one was far more powerful than the previous one, and it was at least at the Golden Immortal Stage.

Han Li lashed out without any hesitation, releasing an arc of golden lightning out of his fingertip to strike the black trident.

The trident exploded, all of the Soul Stirring Winds within a radius of several hundred feet were also torn apart by the eruption of golden lightning, revealing a black, humanoid creature.

The creature was roughly the same stature as an adult human, but its entire body was covered in black scales, and there was a tail dragging along behind it.

At this moment, there was a stunned look on the creature's face, and it let loose a sharp screech before turning to flee.

Right as Han Li was about to put an end to its life, it was swept up by a streak of black light that had flown out of Weeping Soul's hand.

The creature was powerless to resist, and it was sucked into Weeping Soul's mouth in a flash before being devoured whole.

A blissful look appeared on Weeping Soul's face, while a layer of black light began flashing over her body, and it lingered for a long time before finally fading away.

"It's been a long time since I had such a delicious meal," Weeping Soul remarked as she smacked her lips in a joyful manner.

"That was nothing more than a Golden Immortal Stage ghostly creature, was there something unique about it?" Han Li asked.

"There wasn't much yin soul power in its body, but it was of a very high caliber, and this type of yin soul power is very compatible with my body," Weeping Soul explained with an excited expression.

"Is that right?" Han Li mused in a contemplative manner.

Right at this moment, Sun Chongshan suddenly interjected, "Senior Han, Senior Weeping Soul, I can't endure the glacial qi here for much longer..."

His face had turned blue from the cold, and his shivering had grown even worse.

Han Li took a glance at him, then turned to Weeping Soul, and the latter cast him back into the Yama Cauldron as she scoffed, "How useless!"

"Let's keep going down," Han Li said with a hint of intrigue in his eyes.

Thus, the two of them continued on their descent, and half a day flew by in the blink of an eye, but there was still no bottom in sight.

The glacial qi here was so potent that even Han Li was beginning to feel some slight discomfort, but Weeping Soul seemed very much at home here.

After descending for a while longer, the surrounding yin winds suddenly began to recede, and it seemed that they had finally reached the bottom.

The two of them immediately accelerated in their descent upon seeing this, but right at this moment, an enormous, crimson vortex suddenly appeared before them without any warning.

A burst of tremendous suction force surged out of the vortex, catching the two of them completely off guard, and they were sucked in before they had a chance to react.

In the next instant, they found themselves in a crimson space, within which was a giant, crimson lake that was rippling faintly.

The water in the lake very much resembled blood, but it gave off no bloody odor, only a biting chill.

Beyond the crimson lake was a huge, crimson city that was very majestic in appearance, and directly above its gaze were emblazoned the words "Ghost Gate".

Han Li and Weeping Soul exchanged an astonished glance upon seeing this.

Chapter 1276: Yang Cleansing

"This place is so cold and foreboding... Could it be that we really have entered the underworld?" Han Li murmured to himself as he swept his spiritual sense over the crimson city up ahead.

The city was quite large, but it was completely devoid of vitality. There weren't even any dogs or cats to be seen, let alone any living humans.

It was as if beyond this Ghost Gate really was a ghost city.

Weeping Soul was staring intently into the air beyond the Ghost Gate, and Han Li followed her gaze to discover that there was a large, black cloud hovering in the air above the city, and it was very eye-catching in this crimson space.

The black cloud was slowly moving like a living creature, making it appear as if there were something within it, but it also contained some type of invisible force that kept Han Li's spiritual sense at bay.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li peered into the cloud with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Right at this moment, the black cloud shuddered as a burst of tremendous might erupted out of it, causing the nearby space to tremble violently.

Han Li felt a sharp pain in his eyes, and blood began to flow down from their corners as he hurriedly averted his gaze.

"Master!" Weeping Soul exclaimed in an alarmed voice.

"I'm fine," Han Li reassured as he closed his eyes. "There's something very strange about that cloud, so don't try to look into it."

Shortly thereafter, he reopened his eyes, and they had already returned to normal.

"This is not a very inviting place. I think we should leave right away," Weeping Soul suggested as she took a wary glance at the crimson city and the black cloud above it.

"This crimson space is very stable, so we can't just leave as we please. Besides, we're already here, so we may as well go down there and take a look," Han Li said, then began to fly toward the crimson city.

Weeping Soul was still a little hesitant, but she raised no objections as she followed after him in silence.

The two of them descended in front of the city gates, which were wide open, and beyond it was an extremely wide road that could accommodate around a dozen horses riding abreast of one another. The road was lined with tall buildings, the doors of which were also opened up wide.

However, the city really was completely deserted.

Weeping Soul's brows furrowed slightly as she reflexively sidled up a little closer to Han Li.

"Let's go in. I'm curious about exactly what this place is," Han Li said as he stepped into the city, and as soon as he did so, he involuntarily shivered, which was slightly alarming, but aside from that, he didn't notice anything else amiss.

He turned to take a glance at Weeping Soul, but it seemed like she hadn't felt anything at all.

With their speed, it didn't take long for them to explore the entire city, and they discovered that the the facilities in the city were quite complete, and that it was really no different from the average city in the True Immortal Realm. There was furniture and cutlery in the residential buildings, and some of the tables were even laden with food, but there was simply not a single person to be seen.

"Could it be that all of the city's residents were recently abducted?" Han Li speculated.

At this moment, the two of them were standing in a residential home, and there was some tea on the table next to them.

Meanwhile, Weeping Soul was looking around in a contemplative manner, and all of a sudden, she stepped forward and picked up one of the cups of the tea from the table.

The tea was also red in color, and all of a sudden, a look of realization appeared on her face.

"Did you discover something?" Han Li asked.

"I've figured it out, Master! Come with me!" Weeping Soul yelled, then dragged Han Li out of the city to the crimson lake.

"Why have you taken me here?" Han Li asked.

"Just trust me, Master," Weeping Soul replied, then jumped into the lake so that her body was submerged within it, leaving only her head exposed.

Her brows furrowed slightly for a moment, but then quickly unfurrowed again.

As opposed to jumping into the lake with her, Han Li began to inspect the water inside with his spiritual sense.

The water in the lake was giving off a faint, glacial aura, but there didn't seem to be anything else special about it.

Right at this moment, an elated look appeared on Weeping Soul's face as she exclaimed, "I knew it! Master, come in!"

Han Li hesitated momentarily, then jumped into the lake as well.

As soon as he did so, his facial features instantly became slightly twisted in agony.

Submerged within the lake, he felt as if his entire body were being raked by red-hot daggers. He couldn't help but tremble from the pain, and his vision had also become rather hazy, as if a layer of mist had appeared over his eyes.

If the pain were purely physical, then Han Li wouldn't have been fazed at all, but it was acting directly upon his soul, and even with his tremendous mental fortitude, he was finding it rather difficult to endure.

It was as his entire body had been enveloped by a burst of invisible force that was extracting something out of his body and soul.

"This lake is filled with Three Lifetimes Water that can cleanse the yang energy from one's body. Just endure the pain for now, Master," Weeping Soul hurriedly said.

Han Li gritted his teeth and persevered upon hearing this.

Only after a full fifteen minutes did the pain begin to subside, and it quickly faded away entirely. At this moment, Han Li didn't feel any discomfort. In fact, bathing in the lake had become an indescribably blissful experience.

Han Li gently exhaled, and his vision had already returned to normal.

Right as he was about to get out of the lake, Weeping Soul suddenly grabbed onto his arm to stop him, then said in a quiet voice, "Hold on a second, Master. Take a look at the city first."

Han Li cast his gaze toward the crimson city upon hearing this, and his eyes widened in shock as he discovered that rows of guards clad in suits of crimson armor had suddenly appeared in front of the city.

These guards possessed humanoid bodies, but each of them had a single horn on their heads, and they had large ears and long tongues that drooped out of their mouths, much like a dog would stick out their tongue while panting on a hot day, lending a comical element to their fearsome appearance.

The previously completely deserted city had also become extremely lively and bustling, and countless residents seemed to have materialized out of thin air.

Not only that, but more guards clad in crimson armor had appeared above the crimson lake as well, and they were holding chains in their hands, the other ends of which were attached to struggling figures that were being cast into the lake.

As soon as these people plunged into the lake, they immediately began to scream in heartwrenching agony, and plumes of smoke came rising up from their bodies, as if they were being corroded by the lake.

However, it didn't take long for the smoke to dissipate, at which point their bodies would've already turned semi-transparent. From there, they were dragged back to the city gates by the armorclad guards, then arranged into a line to be examined before being allowed into the crimson city.

The guards paid no heed to Han Li and Weeping Soul at all, and it was as if they were unable to see the two of them.

"These armorclad guards are soul harvesting envoys of the underworld. They travel to the True Immortal Realm to harvest the souls of the deceased, and those souls are cleansed of their yang energy before being taken to the underworld," Weeping Soul said.

"That does appear to be what's happening, but how do you know all of this?" Han Li asked in a curious manner.

"As soon as I entered the Three Lifetimes Lakes, these memories suddenly surfaced in mind," Weeping Soul replied.

"How could you possibly have these dormant memories?" Han Li asked in a perplexed manner.

"I'm not sure. Maybe us Xing Beasts have some type of natural connection to the underworld," Weeping Soul speculated.

"Perhaps so," Han Li replied with a nod.

He then turned his gaze back to the crimson city as he mused, "I had always thought that the underworld didn't truly exist, but it appears I was wrong. By the way, why can't these soul harvesting envoys see us?"

"Only the deceased and those who've had all of their yang energy cleansed in the Three Lifetimes Lake can be seen by soul harvesting envoys. Even though we fall into the latter category, I used a special secret techniques to conceal our auras, so these soul harvesting envoys still can't see us. However, this secret technique only just sprang into my mind, so I don't know how well it's going to work," Weeping Soul explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod, then rose up from the lake before flying toward the entrance of the city.

"Master, I just told you that I don't know how well the secret technique is going to work!" Weeping Soul hurriedly said as she followed after him.

Thankfully, they were able to remain undetected, and the soul harvesting envoys stationed at the city gates didn't have any sensory tools at their disposal, so Han Li and Weeping Soul were able to slip into the city unnoticed.

"That was way too reckless of you, Master," Weeping Soul complained.

"I have faith in your secret technique. Besides, if it wasn't going to work, then there would've been no point for us to continue hiding in the lake anyway," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"I suppose," Weeping Soul acquiesced with a nod. "What are you planning to do from here?"

"Let's follow them and see what they do with these souls," Han Li replied as he pointed a finger at the soul harvesting envoys in the city.

At this moment, the soul harvesting envoys were escorting the souls of the deceased toward a certain direction in the city, and there were many people on the streets stopping to look and point at the procession as it passed through.

Han Li and Weeping Soul trailed the soul harvesting envoys from afar, and they quickly arrived at the entrance of a tall building.

The souls were herded into the building by the soul harvesting envoy like sheep, and Han Li and Weeping Soul exchanged a glance with one another before entering the building as well.

Chapter 1277: Exposed

After entering the building, they were greeted by the sight of a long and extremely dark passageway that led downward, extending into a circular, underground space that had been segmented into a series of independent sections.

At the center of the underground space was a crimson pond, while a series of cages in which all types of souls were being held were present in the segmented areas.

The soul harvesting envoys were currently in the process of locking up the souls that they were escorting into the vacant cages, and there were also some other envoys standing in the crimson pond, but it was unclear what they were doing.

"Looks like this is where the souls are held. There's not much to see here, let's go elsewhere to try and find a way to leave this place," Weeping Soul urged.

"What's going on with the Yama Cauldron at the moment? Is it still pointing in a certain direction?" Han Li asked.

Weeping Soul hesitated momentarily, then replied, "The cauldron is trying to guide us toward that dark cloud."

For some reason, Han Li had expected this to be the case, so he wasn't overly surprised to hear this.

After some contemplation, he suggested, "Let's split up to search for ways to leave this crimson space. There's no need to go looking outside the city. I already examined the area with my spiritual sense earlier, and I couldn't find any ways out."

"The effects of this secret technique should be able to last a day and a night, so we should be safe during this time," Weeping Soul replied, and the two of them exited the building before parting ways.

Close to a day later, the two of them reconvened at the entrance of the same building, and both of them had grim looks on their faces.

Neither of them had managed to find a way out.

"How about we try and break through this crimson space by force?" Weeping Soul suggested.

Han Li was just about to respond when his expression suddenly changed slightly, and he led Weeping Soul into the building before casting his gaze toward the souls locked up in the cages.

"What is it, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"I suddenly thought of a way out," Han Li replied with a smile.

"What is it?" Weeping Soul asked in an eager manner.

"It doesn't look like this is the underworld, so I'm assuming that these souls won't be held captive here forever. Instead, they'll most likely be transported from here to the true underworld. If we can find out how these souls are transported, then there's a chance that we'll be able to leave this place through the same means," Han Li replied.

"That could definitely work!" Weeping Soul said in an elated manner.

"The only problem is that we don't know when they're going to carry out the next step of the process," Han Li mused.

"That's not a problem, we can just ask someone," Weeping Soul said as she led Han Li to a secluded area in the building.

A soul harvesting envoy had just thrown a soul into a cage, and it was just about to leave, but as it was passing by a corner, a hand suddenly shot out like lightning, grabbing onto them before dragging them into the darkness.

There was another soul harvesting envoy behind them, and from their perspective, it looked as if their companion had just vanished into a dark corner all of a sudden.

As the soul harvesting envoy was passing by the corner, they looked inside to discover that it was a dead end, and there was nothing inside with the exception of a dusty, red cauldron sitting on the ground.

The soul harvesting envoy murmured something to itself, then continued onward, quickly putting the matter out of its mind entirely.

Inside the internal space of the Yama Cauldron, the soul harvesting envoy was bound and immobilized by streaks of black light that resembled chains, and there was an enraged look on its face as it let loose a string of strange sounds that were extremely unpleasant to the ears, resembling the wailing of a ghost late at night, or the sound of countless crawling centipedes.

"Can you understand what it's saying?" Han Li asked as he turned to Weeping Soul, and the latter shook her head with a wry smile.

"How about you?" Han Li asked as he turned to Sun Chongshan.

"I know some underworld text, but not much, and I don't understand it in its spoken form," Sun Chongshan replied with a shake of his head.

"It looks like we have no choice but to search its soul. That way, we'll at least be able to see its memories, even if we can't understand what's being said in them," Weeping Soul said, then pressed a palm down onto the soul harvesting envoy's head.

A pained look appeared on the soul harvesting envoy's face, and it began to shriek in agony, while its body rapidly withered away.

Shortly thereafter, Weeping Soul released its lifeless body, then turned to Han Li as she said in an elated manner, "It's just as you guessed, Master! The underworld sends ghostly generals to the city every once in a while to escort souls to the underworld, and it looks like they should be scheduled to arrive in the next few days!"

"Good," Han Li replied with a sigh of relief. "How will those ghostly generals be coming here?"

"They'll be coming from that dark cloud, and a spatial passageway will open up for them to transport the souls in the city through," Weeping Soul replied, and Han Li nodded in response.

A thought then occurred to him, and he asked, "By the way, is the absence of this soul harvesting envoy not going to be noticed?"

"There's no need to worry about that," Weeping Soul assured. "There are many soul harvesting envoys, and they're only considered to be fringe members of the underworld, so no one will bother to count them."

With that, Han Li's concerns were put to rest, and over the next few days, they remained in the Yama Cauldron's internal space to learn the language of the underworld from Sun Chongshan.

The soul harvesting envoy that Weeping Soul had searched the soul of had also had a basic grasp of underworld text, and that, in conjunction with Sun Chongshan's lessons, allowed Han Li and Weeping Soul to quickly develop an elementary understanding of the language.

Seven days later, the dark cloud above the city suddenly began to ripple violently, and a burst of tremendous energy fluctuations came surging out of it, causing the entire crimson space to tremble and quiver.

Countless black runes flew out of the dark cloud to form a black vortex, at the center of which was a black passageway that looked as if it were leading into the darkest chasm under the heavens.

A black-robed figure that was holding a black club came flying out of the passageway, and compared with the soul harvesting envoys, their facial features were much closer to those of a regular human.

The soul harvesting envoys in the city had already gathered in front of the dark cloud with the souls that they had detained.

"Time to go!" the black-robed ghostly general declared, and the soul harvesting envoys immediately cast the detained souls forward.

A burst of suction force surged out of the black passageway to suck in all of the souls, and it didn't take very long as there weren't many souls being detained in the city.

The ghostly general entered the passageway after the souls, and the passageway flashed momentarily before quickly closing, but right before it closed fully, two indistinct shadows flew into it in a flash.

Han Li and Weeping Soul felt a burst of tremendous force acting upon them, wrenching them in all directions, but they gritted their teeth and endured in silence.

Only after quite some time did the surrounding forces dissipate, and Han Li and Weeping Soul found themselves in a black space, standing before an enormous abyss.

The abyss was tens of thousands of feet wide and extended as far as the eyes could see in either direction.

Plumes of black mist were constantly rising up from within the abyss, giving off an extremely potent glacial aura and a peculiar type of ghostly qi.

In contrast with normal ghostly qi, the ghostly qi here was remarkably pure, and it was also much heavier and more viscous, almost resembling a liquid.

"Is this the underworld?" Weeping Soul murmured to herself as she summoned the Yama Cauldron, and it immediately swiveled around to point toward the bottom of the abyss.

Weeping Soul's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this, yet right as she was about to spring into action, Han Li grabbed onto her arm to stop her.

"Hold on a second."

"What's wrong, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

Instead of looking at her, Han Li was scrutinizing the abyss up ahead with a cold sneer.

"Did you think you'd be able to fool me? Show yourself!"

An alarmed look appeared on Weeping Soul's face upon hearing this, and even after being alerted by Han Li's words, she was still unable to detect anything.

"Oh? You must possess tremendous spiritual sense if you were able to detect my presence."

A voice that was as unpleasant as the sound of metal grating on metal rang out from up ahead, and it was speaking the language of the True Immortal Realm.

A cloud of black mist then appeared up ahead, and it rapidly swelled to transform into a black cloud that was tens of thousand of feet in size in the blink of an eye.

A chorus of ghastly shrieks rang out from within the dark cloud, striking Han Li and Weeping Soul's souls like a barrage of intrusive arrows.

Han Li and Weeping Soul hurriedly channeled their spiritual sense to protect their souls from the cacophony of ghastly shrieks ringing out up ahead, following which Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a flurry of golden lightning that scattered much of the black cloud.

As a result, it was revealed that there was an army of around two thousand to three thousand ghostly entities lurking within the cloud, and all of them were identical in appearance and aura to the one that Weeping Soul had devoured.

They were also wielding the same black tridents, and all of them were arranged in an orderly and well-organized formation.

Han Li paid no heed to these ghostly creatures as he focused a wary gaze on the figure at the forefront of the ghostly army.

It was a middle-aged man who appeared no different from the average human, but his eyes were glowing with a harrowing, crimson light, and he was observing Han Li and Weeping Soul with a sinister grin on his face.

Draped over his body was a black robe that appeared almost illusory in nature, and all types of fearsome, ghostly shadows were constantly poking their bodies out from beneath his robe. Strapped to his back was a black spear that was around ten feet in length, and it was giving off an aura so formidable that even Han Li was forced to regard it as a serious threat.

"Who are you, and why are you hiding here? Were you planning to ambush us?" Han Li asked.

Chapter 1278: Suspicious Retreat

"I should be the one to ask you that! Don't think that I can't tell that you're cultivators of the True Immortal Realm just because you've cleansed your yang energy using Three Lifetimes Water! Go back to where you came from, you're not welcome in the underworld!" the black-robed man replied in a cold voice.

"So this is the underworld," Han Li mused, pretending that this was news to him. "The two of us only came to this place by chance. Could it be that you're an underworld envoy that's been stationed here?"

"Looks like you insist on overstaying your welcome. In that case, you can both die here! Get into formation!" the black-robed man ordered as he pulled his spear off his back before pointing it forward.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the ghostly army behind him instantly arranged themselves into a pair of triangular formations. The auras of the ghostly beings within the formations were instantly connected together, and it was as if they had become a single unit.

The two triangular formations then transformed into a pair of enormous arrow projections that hurtled directly toward Han Li and Weeping Soul at an astonishing speed, reaching them in the blink of an eye while releasing tremendous wind pressure and ghostly qi fluctuations.

Weeping Soul was caught off guard and sent flying back by the fierce wind, while Han Li was able to remain completely unmoved.

His aura began to swell rapidly, and a golden lightning sword appeared in his grasp before releasing several hundred streaks of golden sword qi, forming a swirling pillar of golden light around him to keep the pair of giant arrow projections at bay.

A resounding boom rang out as the two ghostly formations were stopped cold in their tracks before being repelled back, but they managed to hold themselves intact.

As for Han Li, he was knocked back a couple of steps by the force of the impact before managing to steady himself.

Right at this moment, a black spear projection appeared behind him without any warning, piering toward his heart from behind like a spitting viper.

Another golden lightning sword instantly appeared behind Han Li, as if it had been waiting there all along, parrying the oncoming spear projections with another loud boom.

Two halos of unmatched power, one black and one golden, appeared in the underground space before erupting violently, and the black spear projection was sent flying back, while the black-robed man was revealed with a stunned look on his face.

Han Li was also sent flying once again, but as he flew through the air, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of golden light, which transformed into Jin Tong.

"Jin Tong, go and deal with those two formations with Weeping Soul!" Han Li instructed, then pounced at the black-robed man.

The two golden lightning swords also hurtled directly toward the black-robed man, reaching him in the blink of an eye before swelling to over a hundred times their original size and crossing over one another like a pair of huge scissors.

In response, the black-robed man thrust his black spear forward like lightning, jamming it right into the point where the two golden swords intersected with unerring accuracy.

A loud clang rang out as the pair of golden swords were stopped cold in their tracks, allowing the black-robed man the time to spring back in retreat.

Han Li immediately made a hand seal upon seeing this, and two thick bolts of golden lightning erupted out of the pair of giant swords. Due to the close proximity, the black-robed man was unable to react in time, and the bolts of lightning struck him before exploding into a ball of blinding golden light that encompassed the entire surrounding area within a radius of several dozen kilometers.

All of the yin wind and glacial qi in this space were completely eradicated, and all that remained were crackling and flashing arcs of golden lightning.

However, right at this moment, a ball of black light appeared out of thin air, and it quickly devoured all of the surrounding arcs of golden lightning.

The black-robed man then reappeared, and he was completely unscathed. There was a burst of black light flashing in his right sleeve, giving off a burst of devouring force, and that was precisely the source of the ball of black light.

In the blink of an eye, all of the golden lightning had been sucked up his sleeve.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

Not only did Cardinal Heavenly Lightning possess extremely fearsome destructive power, its innate attributes also gave it a natural advantage over all types of ghostly power, yet the black-robed man had just easily collected it like a confiscated toy.

Despite this rather disheartening turn of events, Han Li continued to persevere, and several hundred golden sword projections erupted out the pair of golden swords at his behest before converging toward the black-robed man, who raised his spear and conjured up countless black spear projections in retaliation.

A string of metallic clangs rang out in rapid succession, while Weeping Soul and Jin Tong were also engaged in fierce battles against the two ghostly formations.

Jin Tong had taken on her Gold Devouring Immortal form, but she wasn't taking much initiative, doing the bare minimum to keep the formation occupied, rather than adopting a more aggressive approach.

Meanwhile, Weeping Soul was flying back and forth through the other formation, and she was looking very excited as she made a grabbing motion with one hand.

The sky abruptly darkened as a giant, black claw the size of a small mountain appeared. It was none other than the Infernal Ghost Claw, and it came grabbing down upon the ghostly formation at her behest.

A burst of tremendous power came crashing down, instantly freezing the entire space within a radius of several dozen kilometers to immobilize the opposing ghostly formation.

However, in the next instant, a burst of black light erupted out of the formation to tear the surrounding, restrictive forces apart, and a High Zenith Stage ghostly being in the formation issued a loud command, then waved a large, black flag that they were holding through the air, releasing streaks of black light that infused themselves into the black light around the formation.

The triangular formation instantly elongated to form a devilish, black dragon to oppose the descending black claw and keep it at bay.

Weeping Soul wasn't fazed at all by this. In fact, a faint smile had appeared on her face, and she opened her mouth to release a streak of black light, which raced toward the tail end of the black dragon at an astonishing speed.

As a result of the formation's elongation, the layer of protective black light around it had thinned out significantly, and the streak of black light was able to quickly tear through it before sweeping up several of the ghostly beings inside the formation.

The High Zenith Stage ghostly being let loose a furious roar while urgently sweeping their black flag through the air upon seeing this, and the devilish dragon formation instantly circled around to send bursts of translucent light that resembled streaks of sword qi hurtling toward the black light.

However, by then, the ghostly entities that had been swept up by the streak of black light had already been pulled out of the formation before being promptly devoured by Weeping Soul, and a blissful look appeared on her face, while the black light emanating from her body became ever so slightly denser.

The black-robed man's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and Han Li immediately took advantage of his moment of distraction to fly directly toward him through the oncoming storm of spear projections.

At the same time, he made a rapid string of hand seals to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis, which released countless waves of golden ripples that swept toward the black-robed man.

However, the black-robed man had been able to instantly react as soon as Han Li had sprung into action, and he was backtracking through the air far faster than Han Li.

As a result, a rapidly widening gap appeared between them, so the golden ripples released by the Mantra Treasured Axis were unable to reach him.

In the blink of an eye, the black-robed man fled into the black abyss while letting loose a long shriek, and the two armies of ghostly beings that were locked in battle against Jin Tong and Weeping Soul immediately began to retreat as well.

"Master, help me capture some of them!" Weeping Soul yelled in an urgent manner as she hurriedly set off in hot pursuit.

Right as the two ghostly formations were flying past Han Li, he made a hand seal to expand the golden ripples released by his Mantra Treasured Axis, encompassing close to a hundred ghostly beings within them.

Now that his Mantra Treasured Axis had fused with the Heavenly Wheel Sundial and taken on a substantial form, it had become far more powerful than before, and all of the ghostly beings caught within its golden ripples were instantly completely immobilized.

The other ghostly creatures made no effort to free their trapped comrades, and they raced back to the black-robed man's side in the blink of an eye.

The man took a long glance at Han Li and Weeping Soul, then vanished into the abyss, followed closely by the pair of ghostly formations.

Jin Tong flew over to Han Li's side, then reverted back to her human form and asked, "What happened? Why did they suddenly retreat?"

"I don't know," Han Li replied with slightly furrowed brows.

During his brief clash against the black-robed man, he had discovered that the latter was definitely no less powerful than him, so if he were the guardian of this place, then he definitely shouldn't have retreated so quickly.

Could it be that there were some other factors at play?

"Master, you can withdraw your axis now," Weeping Soul urged while salivating profusely.

Han Li withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis with an amused smile, and the ghostly beings trapped within instantly fled in all directions in a blind panic, only to be immobilized once again as a black spirit domain fell upon them.

The spirit domain rapidly shrank down at Weeping Soul's behest, and all of the ghostly entities inside shrank down along with it before being devoured by the spirit domain.

In the end, the black spirit domain transformed into a fist-sized ball of black light before flying into her mouth.

The black light emanating from his body instantly began to flash erratically, and it remained this way for quite some time before finally settling down again, at which point, Weeping Soul's aura was much closer to the pinnacle of the early-Great Encompassment Stage than before.

"I don't know why that man suddenly decided to retreat, but I suppose this is a good thing. Let's go down and see exactly what is in this abyss," Han Li said as he flew down into the abyss, followed closely by Weeping Soul and Jin Tong.

As soon as the three of them entered the abyss, they immediately felt as if they had entered an enormous waterfall, and they were enveloped by a burst of power that sent them plunging down into the darkness.

The downward force was so vast that even with their Great Encompassment Stage powers, they were completely unable to resist, and they were sent plummeting downward in an uncontrolled fashion.

Chapter 1279: Exploring the Underworld

Han Li immediately channeled his cultivation arts and time law powers with all his might to try and stabilize himself, but the surrounding forces were simply far too immense, and he felt like a fallen leaf racing through a raging river, completely at the mercy of the turbulent waves.

Initially, the burst of power acted solely in a downward direction, but it quickly began wrenching his body from side to side, making him feel as if the entire world were spinning around him.

In the end, he stopped resisting altogether, only making an effort to protect the vital regions of his body while releasing his spiritual sense to try and get a bearing on his surroundings and lock onto Jin Tong and Weeping Soul.

Thankfully, he was still able to sense Jin Tong and Weeping Soul, but it seemed as if the distance between him and the two of them was fluctuating wildly.

After what seemed like an eternity, Han Li crashed down onto what felt like the ground, immediately following which Jin Tong and Weeping Soul fell onto him with a pair of dull thuds.

The impact from Weeping Soul wasn't too bad, but Jin Tong's body was as hard as a metal statue, and it almost knocked the wind out of his lungs.

"Are you alright, Master?" Weeping Soul asked as she hurriedly scrambled to her feet.

An apologetic look had also appeared in Jin Tong's eyes as she stood up and said, "I didn't mean to do that, Uncle."

"It's fine. Thank heavens I'm relatively sturdy," Han Li said with a wave of his hand, then rose to his feet to inspect his surroundings. "What is this place?"

At this moment, the three of them were standing on a barren desert, and the sky above was pitch-black. Visibility was limited to only less than ten kilometers, and anything beyond that was completely enshrouded in darkness.

Gusts of yin wind were howling through the surrounding area, and they carried glacial qi that was several times more potent than that of the Soul Stirring Winds.

Han Li and Jin Tong's brows furrowed slightly as they channeled their law powers to ward off the glacial qi, while Weeping Soul felt very much at home here, joyfully basking in the immense ghostly qi in the surrounding environment.

"Looks like this should be the underworld. We've finally arrived," Weeping Soul said in a confident manner as she rubbed her own belly.

"So this really is the underworld," Han Li mused with a contemplative nod.

He wasn't of the opinion that Weeping Soul had been to the underworld before, but for some reason, he trusted her judgment on this matter.

"The commotion caused by our landing has most likely already attracted some attention, so it's probably a good idea to get away from this place for now," Jin Tong cautioned, and neither Han Li nor Weeping Soul raised any objections to this.

None of the directions appeared distinguishable from the others, so the three of them quickly chose a direction to depart in.

Mere minutes following their departure, around a dozen black shadows flew onto the scene from afar. It was a group of half-human, half-beast ghostly creatures, and they were different in appearance from both the soul harvesting envoys and the ghostly soldiers under the black-robed man's command.

The group of ghostly creatures descended to the spot where Han Li's trio had been standing not long ago, and they began sniffing vigorously at the air with excited looks on their faces.

After that, the majority of them rose up into the air to set off in pursuit of Han Li's trio, leaving only one of them behind, and it let loose a sharp screech to the heavens.

Moments later, a vast black cloud appeared on the distant horizon before quickly drifting onto the scene.

Within the black cloud was a horde of countless ghostly beings, all of which also set off after Han Li's trio.

......

At this moment, Han Li's trio was flying through the air, and they were proceeding rather slowly, given that they were in a completely unfamiliar environment.

Han Li was scouring his surroundings with his spiritual sense and his Infernal Devilish Eyes as he flew along, but the excessive abundance of glacial qi in the air was significantly hampering his spiritual sensory range.

In contrast, his Infernal Devilish Eyes were much more effective, but even then, visibility was limited to only around three hundred kilometers.

Three hundred kilometers sounded like quite a large distance, but it was a distance that cultivators of their caliber could cover in the blink of an eye, so this really wasn't particularly helpful.

"Master, I can sense a river over five hundred kilometers ahead of us, and it seems to be rather strange," Weeping Soul suddenly said.

"Over five hundred kilometers away? Weeping Soul, what is your spiritual sensory range right now?" Han Li asked.

"There's too much ghostly qi here, so my spiritual sensory range is severely restricted, and it's been reduced to only around a thousand kilometers," Weeping Soul replied.

"What about you, Jin Tong?" Han Li asked.

"My spiritual sensory range is only around forty kilometers. You know me, this has never been my strong suit. Aren't you usually the one with the best spiritual sensory range out of all of us, Uncle?" Jin Tong replied.

"That's usually the case, but in this place, my spiritual sensory range is only around three hundred kilometers, so we'll be counting on you, Weeping Soul," Han Li said.

"Leave it to me, Master," Weeping Soul replied in a confident manner. "I'm not sure why, but this place feels familiar to me, like it was once my home..."

Before long, the three of them reached the river that Weeping Soul had mentioned earlier.

It was a river so vast that even Han Li wasn't able to see its borders, and turbulent black waves were rolling over its surface.

What was strange and rather unsettling about the river was that it was completely silent, despite the immense turbulence, and wisps of black mist were constantly rising up from its depths.

Several thousand feet above the river was a dense blanket of black clouds that appeared to have been formed by the mist rising up from the river, and arcs of black lightning could be seen flashing within them.

Han Li's trio drew to a halt by the river in a cautious manner, following which Han Li asked, "Weeping Soul, can you detect what's on the other side of this river?"

Weeping Soul closed her eyes momentarily to focus, then quickly reopened them and shook her head as she replied, "It's too far away."

"How could such a turbulent river be so silent? Let me try something!" Jin Tong said as she swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a streak of golden light that was over a thousand feet in length, and it plunged into the river in complete silence with not even the tiniest of splashes.

Han Li's trio were all slightly alarmed and concerned to see this.

The streak of golden light released by Jin Tong had appeared all that remarkable, but it had been imbued with immense power, enough to easily slice a mountain into two, yet the river had devoured it like it was nothing.

"There's tremendous ghostly qi in this river, and it has a very potent corrosive effect, so it would be best not to make contact with it," Weeping Soul said.

"What should we do, Uncle? Should we cross the river or try to go around it?" Jin Tong asked.

Han Li pondered the matter for a moment, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a golden bean, which transformed into a golden Dao Warrior that was around ten feet in size in the blink of an eye.

He then cast an arc of golden lightning into the Dao Warrior's body with a flick of his finger, and a series of golden lightning runes instantly appeared over its body.

At the same time, its aura had also become roughly twice as powerful as before, and it set off toward the other side of the black river.

However, it wasn't able to get very far before a thick bolt of black lightning came crashing down upon it from the dark clouds above at an incredible speed.

The Dao Warrior's entire body instantly turned black, and all of the spiritual power fluctuations emanating from it vanished without a trace, following which it plunged down into the river below like a black rock.

The river instantly began churning violently as countless piercing, ghostly shrieks rang out.

Countless terrifying serpentine creatures sprang out of the black river to inundate the Dao Warrior, and it was instantly torn to several pieces before being devoured amid a string of extremely grotesque and disturbing sounds.

The serpentine creatures then turned to Han Li's trio with menacing expressions, as if they were threatening to devour the three of them as well, but ultimately, they quickly disappeared back into the depths, and the black river reverted back to its silent state.

"Looks like crossing this river isn't going to be easy," Jin Tong remarked with a concerned expression.

"The black lightning in those clouds seems to be able to corrode immortal spiritual power, so they'll pose a potent threat even to the three of us. Let's try and follow the riverbank for now and see what happens. By the way, where's the Yama Cauldron pointing right now, Weeping Soul?" Han Li asked.

"Ah, I completely forgot about that!" Weeping Soul exclaimed as she summoned the Yama Cauldron, and it was glowing far brighter than normal.

It seemed to be resonating with the ghostly qi in this place, but it wasn't pointing in any direction.

"It looks like the cauldron was only attracted to the aura of the underworld, but not anyplace in particular," Weeping Soul sighed.

"Judging from its reaction, it most likely arose from this place or has some other deeper connection to this place. In any case, it seems like we've come to the right place," Han Li said.

Given the Yama Cauldron's connection to this place, there was a very good chance that the Yama Manor was also here.

"In that case, let's do some exploring," Weeping Soul replied with a nod, and after a brief discussion, the three of them decided to set off in the upstream direction of the black river.

Right at this moment, Weeping Soul's expression suddenly changed slightly as she exclaimed, "There's a large horde of ghostly beings currently closing in on us!"

As soon as her voice trailed off, a burst of dull rumbling rang out on the horizon, and a vast horde of ghostly beings came storming into view, while a chorus of ghastly howls could be heard amid the thunderous rumbling.

With the inhospitable black river behind them, Han Li's trio had no choice but to stand and fight, and he swept a sleeve through the air to summon thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, all of which were flashing with thick arcs of golden lightning.

Chapter 1280: Stone Statue on the Bridge

With another sweep of his sleeve, the other thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords emerged as well, and they hovered in the air in a row in front of Han Li's trio.

The flying swords began to circle through the air at his behest, forming a lightning sword barrier that was close to ten thousand feet tall.

At the same time, Jin Tong had adopted her Gold Devouring Immortal form, while Weeping Soul had summoned her Infernal Ghost Claw and Soul Scattering Ghost Flute.

Before long, the horde of ghosty creatures was already upon them, and they came in all types of forms and sizes, and some of them didn't even possess any visible forms.

Their auras also varied drastically, with the vast majority of them at the True Immortal Stage, but there were also some Golden Immortal and even High Zenith Stage ghostly beings among them.

Due to their vast numbers, their collective aura was extremely fearsome, and they unleashed a collective barrage of attacks to rain down upon the lightning sword barrier.

The sword barrier instantly began to tremble incessantly, but Han Li remained completely unfazed as he made a rapid string of hand seals, and countless streaks of lightning sword qi shot out of the sword barrier to pierce into the ghostly beings' ranks.

Given the immense destructive power of Cardinal Heavenly Lightning and its extra potency against ghostly entities, none of the ghostly creatures charging at the forefront stood a chance, and they were torn to shreds amid a cacophony of agonized, ghostly shrieks.

However, the rest of them continued to charge onward without pause.

These ghostly beings seemed to have been quite wary of the black river, so they only dared to attack Han Li's trio from the front and the sides, and as a result, they didn't have to watch their backs.

With that in mind, Han Li was tempted to retreat over the river in order to shake off the ghostly army, but he wasn't sure if doing so would only place them in even more peril than they were already in, so he decided to adopt the safe approach and continue to ward off the ghostly army with his sword barrier.

The lightning sword barrier formed by his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords was extremely formidable, but there was seemingly no end to the ghostly creatures, and the sword barrier's powers were gradually beginning to wane.

Weeping Soul and Jin Tong had offered their help on multiple occasions, only to be instructed to stand down and preserve their power by Han Li.

Right at this moment, a sharp screech rang out, one that even all of the ghastly howls weren't able to drown out.

All of the ghostly creatures instantly stopped cold in their tracks, then arranged themselves into four or five massive, sword-shaped formations.

These formations began to rapidly revolve like drill tips before hurtling directly into the golden sword barrier, and radiant black and golden light instantly erupted forth in unison like a fireworks display.

The golden sword barrier was shattered with a loud crack before reverting back into the thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which came spinning back through the air end over end, clearly having suffered some damage to their spiritual nature.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly as he swept a sleeve through the air to stow the thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords to be nurtured in his body, following which he made a grabbing motion with his other hand, and the other thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that were circling around him instantly shot forth toward the oncoming ghostly creatures as thirty-six streaks of dazzling golden light.

A string of loud explosions rang out as close to a hundred ghostly beings were erased from existence, but more ghostly creatures charged forward to take their place.

Jin Tong and Weeping Soul were unable to continue standing by passively anymore upon seeing this, and they immediately sprang into action.

Weeping Soul summoned her Infernal Ghost Claw, and bursts of scorching black flames emerged over its surface as it made a grab for the ghostly creatures charging in from the left.

All of the ghostly beings that came into contact with the Infernal Ghost Claw instantly exploded before being incinerated into ashes by the black flames, and at the same time, she also began blowing on her Soul Scattering Ghost Flute, releasing countless blades of sound to tear through the hordes of ghostly creatures.

At the same time, a burst of black light was surging out of her mouth, sweeping up the surrounding ghostly creatures before sucking them into her belly.

Compared with Han Li and Weeping Soul, Jin Tong's attacks were proving to be far less effective.

With a sweep of her front legs, dozens of streaks of translucent light were sent sweeping toward the ghostly creatures on the right, instantly cutting down large swathes of them.

However, aside from the few ghostly beings that possessed substantial bodies, all of the others were able to simply reform their wraith-like bodies and emerge completely unscathed.

Jin Tong's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and half of her huge body suddenly disintegrated into a golden cloud, while the other half transformed into a smaller Gold Devouring Immortal.

Within the golden cloud were countless Gold Devouring Beetles the size of grains of rice, and they swarmed the oncoming ghostly beings before clinging to their bodies and rapidly devouring them.

However, the rate at which they were devouring the opposing ghostly creatures wasn't able to keep up with the rate at which more ghostly beings continued to storm onto the scene, and Han Li immediately came to Jin Tong's aid upon seeing this.

With a sweep of his sleeve, hundreds of streaks of lightning sword qi were unleashed to eradicate close to half of all of the ghostly creatures on the left side, thereby alleviating much of the pressure on Jin Tong.

Even though they were able to fend off the army of ghostly creatures, they were certainly not doing so with ease, and it seemed as if there were no end to these ghostly entities.

"What do we do, Master? There are too many of them!" Weeping Soul yelled.

"If we stay here, we're eventually going to be overwhelmed, so let's take a risk and retreat along the river," Han Li decided, and thus, the three of them began to retreat in the upstream direction.

Moments later, Weeping Soul suddenly exclaimed in an ecstatic voice, "Look! There's a bridge up ahead!"

Han Li turned to discover that an ancient arch bridge really had appeared over the river.

The bridge was dark red in color, and it extended toward the other side of the river, but it eventually faded into darkness, making it impossible to tell how long it was.

Its surface was riddled with pits and potholes, and it appeared to have been a very old and weathered structure, but overall, it looked relatively intact.

Right at this moment, the ghostly beings suddenly stormed toward Han Li's trio with renewed intensity, and it was as if they had been granted some type of hysterical power.

Han Li raised a hand to release a streak of golden light, which fell upon the bridge before transforming into a golden Dao Warrior.

The Dao Warrior began to rush over the bridge, and no lightning fell from the dark clouds above, while the horrific creatures in the river also left it alone.

Han Li's eyes lit up upon seeing this, and he immediately yelled, "Retreat onto the bridge!"

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, unleashing several hundred thick bolts of golden lightning that instantly eradicated all of the ghostly creature within a radius of several hundred feet.

The three of them pounced on this opportunity to rush onto this bridge, and as soon as they did so, Weeping Soul's legs suddenly gave out from under her, causing her to stumble.

"Are you alright?" Han Li asked as he caught her before rushing over the bridge with her in tow.

The ghostly creatures were all gathered at one end of the bridge with furious expressions, but none of them dared to step onto the bridge.

"There seems to be some type of power on this bridge that subjugates ghostly entities. Thankfully, the debilitating effects aren't too severe on me," Weeping Soul replied as she steadied herself, and Han Li cautioned her to be careful before continuing onward.

Due to the arched shape of the bridge, the further they advanced, the closer the black clouds above became, making Han Li's trio feel rather uneasy. Thankfully, the black clouds displayed no reaction, and it seemed as if their auras had been concealed by the stone bridge.

All of a sudden, Weeping Soul stopped in her tracks, and Han Li and Jin Tong immediately drew to a halt alongside her.

"What's wrong?"

"There seems to be a statue on the bridge up ahead," Weeping Soul replied with a peculiar look on her face.

"A statue?"

Han Li was slightly taken aback to hear this.

The three of them continued onward, and they quickly arrived at the statue.

It was a gray, humanoid statue that was around thirty to forty feet tall, and it wasn't giving off even the slightest amount of aura.

The bridge wasn't very wide to begin with, and the statue blocked most of it.

"Why is there something like this here?" Weeping Soul mused with an intrigued expression.

Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly as he began carefully examining the statue with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Right at this moment, a dull voice rang out from within the statue, and it was speaking the language of the True Immortal Realm.

"Ah, what a rare sight it is to see cultivators of the True Immortal Realm here."

Han Li's trio hurriedly stepped back in an alarmed manner upon hearing this.

"Who are you?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"You most likely won't have heard of me, but just like the three of you, I also come from the True Immortal Realm. It's so good to see fellow cultivators of the True Immortal Realm here!" the statue replied with a hint of irrepressible elation in its voice.

"Are you actually from the True Immortal Realm?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I am from the Earth Emperor Sect in the Vast Earth Immortal Region, and I stumbled into the underworld by chance. What are the three of you doing in the underworld?" the statue asked.

A peculiar look suddenly flashed through Jin Tong's eyes upon hearing this, but she then immediately concealed it.

However, this momentary change in her expression failed to escape Han Li's notice.

"The three of us are vagrant cultivators, and just like you, we stumbled into the underworld by chance after being sucked into a spatial rift," Han Li replied.

"I see. It's terrible luck that you ended up on the Fierce Ghost Plains, but also quite impressive that you were able to make it out alive," the statue mused.

It seems like you know quite a bit about the underworld," Han Li remarked.

"You eventually learn some things once you've been in this place for as long as I have," the statue sighed.

"Why are you here on this bridge, and how did you become a stone statue?" Han Li asked.

"I was sealed here by an enemy secret technique," the statue sighed.

Han Li wasn't surprised to hear this. Through his Infernal Devilish Eyes, he had identified some type of very advanced seal present in the statue's body, but he wasn't able to see what was inside the seal.

Chapter 1281: The Words of a Ghost

"Seeing as all of us are cultivators of the True Immortal Realm, all of us must've been fated to meet here, so would it be possible for you to free me before we talk about anything else?" the statue asked in a hopeful manner.

"We can save you, but the three of us are completely new here and would like to ask you some questions about the underworld," Han Li said.

"I'm happy to answer your questions, but I haven't been to many places in the underworld, and this Black River Region is the only one that I'm relatively familiar with," the statue replied.

"The Black River Region? How many regions are there in the underworld?" Han Li asked.

"The underworld is extremely vast. As for exactly how vast, even the people of the underworld most likely won't be able to answer that question. I'm only aware of the existence of the Black River Region, the Infernal Region, and the Yama Region," the statue replied.

Han Li's interest was immediately piqued upon hearing mention of the Yama Region, but his expression remained unchanged as he said, "Tell us about the Black River Region first."

"The Black River Region is said to be a virtually boundless region, and its name comes from this black river beneath us. It's home to close to twenty noteworthy places, including the Fierce Ghost Planes, the Undead Forest, and the Blood Hell Canyon. There are many ghostly tribes residing here, but not many of them possess high levels of intelligence..."

Through the statue's words, Han Li was able to develop a very basic understanding of the underworld, and it was really quite similar a place to the True Immortal Realm, the Devil Realm, and the Gray Realm.

"Which powerful figures do you know of in these three regions, and what are their cultivation bases?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know too many details, all I've heard is that there are three very prominent figures in the underworld, namely Xue Li, Gui Wu, and the Infernal King. The Black River Region seems to be under the jurisdiction of Xue Li, but I'm not sure who rules over the other two regions. Like I said, there are very few ghostly beings here that possess high levels of intelligence, and that makes it quite difficult to gather information.

“I've heard that all three of them are extremely formidable, but I'm afraid I don't know their exact cultivation bases," the statue replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then changed the subject as he asked, "What do you know about the Yama Region?"

"I've never been to the Yama Region. All I've heard is that the ghostly beings there are very powerful, and that compared with the chaotic Black River Region, everything is much more orderly over there," the statue replied.

"Have you heard of a place called the Yama Manor in the Yama Region?" Han Li asked.

"I vaguely recall seeing such a place in the memories of a ghostly being that I searched the soul of. It's on the outskirts of the Yama Region, and it seems to be a very mysterious place," the statue replied after taking some time to think.

"Do you still recall where that place is?" Han Li immediately asked in a hopeful manner.

"I've been sealed here for so long that many of my memories have become rather hazy, but I can try and find it," the statue replied.

Han Li took a glance at Weeping Soul out of the corner of his eye as he asked through voice transmission, "Can you tell if he's speaking the truth?"

"I can't sense his soul through the seal, but he seems to be telling the truth, judging from the tone of his voice. Of course, there's a possibility that he could just be putting on a very convincing act," Weeping Soul replied.

All of a sudden, Jin Tong interjected, "Which branch of the Earth Emperor Sect are you from?"

Both Han Li and Weeping Soul turned to her with surprised expressions.

The statue faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "It seems like you're quite familiar with our Earth Emperor Sect, Fellow Daoist. I am a disciple of the Earth Emperor Sect's Bitter Bamboo Peak, and my master is Peak Master Yue Jing."

Jin Tong gave Han Li an almost imperceptible nod, and Han Li was rather curious about how she knew so much about the Vast Earth Immortal Region, but he didn't ask any questions as he turned his gaze back to the statue and said, "Alright, I can free you, but in exchange, you have to take us to the Yama Manor."

"Deal!" the statue immediately replied.

"Weeping Soul, help me break this seal," Han Li said as he turned to Weeping Soul, and the latter nodded in response.

"This is quite a complex seal, but over the years, I've managed to get a decent grasp on it. Should I tell you my findings to help you break the seal?" the statue asked.

"There's no need for that. This seal is indeed quite powerful, but it's become a lot weaker with the passage of time, and I've already identified some vulnerabilities that I can exploit," Han Li replied.

He then gave Weeping Soul some instructions on how to assist him, and the two of them began working on breaking the seal together.

Han Li injected his immortal spiritual power into a sealing rune on the right side of the statue's body, while Weeping Soul enveloped the entire statue in her law powers.

A green flame emerged over the rune with the influx of Han Li's immortal spiritual power, and it split up into two lines of fire that spread over the statue before converging back to the same spot.

As Weeping Soul injected her law powers into the statue's body, a layer of dark red light began to emerge, and the stone material began to peel away bit by bit to reveal what was sealed underneath.

Inside the statue was an extremely physically imposing man that was over thirty feet tall. His upper body was bared to reveal his bulging musculature, and his crimson skin was riddled with rings of strange runes that gave off an appearance of primitive power.

What was most bizarre about him was that there was no head attached to his neck, only a grisly wound, and there were two glowing, golden eyes where his nipples should've been on his chest.

"What the hell is this thing?" Jin Tong exclaimed, and Weeping Soul's brows had also become tightly furrowed with apprehension.

"It doesn't look like this guy is from the True Immortal Realm. We may have been fooled," Han Li said in a grim voice.

A burst of sinister cackling rang out from the headless man's body, and Han Li's trio immediately sprang back to distance themselves from him.

"Finally, I'm free! I didn't think you'd actually be able to do it!" the headless man cackled, and his current voice was completely different from the one that he had used earlier.

"Now that you've been freed, please hold up your end of the deal and take us to the Yama Manor," Han Li said with one hand clasped behind his back, ready to lash out at any moment.

"You actually belived me? Only a fool would believe the words of a ghost!" the headless man chortled as a giant, crimson ax that was roughly the same height as himself appeared in his grasp.

The headless man set his foot down onto the ground with an almighty stomp, and an incredibly fearsome aura instantly erupted out of his body, displaying his peak-Great Encompassment Stage cultivation base in its full glory.

"Who are you?" Han Li demanded as an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword appeared in his grasp.

"My name is Xue Li!" the headless man declared in a thunderous voice, then abruptly appeared behind Weeping Soul in the blink of an eye before swinging his ax down upon her.

"Look out!" Han Li yelled as he channeled his time law powers and rushed to Weeping Soul's aid, while Weeping Soul herself sprang forward to just barely evade the sharp edge of the giant ax.

The sound of tearing fabric rang out as the back of her robe was split apart, while blood splattered through the air.

At the same time, Han Li had already arrived behind Xue Li, and he was plunging his sword directly toward the latter's heart from behind.

As opposed to turning around, a strange snapping sound suddenly rang out from Xue Li's shoulders, and his arms twisted around to an impossible angle as he used his ax to parry Han Li's sword.

A flurry of golden lightning instantly erupted out of the sword at Han Li's behest, and Xue Li's entire body was instantly enshrouded in Cardinal Heavenly Lightning.

The eyes on Xue Li's chest were struck by the golden lightning, and he immediately closed them with an agonized howl.

Weeping Soul took advantage of the opportunity to flee to Jin Tong's side, and the latter could see a gruesome gash that ran down the entire length of her back, one that was deep enough to expose the vertebrae underneath.

Jin Tong was furious to see this, and she launched herself at Xue Li with golden light flashing over her body.

Right at this moment, Xue Li let loose a thunderous roar, and a crimson vortex appeared over his giant ax.

The golden lightning released by Han Li's sword was instantly sucked into the vortex, following which Xue Li swung his ax at Han Li's head with almighty power.

As opposed to fighting fire with fire, Han Li evaded the attack, but once again, Xue Li put his incredible speed on display, leaving a trail of afterimages in his wake as he raced after Han Li.

However, before he was able to reach Han Li, he was intercepted by Jin Tong, who had launched herself at him in a seething rage.

In response, Xue Li swung his ax at Jin Tong, who, instead of taking evasive measures as Han Li had, took on her true form and continued to hurtle directly toward Xue Li.

A loud clang rang out as the blade of Xue Li's ax was caught between Jin Tong's front legs, stopping it cold in its tracks.

A hint of surprise flashed through Xue Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he forced his ax down with all his might. As a result, Jin Tong was also forced downward, but her grip on his ax remained firm, and she refused to let go.

Chapter 1282: Reincarnation King

While Jin Tong and Xue Li were grappling with one another, a massive, golden lightning cloud had taken shape in the heavens above, and a majestic heavenly gate appeared within it.

"Get back, Jin Tong!" Han Li yelled, and Jin Tong immediately released Xue Li's ax, then reverted back to her human form as she shot back in retreat.

Immediately thereafter, an enormous, golden sword came crashing down from above amid a deafening thunderclap.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Xue Li's heart upon seeing this, yet right as he was about to take evasive measures, a burst of light suddenly descended upon him from above.

As soon as the burst of light swept over him, his vision suddenly blurred, and it was as if his soul had received an abrupt jolt.

Countless arcs of golden lightning sprang out of the giant sword, filling the entire space within a radius of several hundred feet.

Xue Li was only dazed for a moment before returning to his senses, but by then, it was already too late to evade the oncoming attack.

He took a resentful glance at Weeping Soul, who was the one that had placed him in this perilous position, then swung his ax diagonally upward.

His body instantly swelled to over a hundred times its original size, and the ax in his grasp ballooned in size to the same degree, and the crimson vortex on its surface became brighter and brighter as it rumbled toward the golden lightning sword.

An explosion of blinding light erupted high up in the sky amid a deafening boom as devastating shockwaves swept through the air in all directions.

More explosions continued to ring out one after another, completely decimating everything in the surrounding area. For some reason, as soon as Xue Li was freed from his seal, the army of ghostly beings that had been extremely apprehensive about setting foot on the stone bridge suddenly set aside their inhibitions and stormed onto the bridge in pursuit of Han Li's trio.

The ghostly creatures charging at the forefront were instantly decimated by the destructive shockwaves sweeping through the air with the exception of several of the most powerful ghostly beings among them, and a ghostly general that was leading the way immediately issued a loud order for everyone to stop.

Even Jin Tong was unable to stand firm against the powerful shockwaves, and she was doing her best to shield the wounded Weeping Soul as she stumbled back in retreat.

Only after a long while did the dust finally settle, and at this point, the lightning cloud and the heavenly gate in the sky had already faded away.

It was unclear what material the stone bridge was constructed from, but it remained completely unscathed even in the wake of such an intense battle. Xue Li was still standing on the bridge with the blade of his ax resting on the ground, but there was a horrific gash that ran down from his headless neck to his chest, splitting his entire chest cavity into two.

Han Li was even able to see his moving organs through the wound, but he remained completely still on the spot, and Han Li wasn't able to detect any aura from him using his spiritual sense.

Is he dead?

Han Li observed Xue Li for a moment longer with a skeptical expression, then rushed over to Jin Tong and Weeping Soul.

"Is he dead, Uncle?" Jin Tong hurriedly asked.

"I'm not sure," Han Li replied.

He then cast a concerned gaze toward Weeping Soul and asked, "Are you alright?"

"The injury isn't too severe, but there's a burst of strange law powers present in the wound, preventing it from healing," Weeping Soul replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he walked around her to examine her back, then placed a hand over her wound.

A delicate, green seedling emerged from the palm of his hand, and a root extended out of it before reaching into Weeping Soul's wound.

Weeping Soul gave a muffled groan, then gritted her teeth tightly to endure the pain in silence.

A miniature, palm-sized, golden tree slowly came growing out of the wound on her back, and it was none other than Han Li's Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree.

The roots of the tree served as sewing needles that stitched Weeping Soul's skin and flesh together bit by bit, and under the effects of Han Li's time law powers, the wound quickly healed, following which the golden tree slowly dissipated into nothingness.

"He seems to have mastered some type of reincarnation law powers that are able to constantly restore your flesh to its wounded state, thereby preventing it from healing, but I've forcibly broken the cycle with my time law powers," Han Li said.

"I see. Thank heavens you're able to counteract his powers, Master," Weeping Soul replied with a nod.

"This is a very strange place, and now that Xue Li has been freed, it seems like those ghostly creatures have regained the courage to come after us, so let's get out of here," Han Li said.

Jin Tong and Weeping Soul naturally raised no objections to this. In particular, Jin Tong was very eager to leave this place behind.

Right at this moment, a burst of law power fluctuations suddenly surged out of Xue Li's body, and a crimson vortex that was revolving in the anti-clockwise direction appeared over his chest, then gradually expanded to devour his entire body.

"What's going on?"

Both Weeping Soul and Jin Tong were rather alarmed to see this.

"Forget him, let's get out of here," Han Li urged, and the three of them immediately sped away toward the other end of the bridge.

Only after the three of them had vanished out of sight did the crimson vortex begin to revolve in the clockwise direction, and Xue Li's headless body stepped out from within it.

The injuries inflicted upon him by Han Li had already healed, and even his aura had fully recovered.

"They made a smart decision to run. Otherwise, I would've made them regret ever crossing me! If it isn't for my old injuries, it wouldn't have taken me anywhere this long for me to unleash such a minor reincarnation technique!" Xue Li harrumphed coldly.

Right at his moment, a loud commotion rang out nearby, and the army of ghostly beings stormed onto the scene.

However, before they could reach Xue Li, the ghostly general at the forefront of the army raised a fist up high and loudly ordered everyone to stop.

The ghostly general then cast an incredulous gaze toward Xue Li as he called out in an uncertain voice, "Master Xue Li..."

Xue Li instantly swung around to face the ghostly general, and a surprised look appeared in his eyes as he asked, "Yin Luo, is that you?"

The ghostly general immediately rushed over to Xue Li and fell to his knees, then kowtowed to the ground and declared in a respectful voice, "Yin Luo pays his respects to Master Xue Li."

All of the ghostly beings behind the ghostly general also fell to their knees and kowtowed to the ground as their bodies trembled in awe and veneration.

Xue Li stared at Yin Luo in an absentminded manner, seemingly lost in his own thoughts.

Some time later, he heaved a long sigh as he said, "You may stand."

Yin Luo remained on his knees, but raised his head to reveal an elated expression as he said, "Congratulations on regaining your freedom, Master Xue Li!"

"Those cultivators of the True Immortal Realm were the ones who freed me. Speaking of which, it seems like you're pursuing them, is that right?" Xue Li asked.

"That's right. I don't know how they managed to get here, and we were unable to intercept them," Yin Luo replied.

"I was going to kill them after they freed me, but they had some tricks up their sleeves, and I still have residual internal injuries from long ago, so they were able to get away," Xue Li said.

"Master Xue Li, your injuries..." Yin Luo began, only for Xue Li to raise a hand to stop him.

"Tell me about what's happened since I was sealed away," Xue Li ordered.

"After you disappeared, our forces devolved into internal conflict without your leadership. After that, I received word that you were being imprisoned in Gui Wu's Sinful Mirror City. Yin Qiu, Fan Li, and I attacked the city to try and free you, but we suffered a crushing defeat. After Fan Li perished, most of his forces defected to the Infernal King, while the rest surrendered to Gui Wu," Yin Luo replied.

"What about Yin Qiu?" Xue Li asked.

"Yin Qiu and I have never gotten along with each other, and we parted ways after Fan Li died. I've been trying to hold onto our existing territory to the best of my abilities, while he gradually faded into obscurity. I heard... I heard that he went on to pledge his subordination to the Reincarnation King," Yin Luo replied.

"The Reincarnation King?" Xue Li asked in a puzzled manner.

"He's the mysterious figure who joined forces with the Infernal King and Gui Wu to seal you away," Yin Luo explained.

"How was his identity revealed?" Xue Li asked.

"After he sealed you away, he took over the majority of our territory and declared himself the Reincarnation King. His actions broke the agreement established between the trio, so the Infernal King led her forces to attack him, but were defeated.

“Her most trusted subordinate led what remained of her forces to our territory and revealed to us the truth behind how you were sealed away, but we've been unable to undo the seal on you for all these years," Yin Luo explained.

"The Infernal King is dead?" Xue Li asked as a hint of melancholy crept into his voice.

"Not only that, but Gui Wu is also dead, and both of them were killed by the Reincarnation king. Right now, almost the entirety of the three major regions are already under his control," Yin Luo continued.

A stunned look appeared in Xue Li's eyes upon hearing this.

Before Xue Li was sealed away, the three major regions had each been ruled over by one of him, the Infernal King, and Gui Wu. Xue Li was the most capable warrior of the three, the Infernal King had the most powerful forces, and Gui Wu was the most cunning and treacherous. On top of that, he had a vast collection of life-saving tricks up his sleeve, so it came as quite a shock to Xue Li that even he had perished by the Reincarnation King's hands.

"It sounds like all of us were played by that Reincarnation King. We have only ourselves to blame for constantly fighting over that reincarnation-attribute cultivation method. Otherwise, the Reincarnation King would've never been able to drive such a potent wedge between us," Xue Li sighed in a forlorn manner.

Chapter 1283: Another One

"Master Xue Li, now that you've returned, all we need to do is gather our scattered forces and recuperate for a hundred thousand years or so, and we'll definitely have an opportunity to exact our vengeance on the Reincarnation King!" Yin Luo declared.

"A hundred thousand years is too long. I want revenge now, and an opportunity has already presented itself," Xue Li said in a cold voice.

"What are you referring to, Master Xue Li?" Yin Luo asked.

"Didn't you feel like there was someone familiar among the three people that you were pursuing just now?" Xue Li asked.

Yin Luo's brows furrowed slightly in contemplation upon hearing this, and moments later, his eyes abruptly lit up as he exclaimed, "Now that you mentioned it, that black-robed woman's abilities were rather similar to those of the Infernal King!"

"That's right! I am already 90% sure that she is the reincarnation of the Infernal King. If we want to defeat the Reincarnation King and seize back the underworld, then we have to awaken her memories and work with her," Xue Li said.

"In that case, should we stop pursuing them then?" Yin Luo asked.

"There's no need to continue pursuing them, but you must also make sure to not lose track of them," Xue Li replied.

"I understand, Master Xue Li. I'll send people to track them right away," Yin Luo said as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute.

"I'll leave it to you then. I have to go into seclusion for some time to rest and recover from my lingering injuries," Xue Li said, then sprang up into the air before flying away into the distance.

......

There was a winding river that was filled with flowing, murky, red water in front of a shadowy mountain range.

The river originated from a valley thousands of kilometers away, and it flowed all the way to this point, where the terrain was much more level, before pooling into a large river bank.

Han Li's trio descended upon the river bank, and Jin Tong turned back to take a glance behind them before remarking, "It looks like those guys haven't come chasing after us."

Han Li also took a backward glance, then turned an inquisitive gaze to Weeping Soul.

"I can't sense them anymore, either. It seems like we've managed to open up some distance on them," Weeping Soul confirmed.

Han Li nodded in response, then began to inspect his surroundings, and it was clear from his reaction that he didn't like what he saw.

The white river bank beneath his feet was riddled with bones from both humans and demon beasts, and they were piled on top of one another to form mounds that varied drastically in size.

Han Li crouched down and scattered the layers of bones on the ground with his hands, then grabbed a fistful of the white sand underneath to discover that it was all bone powder.

"Where did all these bones come from?" Weeping Soul asked.

"They most likely came from upstream, and they've been piling up here for so long that the bones on the bottom have already completely decayed and disintegrated into powder," Han Li said.

Right at this moment, an unnatural gust of wind came sweeping toward them from the upstream direction, raising a small cloud of bone powder from the ground, and tiny specks of fire began to appear within the cloud.

Immediately thereafter, a green flame rose up over the red river, then came drifting toward Han Li's trio, and within the green flame was an indistinct human face that was wearing an unsettling smile.

"What the hell is that supposed to be?" Jin Tong asked.

Weeping Soul's nose wrinkled slightly, and it seemed as if she were preparing to suck the green flame into her belly, but Han Li raised a hand to stop her as he said, "Hold on a second, it seems to have something to say."

As soon as his voice trailed off, a faint voice really did ring out in an intermittent fashion from within the green flame.

"Go to... the river... valley..."

The voice sounded extremely elderly and frail, like the final words of an old man on his deathbed, and it only uttered those five words before fading into silence.

Immediately thereafter, the green flame also descended into the river and vanished out of sight.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze toward the shadowy mountain range in the upstream direction.

The dark clouds there were so low that they had almost devoured the summits of the tallest mountains in the mountain range, giving the entire place an even more eerie and forbidding appearance.

"Do we go, Uncle?" Jin Tong asked.

"That ghostly flame seems to have come from a soul fragment, but what could it possibly want from us?" Han Li mused.

"Could it be some type of trap?" Weeping Soul asked.

"I don't think so. We've only just entered the underworld, and even running into that ghostly army was only a chance encounter, so it's impossible that anyone would've set a trap here for us in advance," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"Who cares? Let's just go and take a look," Jin Tong said in an unfazed manner.

"We don't know where to go anyway, so we may as well go and take a look at what's in the river valley. Perhaps we'll be able to find some leads on the Yama Manor," Weeping Soul chimed in in agreement.

"Alright, let's go and take a look, but make sure to be on your guard," Han Li cautioned, and with that, the three of them set off for the river valley upstream.

It didn't take long for them to reach the entrance of the river valley, on either side of which was a sheer cliff face with two natural walkways on their surface.

Han Li's trio made their way up from the path on the left onto the walkway on the left cliff face.

Standing on the edge of the walkway, they could hear the deafening sound of churning water nearby.

The entrance of the valley was tapered like a funnel, and as a result, the water of the red river that flowed to this point instantly became compressed and far more turbulent.

Han Li's trio observed the choppy water for a moment, then continued to make their way along the walkway.

Upon entering the valley, they discovered that it was shaped like a gourd. The entrance was very narrow and tapered, but the area beyond it gradually grew wider, and the water became calmer and calmer as a result.

Han Li's trio stopped in their tracks upon reaching the central point of the valley.

The river channel here had already expanded to several thousand feet wide, and at its center was a large island of sand.

The island was completely with some specks of golden interspersed throughout, giving off faint glimmers of a golden sheen.

At the exact center of the island stood a withered, black tee that was around thirty to forty feet tall, and it looked as if it had been scorched by fire. It had been completely carbonized, and there were even what appeared to have been some carbon crystals on its surface.

What was most strange of all was that there was a charred, black body hanging from the highest branch of the tree. The body appeared to have belonged to a human, and the branch was pierced through its chest, while a square, black box with side lengths of around a foot was being held in its arms.

"There are residual soul fluctuations on that body, but they're very faint. He seems to be the one that was communicating with us earlier," Weeping Soul said.

Han Li released his spiritual sense to scour the entire area, and only after ensuring that nothing was amiss did he drift down onto the island, followed closely by Weeping Soul and Jin Tong.

As soon as Han Li landed on the ground, a faint rustling sand rang out, and the ground beneath his feet was quite loose and loamy.

Weeping Soul crouched down to pick up a handful of sand, and after a brief examination, a surprised look appeared on her face.

"Is there something wrong with this bone powder?" Han Li asked.

"The bone powder isn't anything special, what's remarkable is the golden sand interspersed throughout," Weeping Soul replied.

"What's so special about it?" Han Li asked.

Right at this moment, a gloomy voice rang out from the body on the tree.

"It's Soul Scattering Sand, which, as the name suggests, is able to scatter souls, and it's the most sought after material for ghostly cultivators cultivating the laws of souls."

Han Li's trio looked up in unison upon hearing this, right as a plume of white smoke emerged to envelop the entire body.

The cloud of smoke took on the form of a thin, elderly daoist priest with a benevolent appearance, and around him was a blanket of mystical clouds, while the area behind him was illuminated by five-colored light.

All that he was missing was a pet crane to complete the image of an unfathomable daoist master.

A mysterious smile appeared on the elderly daoist priest's face as he extended a daoist salute while chanting a daoist prayer.

HanLI's trio exchanged a few glances with one another, then turned back to look at the elderly daoist priest as if they were looking at an idiot.

An awkward silence ensued, one that was only broken as the elderly daoist priest cleared his throat and said, "I am Grand Elder Tian Qianzi of the Zenith Daoist Sect in the Celestial Origin Immortal Region of the True Immortal Realm. Over a million years ago, I was banished here by my enemies. It appears that fate has brought us together on this day. If you can free me from this place, then I will be sure to compensate you handsomely."

He snuck a glance at Weeping Soul as he spoke, indicating that he cared a great deal about her reaction.

"That sounds a little familiar, Uncle," Jin Tong exclaimed as she put on an expression of mock surprise.

"He's following almost the exact same script as Xue Li from before," Weeping Soul chuckled.

"Is this a script that all of you people from the underworld follow when you're trying to trick someone? Where's the creativity?" Jin Tong sneered in a derisive fashion.

The elderly daoist priest's expression changed drastically upon hearing this, and he hurriedly asked, "You've already met Xue Li?"

"We have, and we were tricked by him earlier. It seems like you're very familiar with him," Han Li replied with a hint of mockery in his eyes.

"Not at all. In fact, we're sworn enemies," the elderly daoist priest hurriedly replied with a shake of his head.

"Oh? Aren't you supposed to be from the True Immortal Realm? How are you sworn enemies with someone from the underworld? Would you care to tell me how you became enemies when you're in two different realms?" Han Li sneered.

The elderly daoist priest knew that his ruse had been exposed, and he sighed in a defeated manner, "I should've known better than to try and trick you cunning bastards of the True Immortal Realm."

Chapter 1284: The Three Kings

The daoist priest began to undergo a transformation as he spoke, and by the end, all that was left was a dark green, ape-like ghostly creature with a wizened body.

The creature had a large head with a protruding forehead and a pair of sunken eyes, as well as a rather flat nose and mouth that also protruded outward slightly. Its fur was no different from that of a normal monkey, and it's skin was riddled with old scars.

The ghostly creature was hanging its head in a defeated manner, having just had its ruse exposed by Han Li.

"Who are you, and how are you related to Xue Li?" Han Li asked.

"I am King Gui Wu, and I once ruled over one of the three major regions of the underworld. I fell prey to a ploy meant to turn me against King Xue Li, and I sealed him on the Bridge of Forgetfulness. After that, a wedge was driven between me and the Infernal King as well, and in the end, the only one to benefit was the one who had turned the three of us against one another," the ghostly creature sighed in a forlorn manner.

Its gaze then flickered to Weeping Soul again as if it were gauging her reaction.

"You're King Gui Wu?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"You can just call me Gui Wu, Fellow Daoist. Right now, I have no forces under my command, nor do I possess any power, so I'm hardly a king," Gui Wu replied with a wry smile.

"I have no interest in hearing about your past. Right now, I only want to know two things from you. Firstly, why did you lead us here, and secondly, do you know where the Yama Manor is?" Han Li asked.

"I led you here because I knew that you could free me," Gui Wu replied.

"Why should we help you? We were careless and offered our help to Xue Li earlier, and he immediately turned on us as soon as we broke his seal!" Han Li harrumphed coldly.

"That's because Xue Li is a brainless idiot! He doesn't even have a head, so of course he has no brain! I'm not the same as him. I knew you could help me because of your ties with the Infernal King, and right now, I'm nothing more than a soul fragment that poses no threat to you, so what could you possibly have to fear?" Gui Wu exclaimed.

"What does this Infernal King have to do with us?" Jin Tong asked in a perplexed manner.

"Looks like the Infernal King suffered the worst fate of the three of us. Xue Li was sealed, and I was almost killed, but we were both able to survive. In contrast, it appears that the Infernal King met her demise and entered the cycle of reincarnation," Gui Wu mused as he turned his gaze back to Weeping Soul once again.

A puzzled look appeared in Weeping Soul's eyes upon hearing this, but Han Li immediately realized what Gui Wu was implying.

"You're saying that she's the reincarnation of the Infernal King?" Han Li asked.

"There's no mistaking it. Her powers and aura are completely unique. On top of that, if she wasn't the Infernal King, then why would she have been drawn to the Soul Scattering Sand on this island as soon as she set foot here? This Soul Scattering Sand was left behind by her to begin with!" Gui Wu replied.

"I'm the Infernal King?" Weeping Soul asked in an incredulous manner.

"If you don't believe me, then try and use your soul power to summon this golden sand, and its reaction will tell you everything," Gui Wu said.

Weeping Soul closed her eyes in a skeptical manner, then extended her hands forward as a layer of soul power fluctuations surged out of her body.

The entire island instantly began to rustle violently, and particles of golden sand interspersed throughout the bone powder came rising up of their own accord, drawn to the surface by a burst of invisible force. They converged to form a giant, golden ribbon that was several hundred feet in length high up in the sky, and only then did Weeping Soul reopen her eyes as she looked up at the golden ribbon above with an incredulous expression.

The golden ribbon descended from the heavens, then began to circle around her in an affectionate manner.

"You see? I wasn't lying to you!" Gui Wu said as an elated look appeared on his face.

"Weeping Soul, use the golden sand to envelop the roots of that tree," Han Li instructed in a cold voice, and Weeping Soul immediately did as she was told.

"Hey, what are you doing? How could you be so ungrateful!" Gui Wu wailed.

"Drop the act already! You only told Weeping Soul to gather the golden sand to remove a layer of the restrictions placed upon you. If I'm not mistaken, there are three seals placed upon you here in total, one of which is the golden sand, the second of which is this tree, and the final one is that box. Your soul is currently sealed in that box, isn't that right?" Han Li harrumphed coldly.

Gui Wu's expression instantly stiffened slightly upon hearing this, but he then immediately composed himself as he said, "You have a sharp eye, kid, I'll give you that. You are correct in that this seal has three components, and my soul is indeed in this Soul Locking Box. However, I was speaking the truth when I told you that all that remains of me right now is a soul fragment that poses no threat to you, and I harbor no enmity toward you, either."

"How were you able to tell that she's the Infernal King?" Han Li asked.

"Perhaps I've become more sensitive to such matters now that I've been reduced to nothing more than a soul fragment. In any case, she really is the reincarnation of the Infernal King. Many years ago, she destroyed my physical body and sealed me here with the help of the one who turned her against me, only for her to suffer an even worse fate than mine. How ironic," Gui Wu sneered.

Weeping Soul had no recollection of these events at all, so she naturally remained completely unmoved.

"I'm asking you to release me not just so that I can seek vengeance for myself. In addition, I truly do not want to see the underworld descend into a state of chaos," Gui Wu sighed.

"What do you mean by that?" Weeping Soul asked.

"Do you still remember the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate?" Gui Wu asked.

Weeping Soul shook her head in response.

"The Six Paths Reincarnation Plate is one of the most powerful treasures of the underworld, one that is able to influence the six paths of reincarnation. The one who turned the three of us against one another did so precisely so that he could obtain this treasure," Gui Wu explained.

A hint of intrigue appeared in Weeping Soul's eyes upon hearing this.

"After picking off the three of us one after another, that man declared himself the Reincarnation King and seized control over the three regions. However, not only has he not been fulfilling any of his duties as the ruler of the three regions, he has also been using the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate to interfere with the cycle of reincarnation as he pleases.

“His actions completely go against the natural order and the Heavenly Dao, and if things continue in this fashion, not only will the entire underworld be plunged into chaos, the other realms will eventually also be affected," Gui Wu continued.

"How do you know so much about what's been happening in the underworld when you've been trapped here for so long?" Han Li asked.

A wry smile appeared on Gui Wu's face as he replied, "I'm sure you've already guessed the answer to that question. All of the bones that you see here are remains of different beings that I lured here for sustenance. Otherwise, how could I have possibly been able to preserve this soul fragment for so long under such powerful restrictions?"

"From the looks of it, there must've been countless beings that fell prey to your tricks and lost their lives here," Han Li remarked.

"I've done everything in my power to survive, and at this point, I'm only just barely clinging onto life. Thankfully, you've come here with the Infernal King. With her here, not only can I be saved, the entire underworld can also be saved," Gui Wu said as he cast a hopeful gaze toward Weeping Soul.

"I have no recollection of this past life that you speak of, nor do I have any interest in regaining those memories," Weeping Soul said as her brows furrowed slightly.

Her first memories were of the times that she had spent with Han Li in the Spirit Realm, and even if she really had been the Infernal King in her previous life, that hardly mattered to her now.

"After being put through the cycle of reincarnation, you've lost all of your memories from your past life, so it's only natural for you to display such a reaction. However, if you manage to recover those memories, then I'm sure you'll feel far more inclined to help the underworld," Gui Wu said.

"Is it possible to recover memories from a past life?" Han Li asked.

"The memories of one's past life can be gleaned through the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate, which is situated on the bank of the Yellow Springs. Once you've awakened those memories, you'll be able to attain your cultivation experiences from your past life, and that will be sure to significantly enhance your law powers.

“After that, we can go to Xue Li to forge an alliance, and with our combined powers, we'll surely be able to defeat the Reincarnation King and recover the three regions!" Gui Wu said as he his eyes began to glow with excitement.

A hesitant look appeared on Weeping Soul's face, and it seemed as if she were being swayed.

"The Infernal King has returned to the underworld, the seal on Xue Li has been broken, and you and I have been reunited. Don't you feel like all of this is too much to just be a coincidence? The powers of fate are trying to bring the three of us back together!" Gui Wu urged in an earnest and heartfelt manner.

Weeping Soul cast a hesitant gaze toward Han Li upon hearing this.

"I have no interest in the power struggles of the underworld, but I am rather intrigued by this Six Paths Reincarnation Plate, so I wouldn't mind going to the Yellow Springs to take a look at it. However, before that, we have to find the Yama Manor first," Han Li said.

"That can be easily arranged," Gui Wu interjected.

"You know where the Yama Manor is?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I do, and it's not far away from here. At the very most, it should only take you a month to get there," Gui Wu replied.

Han Li was quite excited to hear this, but his expression remained unchanged, and he made it appear as if he were still weighing up his options.

"I can take you to the Yama Manor as long as you promise to take me to the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate and help me recover my powers afterward," Gui Wu offered.

Han Li finally nodded in agreement upon hearing this.

"Alright, seeing as we've reached an agreement, please help me undo this seal, Fellow Daoist," Gui Wu requested with a smile.

"This Soul Scattering Sand can be easily lifted by Weeping Soul, but the other two seals are very peculiar. Would you happen to know how they can be lifted, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu?" Han Li asked.

Chapter 1285: Traveling with a Ghost

"This tree is formed by Sun Wing Wood, and it looks like nothing more than a burnt tree, but in reality, it harbors a divine flame, and it burned itself into this state. If you have a powerful yin-attribute treasure in your possession, then you'll be able to use it to temporarily counteract the tree's powers and allow me to free myself," Gui Wu said.

"What about the Soul Locking Box?" Han Li asked.

"This box was designed to trap my soul, but during my time here, I've been able to modify it into a protective container instead. At this point, my soul has already become inexorably connected to it, and if it's opened, then this soul fragment of mine will be exposed to the elements, and it won't be long at all before it's completely eradicated," Gui Wu said with a wry smile.

"I see. In that case, I have a simple solution in mind. Weeping Soul, I'll get you to withdraw the Soul Scattering Sand first," Han Li instructed with a smile.

Weeping Soul made a beckoning motion upon hearing this, and the golden sand clinging to the roots of the withered tree instantly returned to her side before vanishing into her body.

"I've always been saying that I was going to find a way to replenish your power, and a suitable opportunity has finally arisen," Han Li said with a smile, and a puzzled look appeared on Gui Wu's face upon hearing this.

Immediately thereafter, a fiery, silver figure sprang out of Han Li's shoulder, then rubbed its hands together in a gleeful manner before jumping onto the black tree.

A fearful look instantly appeared on Gui Wu's face upon sensing the Essence Fire Raven's aura.

"There's no need to be afraid. This is a Flame of Essence, and this tree will serve as a perfect source of sustenance for it," Han Li reassured with a smile.

"Please tell that child to be careful not to harm my remains," Gui Wu implored, then returned to the Soul Locking Box.

Han Li gave the Essence Fire Raven some precautionary instructions, then allowed it to transform into a burst of scorching, silver flames to devour the black tree.

It took the Essence Fire Raven over an hour to devour the tree, allowing Han Li's trio some time to rest and recuperate.

Once the tree had been completely devoured, the Essence Fire Raven reverted back into its human form, then jumped into Han Li's shoulder in an unsteady manner as if it were in a state of inebriation before vanishing into his body.

In the absence of the black tree, all that remained on the island was the Soul Locking Box and Gui Wu's charred remains.

Han Li took a glance at Weeping Soul, and the latter immediately swept a sleeve through the air to release her Soul Scattering Sand again, using to envelop the Soul Locking Box and Gui Wu's remains.

"I have to take some necessary safety precautions. I hope you don't mind, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu," Han Li said with a smile.

"Not at all. I feel very fortunate to have such a cautious ally," Gui Wu replied from within the Soul Locking Box.

"We'll have to trouble you to serve as our guide, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu," Han Li said as he stowed the body and the Soul Locking Box away.

"Not a problem at all," Gui Wu replied.

......

Seven days later.

The dark clouds in the sky were hanging at a very low altitude, and there was a nauseating odor of decay permeating through the air.

Han Li's trio was traveling over an undulating, black mountain range, and their surroundings were littered with scattered remains. Whenever a gust of wind blew past, specks of eerie, green flames would rise up into the air.

Before long, they arrived at a sheer cliff, on the other side of which was a bottomless abyss that was filled with dense mist and a rank stench.

"Are we really going to do as he says, Uncle? Weeping Soul already told us that she wasn't able to detect any soul power fluctuations, so why are we making such a long trek over this mountain path? Can't we just fly directly over the abyss instead?" Jin Tong complained through voice transmission.

"The underworld is a completely unfamiliar place to us, so just because Weeping Soul wasn't able to detect anything doesn't mean that it would definitely be safe to fly over the abyss. Besides, there's no reason for Gui Wu to deceive us over something like this," Han Li replied.

"I agree. Gui Wu has served as a very competent guide for us these past few days, and thanks to him, we've been able to avoid a lot of unnecessary trouble," Weeping Soul chimed in in agreement.

She took a glance at the path ahead as she spoke, only to discover that the winding path beneath their feet was completely enshrouded in a dense mist, limiting visibility to only just over a thousand feet.

"Fellow Daoist Gui Wu, if this ghostly python residing on this cliff that you were referring to truly possesses Great Encompassment Stage power, then it could easily claim a territory of its own, so why does it insist on staying here?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know the answer to that question. That ghostly python has a very interesting past. Apparently, back when it was still alive, it already possessed the qualities required to evolve into a dragon, but it was killed by a bolt of tribulation lightning while shielding its child from a heavenly tribulation.

“After its death, it continued to cultivate in the underworld, and it was able to reach a cultivation base beyond its lifetime peak. It's been residing on this cliff for as long as anyone can remember, and it'll hunt down anything or anyone that dares to fly over the cliff.

“In contrast, those who travel along the mountain path won't be attacked by it as long as they don't go out of their way to provoke it," Gui Wu replied, and his voice was ringing out from within a cloth pouch that was trapped to Han Li's waist.

"The sky above this cliff is constantly enshrouded in dark clouds. Anyone that tries to fly over the cliff will inevitably stir up those clouds in a scene reminiscent of the churning of lightning clouds during a heavenly tribulation, and perhaps that's what provokes it into attacking," Han Li speculated.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a streak of light suddenly appeared within the clouds above, as if someone were flying through them.

The clouds were instantly stirred up as a result, and even though there were no thunderclaps, it did indeed look a little like a precursor of a lightning tribulation

"This is not good!" Gui Wu exclaimed in an urgent voice. "Get back from the edge of the cliff and stay close to the mountain face!"

Han Li's trio hurriedly did as they were told, and right at this moment, a burst of thunderous rumbling rang out from within the abyss as the entire mountain began to tremble violently.

Immediately thereafter, the dense mist within the abyss was riled up into a frenzy as a gargantuan figure came rising up from its depths.

All Han Li could see was a black "wall" rising up from the abyss before plunging into the dark clouds above, and the surface of the wall was riddled with countless rhomboid scales that were each over a hundred feet in size, raising large flurries of sparks as they scraped against the cliff face.

Only after it had completely sprung up into the clouds was Han Li able to make it out to be an enormous black python that was close to a hundred thousand feet in length. The python had a single horn on its head, and its eyes were like a pair of light towers, releasing two bright beams of green light.

"It's even more powerful than when I last saw it," Gui Wu remarked. "It's already reached the late-Great Encompassment Stage."

"What? How could a ghostly creature like this possibly reach such an incredible cultivation base?" Jin Tong exclaimed in an incredulous manner.

"There are almighty true spirits even in the primordial land, so why can't there be some unfathomable creatures in our underworld? This thing has most likely existed for even longer than I have. Let's hurry up and get out of here before it decides to attack us," Gui Wu urged.

Han Li's trio immediately picked up the pace upon hearing this.

After reaching the other side of the mountain, Han Li couldn't help but take a backward glance, and he discovered a mountainous, black head in the dark clouds above, observing them with its giant, green eyes.

However, for some reason, the ghostly python chose not to attack them and allowed them to pass through untouched.

"Be honest with me, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu, how is this ghostly python related to you? Why did it choose not to attack us?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know," Gui Wu replied. "It's always been residing in my Yama Region, but I've always left it alone, and we've never had any interaction."

"If we encounter any other creatures of this caliber from here onward, then let's make sure to go around them," Han Li said.

"I only pointed you down this path to avoid the nearby city, so this was the lesser of two evils," Gui Wu explained.

......

Over another month flew by in a flash.

On the western border of the Yama Region was a vast, ghostly swamp that stretched as far as the eyes could see in all directions, and permeating over the entire swamp was a suffocating miasma of death and decay.

On the eastern shore of the swamp was a peninsula that was rather out of place. It was less than a hundred thousand feet in area, but it extended tens of thousands of feet into the swamp.

At this moment, Han Li was standing at the end of the peninsula, looking up at the sky above.

Around ten thousand feet above the swamp was a blanket of vibrant, five-colored clouds that presented a marvelous sight to behold.

Jin Tong was standing behind him, and a suggestive look appeared on her face as she jibed, "What are you looking at, Uncle? Are you thinking of that ghostly bride?"

"Jin Tong!" Han Li scolded as he put on a stern expression.

Jin Tong was completely unfazed as she clasped her hands behind her back, putting on a mature display as she continued, "You really need to take a good look at yourself, Uncle. She may have been a ghost, but she was a real beauty, while you're really not that handsome, so you should count yourself lucky that she fell for you at first sight.

“However, not only did you not reciprocate her feelings, you even cut her down with your sword! That was far too cruel, wouldn't you agree, Weeping Soul?"

Weeping Soul offered no response, but an amused smile had appeared on her face.

The ghostly bride that Jin Tong had mentioned had been an extremely troublesome ghostly entity to deal with. Her illusory abilities were extraordinarily potent, and even with Han Li's Infernal Devilish Eyes and Weeping Soul's sensory abilities, they were still trapped for three entire days.

In the end, it was only thanks to Gui Wu that Han Li was able to track down the bridal sedan chair that the female ghostly had used to set up her illusory array. From there, he was able to force her to reveal herself before cutting her down, and Jin Tong was the only one who was able to look back on that ordeal with any degree of fondness.

Over the past month, Han Li had already had several similar encounters, and he couldn't help but marvel at how many strange things there were in the underworld.

Chapter 1286: Strange Array

"Fellow Daoist Gui Wu, this swamp appears to be quite calm at the moment, but I presume that it's not a safe place, either, am I right?" Han Li asked.

"There are no truly safe places in the underworld, but compared to other places, this swamp is relatively innocuous. A blanket of miasma constantly hangs over this swamp, and over the years, it has condensed into these five-colored poison clouds in the sky. However, you should be fine as long as you don't fly too high and directly enter the poison clouds," Gui Wu replied.

"I see. Where is the Yama Manor?" Han Li asked.

"It's not far away, we should be there soon," Gui Wu replied.

"You've already said that five or six times. Is the Yama Manor in this swamp or not?" Weeping Soul asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"This place looks far too barren for there to be any buildings here. Are you lying to us?" Jin Tong asked with a skeptical expression.

"I wouldn't dare to lie to you! The Yama Manor is on an island in the middle of the swamp, but it's surrounded by a strange array, and no one has ever been able to enter the manor. As for what's so strange about the array, you'll understand once you see it," Gui Wu hurriedly replied.

"In that case, please lead the way there, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu," Han Li said.

"There's a forest roughly a hundred and fifty thousand kilometers west of this peninsula. The trees in the forest are rather... special. Let's go there first," Gui Wu said.

Han Li's trio immediately set off in a westward direction, making sure to fly at an altitude of less than a thousand feet.

Shortly thereafter, a withered, black tree that was several thousand feet in height appeared on the distant horizon.

The tree had an extremely thick trunk, but it was entirely charred black and completely devoid of any vitality. Its branches were bare of leaves, resembling ghostly claws that extended in all directions.

Masses of vines were draped over the tree, with countless decaying bodies hanging from them, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

The landscape beyond the tree was enshrouded in a cloud of miasma, but it was still possible to make out more trees of a similar appearance stretching into the distance as far as the eyes could see.

Right as Han Li's trio was about to reach the tree, Gui Wu suddenly cautioned.

"These trees are Corpse Hanging Ghost Vines, and they're rather difficult to deal with, so make sure you don't get too close to them. From this point, we have to travel northward for around eight hundred and fifty thousand kilometers to find a floating rock that resembles a ghostly figure. From there, we travel four hundred thousand kilometers to the west, and we'll be able to reach the island that the Yama Manor is situated on."

Han Li's trio immediately set off northward upon hearing this.

......

Under Gui Wu's guidance, Han Li's trio was able to reach the island that was home to the Yama Manor after roughly three more days of travel.

At the moment, they were situated close to a thousand kilometers away from the island, which seemed to have been encompassed within some type of restriction that kept out all of the surrounding miasma, ensuring the air around the island remained clear and pure.

Han Li quickly noticed that the restriction contained immense time law powers.

The three of them were suspended in mid-air outside the restriction, and from there, they could see that time seemed to have been standing completely still on the island.

"Is this the Yama Manor?" Weeping Soul asked.

"That's right," Gui Wu confirmed.

"What's going on with everything on the island?" Jin Tong asked.

"This restriction is filled with time law powers, and as a result, everything inside is frozen in time. No one has ever been able to breach this restriction, let alone reach the island," Gui Wu explained.

After a brief examination, a perplexed look appeared on Han Li's face as he said, "This restriction does indeed contain immense time law powers, but it's not a powerful offensive array, nor is it an impregnable defensive array, so why has it never been breached before?"

"Rather than have me explain, you can pass through it yourself to find out," Gui Wu replied in a mysterious manner.

"I bet he's just trying to scare us! Wait for me, Uncle, I'll give it a try," Jin Tong scoffed in an unconvinced manner, then flew into the restriction before Han Li had a chance to stop her.

In the next instant, Jin Tong reappeared outside the restriction, then scoffed, "I bet he's just trying to scare us! Wait for me, Uncle, I'll give it a try."

Immediately thereafter, she returned to the same spot and repeated for a third time, "I bet he's just trying to scare us! Wait for me, Uncle, I'll give it a try!"

It was as if she had been caught in a time loop, one that she was completely oblivious to herself.

After reappearing outside the restriction once again, Han Li caught her by the arm before she could continue the futile cycle.

"What are you doing, Uncle? Let me give it a try!" Jin Tong complained as she struggled free from Han Li's grasp.

"You've already tried many times to no avail," Han Li said.

"What do you mean?" Jin Tong asked with a perplexed expression, then turned to Weeping Soul with an inquisitive expression.

"Master's not lying, you really have already tried many times," Weeping Soul confirmed.

"Why don't I remember?" Jin Tong asked with a dazed expression.

Han Li offered no response. Just as Gui Wu had said, it was much easier to explain the effects of the restriction by demonstration than through words.

"It seems that anyone who tries to enter the restriction will be affected by the time law powers within, taking them back to the instant before they entered the restriction. If there's no one to stop them, then they'll probably be doomed to repeat the cycle for all of eternity," Han Li said.

"I don't get it," Jin Tong said in a puzzled manner.

"Essentially, even if you had tried to enter the restriction a million times, you would've only been transported out of every single time, and you wouldn't have been able to realize that," Han Li explained.

"That is indeed the case, Fellow Daoist Han," Gui Wu chimed in in confirmation. "However, one thing I'll add is that this cycle won't repeat itself for all of eternity. Instead, once someone has entered the restriction a certain number of times, their physical body will be broken down by the time law powers within, and their immortal spiritual power will flow into the array as sustenance for it."

Both Weeping Soul and Jin Tong were quite alarmed to hear this, while Han Li didn't seem particularly surprised as he inspected the array with a contemplative gaze.

"Why didn't you say that earlier, you old bastard? Were you trying to get me killed?" Jin Tong yelled.

"You only entered the restriction a few times, so you'll be fine. One would have to enter the array at least tens of thousands of times before their body completely breaks down, and unless someone stops them, they won't be able to feel the deterioration in their own condition at all, which means that if you come here with no companions, then your fate is sealed from the moment that you decide to enter the restriction for the first time," Gui Wu said.

"Do you know how to unravel this restriction, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu?" Han Li asked.

"The answer to that question should be obvious, Fellow Daoist. If I could unravel the restriction, then everything in this Yama Manor would've already been mine," Gui Wu replied with a wry smile. "Having said that, what I can say is that seeing as this a time-attribute restriction, it should also require time law powers to unravel."

Han Li nodded in response with a thoughtful expression, then made a hand seal as he began chanting an incantation, and waves of time law power fluctuations surged out of his body as his five time law treasure manifestations appeared before circling around him.

He channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra as he swept a sleeve through the air, and the five time law treasure manifestations rose up into the air before descending upon the restriction from five different directions.

Five different types of time law power fluctuations began to sweep over the restriction, causing its surface to ripple like the surface of a disturbed lake.

Han Li raised a finger before gently prodding the restriction with it, and the entire light barrier disintegrated on its own with a faint pop.

All of the surrounding miasma in the air instantly began to converge toward the island, while the birds that had been suspended in mid-air for countless millennia were finally able to fly again, but their joy was short-lived as they were quickly suffocated by the converging miasma and fell out of the sky.

"That was way too fast!" Gui Wu exclaimed in an incredulous manner.

Han Li offered no explanation as he flew onto the island, followed closely by Jin Tong and Weeping Soul.

As soon as Han Li set foot on the island, he was immediately able to detect a faint burst of time law power fluctuations emanating from its center.

The island was filled with lush greenery, but there wasn't even a single, trodden path, so Han Li's trio was forced to advance through the overgrown grass and shrubs.

As they continued onward, the terrain on the island began to elevate, and the greenery wasn't as lush and dense as before. By the time they reached the summit of the island, the greenery had mostly receded, and Han Li was greeted by the sight of a dilapidated stone plaque.

Chapter 1287: The Pinnacle of the Great Dao

The plaque was covered almost entirely in dark green moss, and only a part of a character for "Manor" could be made out on its surface.

The plaque was also broken in a very uneven fashion, and there was a fist-sized hole in its center.

"Look over there, Uncle!" Jin Tong suddenly yelled, and Han Li turned to the direction that she was pointing in to discover the other half of the plaque.

After brushing away the soil and weeds on its surface, Han Li discovered that the characters for "Yama" were engraved onto its surface.

"Looks like this is where the Yama Manor is. I can't see any physical building here, so it must be in something like a secret area or an array," Weeping Soul analyzed.

"It's right here," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Where?" Jin Tong asked in a puzzled manner.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he made a grabbing motion to release a streak of golden light, which swept up the half of the plaque that was laying on the ground before lifting it up into the air and setting it down onto the half of the plaque.

The two halves of the plaque came together in a seamless manner, but there was still a piece missing.

"Why's there a hole in the middle?" Jin Tong asked.

"It looks like we're still missing a key," Gui Wu said.

"Would you happen to know what this key is, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu?" Han Li asked.

"The Yama Manor has existed for countless years, and I don't even know who constructed it, so I'm afraid I don't know what this key could be, either," Gui Wu replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this. Patriarch Miro had only instructed him to visit the Yama Manor, but had never mentioned its specific location or any key that was to be used to access it.

He approached the stone plaque to conduct a closer inspection, but wasn't able to detect any clear law power fluctuations emanating from it.

After some contemplation, he began paying closer attention to the hole in its center, and it suddenly occurred to him that the hole was of a rather familiar size and shape. His eyes immediately lit up at this discovery, and he flipped a hand over to produce a golden inkstone.

It was the very same inkstone that had been given to him by Wu Yang back in Nine Origins City.

As soon as the inkstone appeared, it immediately began to give off a golden glow along with waves of tremendous earth law powers.

A dense passage of runes instantly surfaced over the plaque, as if to resonate with the inkstone, and a burst of golden light appeared in the hole in its center to release bursts of suction force.

Han Li extended his hand forward, and the golden inkstone flew into the hole on its own. It was a perfect fit, and it quickly fused into one with the plaque.

Immediately thereafter, a golden vortex abruptly appeared over the surface of the plaque.

"That's it!" Jin Tong exclaimed in an ecstatic manner.

Was this all predestined by fate, or did you arrange all of this, Patriarch Miro? Han Li wondered to himself.

"What are you spacing out for, Uncle? Why aren't you going in?" Jin Tong asked with a puzzled expression.

Han Li shook his head to cast aside these disruptive thoughts, and right as he was about to go in, he turned to Jin Tong and Weeping Soul before instructing, "Now that the restriction on this island has been broken, it'll be accessible to outsiders, so we'll have to be on the lookout for potential intruders. Hence, I'll get you two to stay outside while I go in."

"You can count on us, Master," Weeping Soul immediately replied with a nod.

Jin Tong was very curious about what was inside the Yama Manor, but she still reluctantly obliged to Han Li's instructions.

"I'll leave Fellow Daoist Gui Wu in your care for now as well," Han Li said as he removed the pouch from his waist before handing it to Weeping Soul, and the latter gave an affirmative response, while Gui Wu remained silent.

Only after doing all of that did Han Li finally step into the golden vortex.

The entire world instantly began to spin around him, and by the time everything around him settled, he found himself on a lush, green plain.

The plain stretched as far as the eyes could see, and there were also some indistinct mountains that could be made out in the extremely far distance.

There was a date tree that was over a hundred feet tall standing several thousand feet away, and beneath the tree was a small thatch hut.

Despite its lackluster size, the thatch hut had clearly been very meticulously constructed, and even the thatch on the roof had been woven together in a very tidy fashion.

Right at this moment, a familiar voice rang out from within the thatch hut.

"What are you looking at? I've already been waiting for you for a very long time."

Immediately thereafter, a rotund monk in a red kasaya squeezed his way out of the hut's entrance.

He had a pair of extremely long earlobes that drooped all the way down onto his shoulders, and there was a benevolent smile on his face that squeezed his eyes into a pair of tiny slits. That, in conjunction with his enormous belly, gave him a very festive and joyful appearance.

"Master!" Han Li exclaimed in an ecstatic voice, only to quickly realize that this was nothing more than a soul fragment of Patriarch Miro's.

"You seem a little disappointed," Patriarch Miro jibed.

"I thought you were still alive, and I couldn't help but feel disappointed at the realization that this is not the case," Han Li sighed in a dejected manner.

In contrast, Patriarch Miro appeared as joyful as ever as he said, "Now that you're here, it was worth the long wait for me."

"I should also be happy that I get to see you again," Han Li said as a smile appeared on his face.

"I created this secret area with what remained of my power, and the restriction around the island has ensured that my power remains fully intact. However, now that the restriction has been undone, my power is going to begin dissipating very quickly, so we don't have any time to waste. Show me the fruits of your cultivation," Patriarch Miro urged.

Han Li nodded in response, then immediately channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra while simultaneously conjuring up his time spirit domain, which encompassed the entire area within a radius of close to ten kilometers around the thatch hut.

A slightly surprised look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and Patriarch Miro smiled as he explained, "That's the extent of the size of this space. The mountains and landscape that you see in the distance are nothing more than illusions."

Han Li was even more surprised to hear this as he wasn't able to identify this at all.

However, he quickly cast those thoughts aside and began focusing on channeling his cultivation arts.

A full moon, a mountain range, a winding river, and a lush forest emerged in his spirit domain in quick succession, and Patriarch Miro nodded with a pleased expression as he praised, "Not bad at all. Once all five of your time law treasures are manifested into substantial forms, your Five Elemental Illusory World will become even more powerful."

"I was going to work on that, but some unforeseen mishaps arose, and I had a lot of trouble with my wicked corpse soul, so everything was delayed," Han Li explained.

"I see that you've already severed a corpse soul..." Patriarch Miro remarked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Is there something wrong, Master?" Han Li asked.

After some contemplation, Patriarch Miro replied, "There's nothing wrong with that, it's just that given how far you've managed to cultivate the laws of time, I presume you must've already caught the attention of Gu Huojin."

Gu Huojin was the name of the Time Dao Ancestor, and Han Li's heart instantly jolted slightly upon hearing this.

"I've already been on the Heavenly Court's Immortal Slaying List for a very long time, but I'm not sure if the Time Dao Ancestor has already noticed me," Han Li said with a wry smile.

"The battle for the Great Dao is extremely perilous. I didn't even have any intention of fighting over the berth of Time Dao Ancestor with Gu Huojin, yet I was still killed by him. Your aptitude in cultivating the laws of time exceeds even my own, so there's no way that he hasn't already noticed you," Patriarch Miro said.

"Why didn't you want to become the Time Dao Ancestor?" Han Li asked.

"Do you know what becoming a Dao Ancestor entails?" Patriarch Miro asked with a smile.

"A Dao Ancestor is someone who has reached the pinnacle of the Great Dao," Han Li replied.

"That's right. In that case, do you know what reaching the pinnacle of the Great Dao entails?" Patriarch Miro asked.

Han Li was stumped by this question.

"Dao Ancestors stand at the very pinnacle of the law powers that they've mastered, but the Heavenly Dao still transcends above them all. While one is beneath the Great Dao, the law powers that they wield must rely on the support of the Great Dao and also be subject to the restrictions of the Great Dao. However, Dao Ancestors are cultivators who have become equals with the Great Dao, so what do you think will happen to them?" Patriarch Miro asked.

"Could it be that once one becomes a Dao Ancestor, they'll fuse with the Great Dao and become a part of it?" Han Li asked as a harrowing realization began to dawn on him.

"According to my knowledge, a Dao Ancestor won't be devoured by the Great Dao right away. However, whenever they use their law powers, that will speed up the rate at which they are assimilated by the Great Dao," Patriarch Miro explained.

"That must be why Dao Ancestors so seldomly take part in battle!" Han Li exclaimed as a look of realization appeared on his face.

"Precisely. However, they will still strike if they see someone that poses a threat to their status as Dao Ancestor, and there are some ways for Dao Ancestors to delay their assimilation to the Great Dao," Patriarch Miro replied.

Chapter 1288: Parting Gift

"There's no need to be too concerned, Master. The Reincarnation Palace has been making many moves of late, and the Gray Realm has also begun its invasion. Given how much turmoil the entire True Immortal Realm is in, surely the Heavenly Court won't be able to focus its attention on me anytime soon," Han Li said.

"Setting the Reincarnation Palace aside, the Gray Realm is hardly a threat in Gu Huojin's eyes. You don't understand just how powerful the Heavenly Court is. Once Gu Huojin identifies you as a threat, there's no way you'll be able to keep yourself safe from him at your current cultivation base. Hence, you have to progress your cultivation base as quickly as possible.

“Only once you've reached the late-Great Encompassment Stage will you be able to deal with the Heavenly Court on your own," Patriarch Miro said in a solemn manner.

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face, and he said, "It hasn't been long since my first corpse soul severance, and I've only just consolidated by mid-Great Encompassment Stage cultivation base. On top of that, there are still many immortal acupoints that I've yet to open, so I won't be able to sever my second corpse soul anytime soon."

"You are different from the average cultivator in that you're dual cultivator, and you've opened up almost all of the profound acupoints in body, so as long as you have sufficient resources at your disposal, it won't be difficult for you to open more immortal acupoints with the help of the Celestial Time Array. Hence, your true concerns must be elsewhere, right?" Patriarch Miro asked.

"Your wisdom is truly unmatched, Master. My last corpse soul severance wasn't a voluntary endeavor. Instead, someone used a Corpse Severance Talisman on me, thereby forcing me to sever my wicked corpse soul under very risky circumstances. If I try to sever a second corpse soul too soon, I fear that my cultivation foundation would be lacking in stability," Han Li explained.

"That's not a valid concern," Patriarch Miro reassured with a smile. "There is an element of fate when it comes to corpse soul severances, and it's not necessarily the case that one will be able to naturally sever their corpse souls once they've opened up enough immortal acupoints.

“Otherwise, people wouldn't have expended so many resources to create things like Corpse Severance Talismans. Of course, the more powerful one is and the more well-prepared they are, the higher the chances of a successful corpse soul severance.

“All I'm asking is that you build up a foundation as quickly as possible and sever your corpse souls as soon as you can when the time is right. Once you reach the late-Great Encompassment Stage, you'll be able to fend for yourself unless a Dao Ancestor personally comes after you."

"I see. Thank you for enlightening me, Master," Han Li said with a nod.

"Before that, you have to first complete your Five Elemental Illusory World to truly elevate your spirit domain to the Oneness Tier. That way, your spirit domain will be able to better work with the Celestial Time Array to speed up your cultivation," Patriarch Miro said.

"I've still yet to gather all of the treasures required to manifest all five of my time law treasures, so I'm afraid that will have to wait," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Have you forgotten why I instructed you to come to this Yama Manor?" Patriarch Miro asked with a smile.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a look of realization appeared on his face.

During their previous meeting, Patriarch Miro had given him three time law materials and a golden jade book, but all of those things had vanished after he transmigrated back to his time.

Patriarch Miro had told him to come and search for those things in the Yama Manor if it turned out that he was unable to take them back with him.

With that, Patriarch Miro swept a sleeve through the air to summon a length of azure wood, a broken, blue halberd, and a round, yellow stone, as well as that golden jade book.

On top of that, there were also two storage rings and a golden jade slip.

"These storage rings contain some Immortal Origin Stones and time law materials of different calibers to assist you in your cultivation. This jade slip contains the Immortal Golden Cloud cultivation art, which you stole back in the Merit Pavilion, but was unable to take with you," Patriarch Miro said.

Han Li was very touched by this gesture, and he extended a deep bow toward Patriarch Miro, who accepted his bow with a benevolent smile.

"Alright, we don't have much time left, so take this time to complete your Five Elemental Illusory World," Patriarch Miro instructed.

"Thank you, Master," Han Li said with another respectful bow, then began to examine the items laid out before him.

The length of azure wood, the broken, blue halberd, and the round, yellow stone were all time-attribute immortal treasures of quite a high caliber, and they corresponded with the wood, water, and earth attributes respectively. Clearly, Patriarch Miro had prepared them for the explicit purpose of facilitating the refinement of his Five Elemental Illusory World.

The Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree had already taken on a material form after fusing with the Twin Births Tree, thereby rendering the length of azure wood redundant, but the blue halberd and the yellow stone could be fused with his Clear Time Vial and Illusory Dawn Hourglass.

After stowing everything else away, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed under the date tree, and the Five Elemental Illusory World around him began to undergo a series of transformations at his behest.

The forest formed by the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree began to shrink before combining into a single Twin Births Tree, while the full moon formed by the Mantra Treasured Axis reverted back to its original form to hover in the air behind him.

The countless stars in the sky converged to form a golden torch that descended in front of him, while the winding river of time and the short mountain range remained in their original state, continuing to exist in an illusory form.

Han Li made a beckoning motion, and the blue halberd and the round stone rose up into the air before descending upon the river and the mountain range, respectively.

The halberd fell into the river with a splash, while the earth trembled violently as the stone fell into the mountain range.

Time law powers surged out of Han Li's body in a frenzy as he cast a rapid string of incantation seals toward the river and the mountain range.

All of a sudden, a layer of radiant, golden light filled the entire space, and a proud look appeared on Patriarch Miro's face upon seeing this, following which he strode over to his thatch hut before sitting down with his legs crossed against the wall.

He then joined his palms in front of his own chest, then swept his hands outward through the air before rejoining his palms, and a burst of golden light emerged from between them before filling this entire space.

Basked in the golden light, Han Li was struck by an indescribably blissful sensation, allowing him to instantly fully immerse himself in his cultivation.

The blue halberd began to slowly disintegrate into specks of blue light within the river of time, which also turned from golden to blue in color, while its surface began to ripple.

Meanwhile, the round, yellow stone had fused as one with the mountain range beneath the river of time, and the mountain range was also beginning to take on a substantial form.

Immediately thereafter, the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Time Severing Torch rose back up into the air in unison to form the moon and the stars, while the Twin Birth Tree descended back onto the mountain range to revert back into a lush forest.

A burst of formidable time law power fluctuations spread through the as the Five Elemental Illusory World was finally complete, and with that, Han Li's time spirit domain had truly reached the Oneness Tier.

An ecstatic look appeared on Han Li's face, but right at this moment, Patriarch Miro's voice suddenly rang out within his consciousness.

"I really want to see what heights you'll be able to reach in your cultivation of time law powers, but unfortunately, I don't have enough time left. It's unfortunate that I wasn't able to spend more time with you, and I'm afraid this is where I bid farewell to you, but before I go, here is my final parting gift. Do not squander it..."

Patriarch Miro's voice became quieter and quieter as he spoke, and Han Li cast his gaze toward him to discover that he was still wearing his usual, benevolent smile, but his facial features were beginning to blur, and his body was disintegrating into countless specks of golden light that spread through the air like the seeds of a dandelion.

"Master!" Han Li called out.

In the next instant, the entire secret area shuddered violently, and an enormous and extremely intricate array slowly rose up from the ground before springing into action on its own.

To Han Li's surprise, it was a Celestial Time Array.

Clearly, Patriarch Miro wanted him to go into seclusion here and use the Celestial Time Array to progress his own cultivation base as quickly as possible.

The Celestial Time Array fused as one with Han Li's Oneness Tier spirit domain to form an unprecedented space of accelerated time, and he immediately made a hand seal to channel his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

A vortex of golden light descended from the heavens to indundate Han Li's entire body, and countless bursts of extremely potent time law powers surged incessantly into his body from all directions.

Han Li threw his head back and roared to the heavens as golden light came erupted out of all of his orifices, and every single one of the pores on his entire body had been pierced through by time law powers.

A string of dull thumps rang out within his body as immortal acupoints were opened one after another in rapid succession.

However, this was not a pleasant experience at all for Han Li. Such a violent influx of time law powers was something that even a late-Great Encompassment cultivator may not have been able to endure, and only his tremendous physical constitution, coupled with the fact that this burst of power was combined with some of Patriarch Miro's time law powers, allowed him to cling onto a shred of lucidity.

Due to the influence of Patriarch Miro, this burst of power was traveling through Han Li's body as gently as possible, but even so, it was still subjecting him to unimaginable agony.

Chapter 1289: Leaving the Yama Manor

Han Li's robes were instantly reduced to nothingness by the golden light erupting out of his body, and all of his hair began to stand up on end in a completely vertical fashion. At the same time, countless crimson runes had appeared over his exposed body.

Right at this moment, the Heaven Controlling Vial rose up from his chest to hover in front of his eyes, and all of the leaf patterns on its surface lit up, releasing a burst of green radiance that encompassed his entire body, following which the vial spirit's voice suddenly rang out.

"You really are a lucky little bastard! Focus all of your efforts on absorbing this power, I'll take care of the rest."

Han Li wanted to cuss out the vial spirit for finally showing up after pretending to be mute this entire time, but he was in too much pain to utter a coherent sentence.

He did as the vial spirit instructed, opening up all of his acupoints to embrace the time law power surging into his body, and all of a sudden, he felt as if an explosion had suddenly rung out in his mind.

His spiritual sense descended deep into his consciousness, and he was no longer able to feel any of the changes in his physical body, but he had become far more sensitive to the changes taking place in his consciousness.

All of a sudden, a series of golden characters appeared in his consciousness to form a passage of golden text, and it was the contents of the golden jade book that had been given to him by Patriarch Miro.

The book contained Patriarch Miro's cultivation insights when it came to the laws of time, as well as many of the True Mantra Sect's time-attribute secret techniques, including the likes of the Mantra Domain and the True Mantra Palm Seal.

Han Li immediately began reading through the passage of text, and before long, he became completely immersed in it.

......

Close to twenty years flew by in a flash.

Under the cloud of suffocating miasma, the lush and vibrant island had been reduced to a barren wasteland.

Weeping Soul was seated with her legs crossed and her eyes closed beside the stone plaque at the center of the island with the Soul Locking Box that contained Gui Wu's soul fragment sitting beside her, while Jin Tong was nowhere to be seen.

Right at this moment, Gui Wu's soul fragment emerged from the box, then cast a concerned gaze toward Weeping Soul as it urged in a sincere and heartfelt manner, "The entrance of this stone plaque closed over ten years ago. In all likelihood, your master has already perished in there, so why insist on staying here? Come with me to find the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate so you can recover your memories and uncover your true purpose!"

This was clearly not the first time that Weeping Soul had heard something like this from Gui Wu, and she didn't even bother to respond.

Right at this moment, a beam of golden light came crashing down from the heavens right beside Gui Wu, and the impact of its landing sent such powerful shockwaves sweeping through the air that Gui Wu's soul fragment was almost scattered on the spot.

Jin Tong emerged from the dust with a small, dark green beast in her grasp, and she took a hostile glance at Gui Wu, then asked, "He's trying to convince you to leave again, isn't he?"

Weeping Soul opened her eyes as she replied with a smile, "He says the same things every single time, it really is starting to get very repetitive."

"Your spiritual connection with him has already been severed, so why are you both still so convinced that he'll return?" Gui Wu wailed.

"Because he always comes back," Jin Tong replied in a confident manner.

"Master will be back for sure," Weeping Soul chimed in in agreement, then closed her eyes.

Jin Tong gave Gui Wu a menacing glare, then sat down onto a rock to play with the little beast that she had just captured.

Gui Wu could heave a forlorn sigh before returning to the Soul Locking Box.

Meanwhile, in the Yama Manor.

Han Li remained seated on the spot with his legs crossed, and all of the golden light emanating from his body had already faded, but his entire body was still radiating golden light from all of the immortal acupoints that he had opened, of which there were 1,319, indicating that he had already reached the pinnacle of the mid-Great Encompassment Stage.

"My last corpse soul severance was forced upon me, but this time, my corpse soul refuses to appear, even though I'm ready for it," Han Li sighed to himself as he opened his eyes.

The Celestial Time Array around him had already faded, leaving only his spirit domain behind.

He had already opened all of these immortal acupoints two years ago, but he had remained in seclusion in the hopes that he would be able to sever his second corpse soul as well.

However, on this occasion, his kind corpse soul wasn't displaying any signs of emergence.

I've already been cultivating for hundreds of thousands of years in the Celestial Time Array, which means that quite a long time must've passed by in the outside world as well. Jin Tong and Weeping Soul must be worried about me, and I'm not making any further progress here anyway, so it's about time that I left.

With his spirit domain completely elevated to the Oneness Tier, the time accelerating effects of the Celestial Time Array had been enhanced even further, to the extent that one year in the array was equivalent to thirty thousand years in the outside world.

With a sweep of his sleeve, his Five Elemental Illusory World reverted back into his five time law treasure manifestations, and there was a cumulative one thousand eight hundred time law threads wrapped around them.

For some reason, he was unable to attain any further time law threads beyond one thousand eight hundred.

Even so, he had benefited immensely from this stint of seclusion. Not only had he reached the pinnacle of the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, the number of time law threads in his possession had doubled. Furthermore, his understanding of time law powers had improved significantly, and he had also mastered several powerful abilities of the True Mantra Sect.

He wasn't able to reach the late-Great Encompassment Stage as Patriarch Miro had hoped, but this amount of progress was certainly nothing to scoff at.

With a casual sweep of his sleeve, he conjured up a vortex of golden light before stepping into it, and in the next instant, he emerged from the stone plaque on the island amid a flash of golden light.

Weeping Soul immediately opened her eyes, while Jin Tong tossed aside the little beast that she was playing with as she exclaimed in an ecstatic manner, "You've finally come out, Uncle!"

Gui Wu also emerged from the Soul Locking Box once again, and a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes as he said, "Congratulations on the significant strides you've made in your cultivation, Fellow Daoist Han."

"Weren't you just saying that Uncle must've already died in there?" Jin Tong asked with a disdainful expression.

Gui Wu's expression remained unchanged as he countered, "I said no such thing. You must've misheard."

"Sorry to keep you all waiting," Han Li said.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I've already brought you to this Yama Manor, so in return, it's about time that you took me to the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate," Gui Wu reminded.

"I'll be sure to fulfill my promise to you," Han Li replied.

An intrigued look appeared on Gui Wu's face as he asked, "May I ask what was in the Yama Manor, Fellow Daoist Han? There must've been some astounding opportunity waiting for you inside for you to have advanced so far in your cultivation base in such a short time."

Weeping Soul and Jin Tong began to carefully examine Han Li upon hearing this, but neither of them were able to see any change in him.

Han Li smiled as he dodged the question and said, "You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu. Let's set off for the Yellow Springs. Can I ask you to lead the way again?"

"Of course," Gui Wu repiled. "The Yellow Springs can be found where the Black River, Infernal, and Yama Regions meet. If we set off from here, we'll have to pass through most of the Yama Region, and on top of that, the Reincarnation King himself constantly cultivates near the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate, and his forces are also stationed near the Yellow Springs, so it won't be easy to get there," Gui Wu replied.

"How are we supposed to get there then? Given that the Reincarnation King is the ruler of three regions, his forces must be extremely formidable. How are we supposed to contend with that? And what is the Reincarnation King's current cultivation base?" Han Li asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"Back before I was sealed away, the Reincarnation King was already at the late-Great Encompassment Stage, so he's most likely already at the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage now. However, I'm sure he still hasn't become a Dao Ancestor yet. Otherwise, I would've been sure to have sensed it," Gui Wu replied.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this.

"If the Reincarnation King is at the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage, then you're trying to send us to our deaths!" Weeping Soul accused.

"There's no need to be concerned. Once we reach the Yellow Springs, I have a way to sneak us in," Gui Wu reassured.

"How are you going to do that?" Jin Tong asked.

"It's too early to reveal that now. All will be revealed once we reach the Yellow Springs," Gui Wu said with a mysterious smile, and both Jin Tong and Weeping Soul's expressions instantly darkened upon hearing this.

"Now's not the time for jokes, Gui Wu. Tell us how you plan to get us to the Yellow Springs. Otherwise, if these two get angry, you know what consequences will await you," Han Li threatened.

"Alright," Gui Wu acquiesced. "The place where the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate is situated is one that concerns the cycle of reincarnation, and every once in a while, a Six Paths Gale will come blowing out of it. The Six Paths Gale is something that even Dao Ancestors don't dare to touch, so whenever this happens, the Reincarnation King and his forces will evacuate the Yellow Springs, thereby allowing us the opportunity to sneak in."

"If this Six Paths Gale is as formidable as you say, then how will we be able to get in there?" Han Li asked.

"During all of my time presiding over the Yama Region, I've conducted some research into the Six Paths Gale, and I know of some loopholes that we can exploit. It'll only give us a limited amount of time, but it'll be enough for us to make a round trip," Gui Wu replied with a confident smile.

Chapter 1290: Encountering Devils in the Underworld

"Seeing as you've already considered everything, I'll go there with you, and I'll decide how to proceed depending on the situation there," Han Li said.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Han. I'm sure the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate is an extraordinary treasure that I'm sure will be very helpful to you as well," Gui Wu replied in an ecstatic manner.

"Hold on a second, Master, there's something else I need to ask," Weeping Soul interjected, and Han Li gestured for her to go ahead.

"Ask me anything, Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul," Gui Wu prompted with a smile.

"When you say the Six Paths Gale emerges every once in a while, what length of time are you referring to? We can't stay in the underworld for too long," Weeping Soul said.

"The Six Paths Gale arises very frequently, roughly once every one thousand years. According to my calculations, the next one is set to arise within the next century," Gui Wu replied.

"If these Six Paths Gales are so formidable, won't they damage the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate?" Weeping Soul asked.

"The Six Paths Reincarnation Plate is a naturally occurring treasure in the underworld, a manifestation of the Great Dao here, so it's incredibly resilient. On top of that, the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate and the Six Paths Gale share the same origins, so one won't damage the other," Gui Wu explained.

"Will we be passing through the territories of many powerful ghostly tribes on the way to the Yellow Springs?"

This time, the question was raised by Jin Tong.

"We'll inevitably have to pass through some ghostly settlements, but given your powers, you'll definitely be able to pass through just fine. On top of that, I'm very familiar with the route that must be taken to get there, and I'll be sure to provide the three of you with instructions to avoid as much trouble as possible," Gui Wu replied.

"It seems like you have everything very well thought out, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu," Han Li remarked.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Han. Without your help, all of my planning will hardly amount to anything," Gui Wu replied with a smile.

With that, the three of them set off in the northwestern direction in accordance with Gui Wu's instructions.

"Do you really believe in what he says, Master? What if he's deceiving us like that Xue Li did?" Weeping Soul asked through voice transmission.

"Were you able to tell whether he was lying or not earlier?" Han Li asked.

"I wasn't. Even though all that remains of him is a soul fragment, his lofty cultivation base made it impossible for me to detect anything," Weeping Soul replied in a slightly dejected manner.

"It's fine. Right now, Gui Wu is nothing more than a soul fragment, so if he tries to step out of line, then I'll strike him down right away. On top of that, this Six Paths Reincarnation Plate sounds like an extremely powerful treasure, so it's worth the risk," Han Li said, and Weeping Soul nodded in response.

Half a month flew by in the blink of an eye, and the deeper they ventured into the Yama Region, the more ghostly tribes they encountered.

These tribes either formed settlements or resided in cities, presenting a stark contrast to the chaos of the Black River Region.

Fortunately, with Gui Wu serving as their guide, they were able to traverse through the Yama Region without encountering much danger, and at the moment, the three of them were flying through the air, using the dark clouds as cover.

While flying along, Han Li was simultaneously reading through a thick book that he had stolen from a city that they had passed by, and the information in the book matched everything that Gui Wu had told them thus far.

"Master, there seems to be a battle taking place up ahead," Weeping Soul suddenly said, and Han Li immediately stopped in his tracks as he stowed his book away.

Weeping Soul and Jin Tong also drew to a halt on either side of him.

"Oh? I didn't think there would be more outsiders here in the underworld. And this time, they're from the Devil Realm. How intriguing," Gui Wu remarked as he emerged from his Soul Locking Box.

Han Li took a glance at him, then turned his gaze to Weeping Soul for confirmation.

Weeping Soul took a surprised look at Gui Wu, then confirmed, "That's right, one of the two parties up ahead does indeed consist of cultivators from the Devil Realm."

"How are you able to detect something so far away even in your current state?" Han Li asked as he turned to Gui Wu.

"In the underworld, one can easily detect things over this distance as long as one is skilled in the manipulation of their spiritual sense fluctuations. You're a human, so it's only to be expected that you're not that proficient in manipulating your spiritual sense, but it's very surprising that Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul was only able to detect the battle from such close proximity.

“Have you forgotten even the fundamental abilities of our underworld ghostly tribes?" Gui Wu asked in a bewildered manner.

"I already told you that I don't remember anything about the underworld," Weeping Soul harrumphed coldly.

Gui Wu spoke no further on the subject as he averted his gaze.

"How far is your current sensory range, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu?" Han Li asked.

"Right now, I am but a soul fragment, so my sensory range has been reduced to only around sixty thousand kilometers," Gui Wu replied.

Han Li was stunned to hear that even in Gui Wu's current state, his sensory range was still fifty to sixty times that of Weeping Soul.

"That's far further than any of us. Can we count on you to serve as our scout from now on, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu?" Han Li asked.

"Of course," Gui Wu replied with a smile.

"Let's get a little closer to see what's happening up ahead," Han Li said with a wave of his hand, and the group continued onward for a short while before concealing themselves near a valley.

Weeping Soul chanted an incantation to unleash the concealment technique that she had used on herself and Han Li earlier.

It was just a pity that this technique was only effective for a limited time. Otherwise, it would've spared them a lot of trouble on this journey.

"This is the Infernal King Aura Concealment Technique! You really are the reincarnation of the Infernal King! She was the only one capable of using this ability!" Gui Wu exclaimed in an ecstatic manner.

"I don't know what you're talking about. I'm Weeping Soul, not the Infernal King that you speak of," Weeping Soul harrumphed coldly.

Meanwhile, Han Li was peering into the valley to discover that it was roughly ten to fifteen kilometers in size, and there were countless black shadows gathered within it to form an enormous encirclement.

These black shadows were all ghostly creatures with human bodies and goat heads, and they each stood at around forty to fifty feet tall with dense, black fur covering the entirety of their bodies.

These ghostly beings wielded giant, black scimitars that were giving off dense, black mist, and with each slash of the scimitar, a saber projection of black mist would be unleashed toward the center of the encirclement.

These ghostly beings were clearly very proficient at working together, and the black saber projections that they unleashed came together to form a huge saber array that encompassed the entire valley like a massive dome.

"This is the Shang Goat Ghost Tribe, a tribe that's not particularly powerful in the context of the three regions," Gui Wu said.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the center of the array to discover a pair of black-robed figures, one tall and one short, and both of them had their faces concealed.

Furthermore, their black robes were imbued with some type of power that kept out all prying spiritual sense, making it impossible to glean the appearance of the two figures.

Four black banners with purple clouds embroidered upon them were circling around the pair of black-robed figures, forming a purple, hemispherical, protect barrier to ward off the surrounding saber array.

The protective barrier was extremely resilient, displaying no signs of weakness in the face of the formidable saber array.

"Those are indeed two devilish beings, and their cultivation bases are quite advanced. I wonder what they're doing here," Han Li mused.

Extremely pure devilish qi was emanating from their bodies, and the aura of the taller one indicated that they were already at the Great Encompassment Stage.

Even though the appearance of the shorter figure was completely concealed, the delicate curves of their body suggested it was a woman, and her cultivation base was slightly inferior to that of her companion, but it was also at the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage.

Despite their formidable powers, they were surrounded by far too many Shang Goat beings, and they were trapped within the saber array, unable to break free.

"Those two look like they're in trouble, Master. Should we save them?" Weeping Soul asked.

As opposed to answering her question, Han Li turned to Gui Wu as he asked, "Fellow Daoist Gui Wu, are there any formidable ghostly beings nearby? Will we attract any trouble if we attack these Shang Goat beings?"

"Those Shang Goat Ghost Tribe isn't all that powerful, but they serve the Horse King Ghost Tribe, one of the four most powerful tribes of the Yama Region. If you want to save them, then you can, but you have to do so quickly. As long as you can ensure that, then you should be able to stay out of trouble," Gui Wu replied.

Han Li weighed up his options for a moment, then instructed, "Jin Tong, Weeping Soul, break the saber array and save those two."

Weeping Soul and Jin Tong gave an affirmative response, and the latter reached out to make a grabbing motion with her right hand, conjuring up a mountainous, black claw that came swooping down upon the saber array in the valley.

At the same time, Jin Tong transformed into a Gold Devouring Immortal the size of a house before sweeping her front legs through the air, releasing a flurry of sword qi that instantly formed a sword mountain before crashing into the saber array alongside the giant, black claw.

The Shang Goat beings had completely failed to detect the presence of Han Li's trio due to Weeping Soul's concealment technique, so they were caught completely off guard.

Two earth-shattering booms rang out in rapid succession as the black claw and the sword mountain came crashing down upon the saber array, instantly destroying most of it, but the array was still just barely able to hold itself intact.

Black and golden waves of light swept through the surrounding air, easily pulverizing the mountains that surrounded the valley.

Gusts of ferocious wind erupted into the heavens before sweeping outward in all directions, razing everything within a radius of several hundred kilometers to the ground.

Chapter 1291: Reunion

The pair of devilish beings trapped within the saber array didn't know what was happening, but they seemed to have realized that reinforcements had arrived, and they immediately began their retaliation.

A silver lute appeared in the hands of the taller devilish being, and as he strummed his fingers over its strings, around a dozen long, black spatial rifts emerged around him, then darted toward the broken section of the saber array like a nest of den of black pythons.

A loud tearing sound rang out as the saber array was torn apart even further, to the point that only a thin layer of it remained.

A combination of shock and recognition instantly appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

Immediately thereafter, the black-robed woman also sprang into action, sweeping her sleeves through the air to release a pair of purple balls, which transformed into two purple puppets with arcs of purple lightning flashing over their bodies.

The auras of these two puppets weren't inferior to hers in the slightest, and the purple lightning flashing over their bodies contained a type of explosive lightning law powers.

The woman spread her hands open, and ten black threads that were imbued with a type of peculiar law powers shot out of her fingertips before vanishing into the bodies of the two puppets.

The auras of the purple puppets instantly swelled by around twofold, and they transformed into a pair of giant, purple balls of lightning before exploding violently.

Finally, the saber projection was unable to hold itself together any longer, and a huge hole was torn into it by the force of the explosion.

The taller devilish being immediately grabbed onto the black-robed woman's arm before flying out of the hole in the saber array as a streak of silver light, and they were met by Han Li a short distance away.

Wary looks appeared on the faces of the two devilish beings, and the taller one of the two asked, "Who are you?"

At the moment, Han Li had adopted a disguise using his black Reincarnation Palace mask that made him strongly resemble a ghostly entity, so it was no wonder that these two devilish beings were so wary of him.

Jin Tong and Weeping Soul had flown back to Han Li's side, while the Shang Goat beings were also storming toward them from afar.

"This isn't the place to talk, let's get out of here," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air, and five enormous bolts of golden lightning erupted out of his hand, threatening to tear the surrounding space apart.

This was the first time that Han Li was using his Cardinal Heavenly Lightning since reaching the pinnacle of the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, and its tremendous power came as a surprise even to himself.

The five bolts of lightning descended near the group before intertwining to form a lightning teleportation array, but right at this moment, the black-robed woman spread her fingers open to release five black threads once again, and they vanished into the surrounding lightning array, upon which the array instantly fell still, as if it had fallen under her control.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

"Where are you planning to take us?" the woman yelled, and her companion did nothing to stop her.

It was clear to them that this lightning array was intended to teleport them away from this place, and even though Han Li's trio had just saved them, they were still unable to tell whether their saviors were friends or foe.

As for the approaching Shang Goat beings, the taller devilish being didn't regard them as a threat. Now that they had been freed from the encirclement, they could get away anytime that they pleased.

With no time to explain, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to eradicate the black threads extending out of the black-robed woman's fingertips, and the golden lightning array instantly took shape.

A storm of black saber projections from the Shang Goat beings tore through the surrounding area, but by then, Han Li and the others had already vanished from within the lightning array.

The Shang Goat beings began yelling and cursing as they continued to attack the spot where the lightning array had been just a moment ago to vent their frustration.

"Alright, that's enough!"

An authoritative voice rang out as a particularly tall and imposing Shang Goat being emerged.

This Shang Goat being was roughly twice the height of his brethren, and he had a pair of scimitar-like horns on his head, giving him a very authoritative appearance.

All the other Shang Goat beings immediately turned to him, and one of them asked, "Should we go after them, Chief?"

"I'd like to see you try! Those outsiders were very powerful, and their allies seem to be just as formidable, if not more so. You can go after them if you like, but don't blame me if you get yourself killed!" the chief of the Shang Goat Ghost Tribe sneered.

The other Shang Goat being immediately hung his head and fell silent upon hearing this.

"Let's all go back and report this matter to the Horse King Tribe," the chief declared, and all of the Shang Goat beings promptly departed.

......

In the sky above a black forest several million kilometers away, a golden lightning array abruptly appeared out of thin air with Han Li and the other inside.

However, instead of dissipating, the lightning array immediately activated once again, teleporting Han Li's group away a second time.

After several stints of teleportation in rapid succession, the group appeared over a dark red desert, and only then did the lightning array finally fade away.

The two devilish beings immediately sprang back in retreat as they asked in a wary manner, "Who are you?"

"It's me," Han Li said as he reverted back to his original appearance.

"Fellow Daoist Han!" the taller devilish being exclaimed as he pulled down the hook of his cloak, revealing himself to be none other than Shi Chuankong.

He was significantly taller than before, and his physique had also become far more muscular, clearly indicating that he had made some stunning progress in the realm of physical cultivation.

"I didn't think we would be reunited here in the underworld, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li said, then turned to the black-robed woman with an affectionate look in his eyes.

"Long time no see, Violet Spirit."

"What are you doing here, Brother Han?" the black-robed woman asked as she also removed her own hood to reveal a set of stunningly beautiful features.

Having just endured a fierce battle, she was looking a little pale, and her chest was heaving slightly from exertion, giving her an additional layer of allure.

A wave of emotions welled up in Han Li's heart at the sight of her, but he forcibly suppressed them.

Seeing as Han Li had already revealed his true appearance, Jin Tong and Weeping Soul also did the same.

Violet Spirit's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of them, but she didn't say anything.

Han Li naturally noticed the change in her expression, and he introduced, "These two are Jin Tong and Weeping Soul. They used to be my spirit beasts, but both of them have attained human forms."

Violet Spirit's concerns were immediately put to rest upon hearing this, and she turned to the two of them with an intrigued smile.

Han Li had told her about Jin Tong and Weeping Soul in the past, and they had even met back in the mortal realm. However, at the time, Jin Tong and Weeping Soul were still yet to attain high levels of intelligence.

Back then, they had still been a soul-sucking giant ape and a Gold Devouring Beetle, yet both of them had undergone massive transformations since then.

Jin Tong merely gave Violet Spirit a nod, while Weeping Soul was much more friendly as she said, "I heard from my master that you two previously met in the Devil Realm, but at the time, I was in an unconscious state in the Flower Branch domain."

"Indeed. Thank you for saving me and Fellow Daoist Shi," Violet Spirit said as he extended a grateful salute toward Weeping Soul and Jin Tong.

"There's no need to thank us, Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit. It's only right that we come to the rescue of someone so close to our master's heart," Weeping Soul replied with a smile.

A faint blush appeared on Violet Spirit's face upon hearing this, while Shi Chuankong placed a hand on Han Li's shoulder as he jibed, "Look at all these beauties around you! You truly are the envy of all men, Fellow Daoist Han."

Han Li slapped his hand away as he replied in an exasperated manner, "Quit talking nonsense! Jin Tong and Weeping Soul are just companions of mine. By the way, what are the two of you doing here?"

A hesitant look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face, and he didn't immediately respond.

"If the answer concerns some secret of yours, then just pretend like I never asked," Han Li said.

"Thank you for being so considerate, Fellow Daoist Han," Shi Chuankong said in a relieved manner.

Violet Spirit turned to Shi Chuankong as if she wanted to say something, but ultimately decided against it.

Shi Chuankong also wanted to ask Han Li why he was in the underworld, but he felt too embarrassed to ask, seeing as he had refused to answer the same question when posed to him by Han Li.

In order to break the awkward silence, he looked around as he asked, "What is this place?"

"Judging from the environment, it looks like this should be a place called the Hellfire Desert. The climate here is very hot, so most ghostly beings stay far away from here. As a result, there aren't any powerful tribes residing nearby, making it a relatively safe place. Do you two need to take a rest?" Han Li asked.

"I would like to take a rest. I'm a little weary from the earlier battle," Violet Spirit replied.

The battle against the Shang Goat beings had taken its toll on her, and now that she and Shi Chuankong had been saved, a wave of exhaustion was walking over here.

"In that case, let's rest here for a while," Shi Chuankong said as he swept a sleeve through the air to release several hundred streaks of black light, all of which were array tools that landed in the surrounding area to form a black light barrier that was several thousand feet in diameter.

Violet Spirit and Shi Chuankong sat down with their legs crossed and pulled out some Devilish Origin Stone to aid them in their recovery, while Han Li's trio stood on lookout duty.

Chapter 1292: Shocking Identity

"Brother Han..."

Right at his moment, Violet Spirit's voice rang out beside his ears, yet before he could turn to look at her, her voice rang out once again, this time with a bit more urgency.

"Don't move! Otherwise, you're going to arouse Shi Chuankong's suspicions."

"Do you have something to tell me?" Han Li asked through voice transmission while continuing to pretend to survey the landscape.

"Shi Chuankong definitely won't allow me to tell you about the objective of our journey to the underworld, so I can only tell you in secret like this," Violet Spirit said.

"What is your objective?" Han Li asked in a curious manner.

"We've come to the underworld to secure a treasure by the name of the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate. It's an incredible treasure that can allow one to regain their memories from their past life, thereby receiving their cultivation experience from their previous life to significantly enhance their cultivation base," Violet Spirit revealed.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

Violet Spirit mistook the surprise in Han Li's eyes for disbelief, and she hurriedly continued, "I know it sounds unbelievable, but I'm telling you the truth. Someone in the Devil Realm has previously used this method to make significant strides in their cultivation base in a very short time, and Senior Xie sent me and Shi Chuankong into the underworld to try and secure it.

“This is a secret of the Night Sun Empire's imperial family, and that's why Shi Chuankong didn't tell you. I suggest you follow me and Shi Chuankong in secret, Brother Han. The Six Paths Reincarnation Plate will definitely be useful for you as well."

"I believe you, Violet Spirit," Han Li reassured. "In fact, I've already heard about the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate, and we're actually on our way to it as well."

This time, it was Violet Spirit's turn to be surprised.

After a brief silence, she said, "I'm glad to hear that. I've heard that the Heavenly Court has been exerting tremendous pressure upon you of late, so you have to make sure to grasp this opportunity."

A hint of warmth welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this, and there were countless things that he wanted to say to her, but ultimately, he replied, "I'll do my best."

With that, Violet Spirit fell silent as she continued to focus on her own recovery, while Han Li also turned his attention back to lookout duty.

Close to two hours later, Violet Spirit and Shi Chuankong opened their eyes before rising to their feet, and the latter said in an apologetic manner, "Sorry to keep you waiting, Fellow Daoist Han."

"It's fine. Now that both of you have had a chance to rest, it's time to set off. We're traveling to the Yellow Springs, how about you?" Han Li asked with a smile.

Shi Chuankong was clearly very much taken aback to hear this, and Han Li explained, "We heard that there's a treasure by the name of the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate there that can awaken memories of one's past life, and we really want to see it for ourselves."

A wry smile appeared on Shi Chuankong's face as he said, "So you already knew about the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate. If I had known that, I would've been honest and upfront with you from the outset. Violet Spirit and I are also going there, so let's travel together."

"That's quite a coincidence," Han Li replied with a nod, and shortly thereafter, the group set off for the Yellow Springs.

......

Somewhere vast, chaotic space was a massive, floating city. The city was riddled with tall buildings, while its streets were wide and pristine. It was a city that wasn't inferior in the slightest even compared with the likes of Nine Origins City and Gilded City.

There were countless people roaming the streets, while innumerable streaks of light flashed through the air, presenting a lively and bustling sight to behold.

The people in the city came in all descriptions, including humans, devilish cultivators, demon beasts, ghostly beings, and even Gray Immortals, and all of them were getting along in a very harmonious fashion.

This would've undoubtedly been an astonishing sight for many cultivators of the True Immortal Realm.

At the center of the city stood a tall, dark red castle that dwarfed all of the surrounding buildings, and there were countless antiquated buildings within the castle.

The castle was also surrounded by tall and imposing walls, clearly indicating that it was a very important place.

Right at this moment, a streak of dark red light flew directly into the castle from afar, then descended in front of the palace to reveal none other than Wyrm 3.

The palace gates were wide open, and there were two yellow-robed guards standing on either side of them, both of whom immediately extended salute toward Wyrm 3.

Wyrm 3 paid no heed to the two of them as she entered the palace, and the interior was rather dimly lit, illuminated only by two rows of lit braziers hanging from the walls on either side of the palace.

The palace was completely empty with the exceptions of a raised platform at the very back and a chunk of azure jade that was the same height as a grown man at the center, standing beside which was an azure-robed man.

The man was slightly hunched over, and he was in the process of meticulously chiseling away at the chunk of jade.

The statue was already close to half-complete, and judging from its outlines, it appeared that the azure-robed man was carving out a woman.

"Wyrm 3 pays her respects to the esteemed palace master!" Wyrm 3 greeted with a respectful bow.

"How are things going on your end?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked as he continued to focus on his sculpting.

"The Nine Origins Temple and the Heavenly Court still have a very strong presence in the Golden Origin Immortal Region, so I've already evacuated all of our members who are most prone to being exposed. The ones left are all extremely well concealed, and it should be impossible for the Nine Origins Temple and the Heavenly Court to uncover them, Wyrm 3 reported."

"It's better to be safe than sorry. Distribute Soul Reversion Pills to all of them, and if they're exposed and perish in battle, draw their souls into the underworld right away to arrange reincarnations," the Reincarnation Palace Master instructed, and Wyrm 3 gave an affirmative response.

"Where is Han Li right now?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked.

"I've already sent out people to search for him, but he seems to have gone missing after he was last sighted on Raised Flagon Mountain of the Chu Yu Immortal Region," Wyrm 3 replied with slightly furrowed brows.

"Oh? Could it be that he's gone into seclusion somewhere?" the Reincarnation Palace Master speculated.

"That's certainly a possibility," Wyrm 3 replied.

"If you can't find him, then don't bother searching for him anymore. Now that he's already seen Rushuang, I'm sure he'll reveal himself to us soon," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

Wyrm 3 hesitated momentarily, then asked in an intrigued manner, "How are the two of them related, Palace Master? It seems like Han Li cares a great deal for her."

"Rushuang was Han Li's dao partner back when he was in a lower realm," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"I see," Wyrm 3 mused with an enlightened expression.

The Reincarnation Palace Master turned around as he said, "You've been working very hard lately. Go and take a good rest."

His face was still concealed in shadows, but judging from the outlines of his facial features, there seemed to be quite a gentle look on his face at the moment.

"Palace Mster, you told me that you would tell me about my past once I completed the Nine Origins Temple mission. Now that the mission is complete, can you tell me who my parents are?" Wyrm 3 asked with a look of resolve in her eyes.

The Reincarnation Palace Master looked back at her in silence, and the resolve in her eyes began to waver slightly in the face of his gaze, but she didn't back down.

"It looks like you really want to know. Fine, in that case, I can tell you who your mother is right now," the Reincarnation Palace Master sighed, and Wyrm 3 breath instantly became hitched in her throat upon hearing this.

"I brought Rushuang back to our Reincarnation Palace not just for Han Li, but also for your sake. Do you understand what I'm saying?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked.

An astonished look appeared on Wyrm 3's face upon hearing this.

"You're saying Rushuang is my..."

"That's right, Rushuang is your mother," the Reincarnation Palace Master revealed.

......

Some time later, Wyrm 3 had already left the palace, leaving the Reincarnation Palace Master to continue his sculpting.

The sculpture was quickly completed, and it was a woman in a palatial dress, but her face was completely smooth and devoid of features, and it appeared that the Reincarnation Palace Master had no intention of continuing.

The Reincarnation Palace Master's artisanship was so exceptional that even with the woman left completely devoid of facial features, she was somehow still extremely lifelike, and he reached out to stroke the woman's smooth face in an entranced manner.

......

In the underworld.

Due to the fact that they had already been exposed to the Shang Goat Ghost Tribe earlier, they made no further effort to conceal themselves and were traveling at full speed.

As opposed to traveling in a straight line, the group was constantly changing directions in accordance with Gui Wu's instructions, doing their best to avoid the ghostly settlements along the way.

Several days later, they arrived before a black forest.

The trees in this forest were remarkably tall, with many of them standing at several thousand, even in excess of ten thousand feet, and their canopies were also very lush and dense, almost forming an impermeable barrier that kept out all natural light.

As a result, it was extremely dark in the forest, and there was a vast abundance of ghostly qi inside.

As the wind blew through the forest, a strangled, howling sound rang out, resembling the wailing of countless ghosts.

"This appears to be the Hundred Ghost Forest, a renowned place of peril in the underworld. Are we going to pass straight through it?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"The Yellow Springs are just on the other side of the forest, and they're surrounded by the forces of the four major ghostly tribes of the Yama Region. It would be bad if we were discovered by them, so it's safer to travel through the Hundred Ghost Forest," Han Li replied.

This was a path suggested to him by Gui Wu, who had begun communicating to Han Li solely through voice transmission ever since Shi Chuankong and Violet Spirit joined their party, and it seemed that he didn't want to reveal his own existence to them.

Chapter 1293: Bleak Souls and Reincarnation

"According to my knowledge, the Hundred Ghost Forest is a very dangerous place, and we know next to nothing about it, so isn't this too risky a course of action?" Shi Chuankong asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"How much do you know about this Hundred Ghost Forest, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know a whole lot, but I've heard that there are many bleak souls in the Hundred Ghost Forest that are very troublesome to deal with," Shi Chuankong replied.

"What are bleak souls?" Han Li asked, and Weeping Soul, Jin Tong, and Violet Spirit also turned to him with curious expressions.

"Normally, there's a limit on the number of times that a soul can enter the cycle of reincarnations, but there are some souls that possess exceptional aptitude or were able to exceed this limit due to other special reasons. These souls will gradually turn into bleak souls, which possess no intelligence, only a basic instinct for slaughter.

“Due to the special environment in this Hundred Ghost Forest, it has become a perfect gathering place for these bleak souls, making it a very dangerous place," Shi Chuankong explained.

"No matter how powerful these bleak souls are, they're still souls, are they not? Surely they'll be easier to deal with than the four major tribes," Weeping Soul said.

"I agree. With Weeping Soul on our side, no souls will be able to pose any threat to us," Jin Tong chimed in in agreement.

"In that case, let's try our luck through the Hundred Ghost Forest," Shi Chuankong acquiesced with a nod.

With the decision made, the group immediately flew into the Hundred Ghost Forest.

Inside the forest, visibility was limited to no more than several dozen feet, but thankfully, spiritual sense remained uninhibited here, so they were able to traverse through the forest without too much trouble.

Han Li was flying along at the forefront of the group with his Infernal Devilish Eyes activated, paying close attention to everything that was happening in the surrounding area.

All of a sudden, a petite, two-headed, black snake shot out of the forest like lightning with the intention of sinking its fangs into his calf.

However, before it was even able to reach Han Li, its body was split into two down the center by a streak of golden light. Black blood came spilling out of its body, sending plumes of smoke rising up into the air upon splattering onto the ground.

The two halves of its body twitched a few times before falling still, and by then, Han Li's group was already long gone.

"It looks like there are also many powerful ghostly beasts in the Hundred Ghost Forest in addition to the bleak souls. Make sure to be on your guard, everyone," Shi Chuankong cautioned, and everyone nodded in response with alert expressions.

Around half a month passed by in the blink of an eye, and as the group advanced deeper and deeper into the Hundred Ghost Forest, they began to encounter more and more ghostly beasts, some of which had already reached the High Zenith Stage.

The group tried to avoid trouble as much as possible, and all of the trouble that they were unable to avoid was quickly eradicated.

Close to another month quickly passed by.

On this day, a cacophony of roars and sharp cries rang out near a black river, and the commotion was audible for hundreds of kilometers.

However, it then quickly subsided, and peace and quiet was restored.

The entire area within several dozen kilometers of the river had been severely ravaged, and several massive, bottomless rifts that stretched for dozens of kilometers in length had appeared on the ground, with plumes of smoke rising up from within them.

Han Li's group was situated next to the river with close to ten thousand black, wolf-like ghostly beasts littered across the ground.

These ghostly beasts were each around seventy to eighty feet in length, and they possessed thick and muscular bodies that were covered in coarse, black fur.

However, all of them had been split in half, or had had their heads, chests, or other vital regions punctured, and the ground was soaked in their black blood, which possessed very potent corrosive properties, reducing the nearby ground to a charred black state.

Han Li, Weeping Soul, and Shi Chuankong were doing just fine, but the Violet Spirit and Jin Tong were looking a little pale.

These wolf-like ghostly beasts had been quite formidable, and in particular, they were capable of unleashing a type of spiritual attack. Violet Soul and Jin Tong's souls were particularly powerful, so the two of them had struggled more than everyone else in the group.

"Are you two alright?" Han Li asked.

"I'm fine," Jin Tong replied with a forced smile, while Violet Soul also nodded in response.

"According to the scriptures that I've read on the Hundred Ghost Forest, the spiritual attacks unleashed by the bleak souls in the forest are far more formidable than what these ghostly beasts are capable of.

“Right now, we should still be in the outskirts of the forest, and that's why we haven't encountered any bleak souls, but we should be encountering them soon from this point. If it becomes too much for you, then stand down and don't force yourselves," Shi Chuankong said.

Violet Spirit and Jin Tong nodded in response, and the group set off once again.

Han Li approached Violet Spirit as he asked, "How have you been doing Devil Realm, Violet Spirit."

"I've been doing quite well. With Senior Xie and Fellow Daoist Shi taking care of me, I haven't had to worry about anything aside from cultivation," Violet Spirit replied.

"Speaking of cultivation, it's truly remarkable that you were able to make such incredible progress in the less than one thousand years that we've been apart," Han Li said.

"It's all thanks to Senior Xie. He set up a special space in which I was able to progress very quickly in my cultivation, and everything that you left behind for me has also been very beneficial to my cultivation," Violet Spirit explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

As a Dao Ancestor, it was no surprise that Daoist Xie had some tricks up his sleeve to accelerate Violet Spirit's cultivation.

"How is Fellow Daoist Xie? Is he still in the Scalptia Spatial Domain?" Han Li asked.

Violet Spirit was just about to answer when Han Li suddenly stopped in his tracks and raised a hand to stop her.

Shi Chuankong, Weeping Soul, and the others also drew to a halt with solemn looks on their faces.

Violet Spirit hurriedly cast her gaze forward, and she discovered that a layer of deathly white mist had appeared in the forest up ahead.

The cloud of mist was rapidly drifting toward them, and everything in its wake was enshrouded in a layer of frost.

An incredibly menacing aura was emanating from deep within the mist, and Shi Chuankong warned in a wary voice, "It's a bleak soul, and this one is at least a thousand years old, so make sure to be on your guard, everyone!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, the white mist up ahead suddenly began to churn violently, and countless gusts of white yin wind came surging out from within to form a massive, white storm.

The nearby forest was instantly devoured by the storm, and everything within it was pulverized into powder.

The white storm came sweeping toward Han Li's group with unstoppable might, and the sound of shrill, ghastly howls could be heard ringing out from within it.

In the face of this harrowing sound, Shi Chuankong's soul began to ripple uncontrollably, and his devilish qi circulation also began to stagnate involuntarily.

He hurriedly darted back in retreat while doing everything in his power to suppress the unrest in his own soul, and everyone else quickly followed suit, with the exception of Han Li.

He remained standing still on the spot as a layer of golden light surfaced over his body, and he was peering intently into the white storm up ahead with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

"Master!" Weeping Soul called out in an urgent manner as she stopped in her tracks before preparing to return to his side.

Jin Tong hurriedly grabbed onto her arm to stop her as she said, "Hold on a second! Uncle's not a reckless person, so there must be a reason why he's doing this. On top of that, this is only a single bleak soul, so I'm sure Uncle can handle it just fine."

A concerned look had also appeared in Violet Spirit's eyes upon seeing this.

The white storm descended upon Han Li in the blink of an eye before devouring him like a giant mouth.

Han Li remained completely still, and the golden light emanating from his body only grew brighter, forming a radiant barrier against the white storm.

The storm was instantly immobilized several dozen feet away from the golden light, unable to advance any further beyond that point.

All of a sudden, a thunderous roar rang out from deep within the white storm, and a wave of harrowing killing intent swept through the air, causing Shi Chuankong and the others to shudder in an involuntary fashion.

"What a fool! You've doomed yourself now that you've revealed yourself to me!" Han Li harrumphed coldly as he pointed a finger forward, and a streak of golden light erupted out of his fingertip before piercing into the white storm.

The violent, white storm instantly fell still, then exploded into scattered clouds of mist to reveal a giant, white ghostly creature that was over a thousand feet tall, but was incredibly thin, resembling a bamboo pole.

The ghostly creature was wearing a long, white robe that was dragging along behind it, and there was a long tongue hanging out of its mouth.

Tremendous ghostly qi was emanating from the creature's body, and it wasn't even inferior by much compared with Xue Li in this regard.

The streak of golden light had punched a large hole into its chest, and it was looking down at the hole with an incredulous expression, one that was mirrored on the faces of Shi Chuankong and the others.

Han Li raised his arm, and the streak of golden light slashed upward to slice the creature's upper body into two, following which its entire body disintegrated into dense, white smoke that dissipated in all directions.

Chapter 1294: Wrath of the Xing Beast

Right at this moment, a burst of black light descended from the heavens to encompass the entire cloud of white smoke, and the balls of white light were struggling with all their might to break free, but were ultimately powerless to resist and sucked away.

Before long, all of the white smoke and orbs of light had been devoured by the black light, which then rapidly shrank down to form Weeping Soul.

Her aura had swelled drastically, but it was a little unstable.

"Are you alright?" Han Li asked.

"I'm fine. It's just that I've absorbed too much ghostly power at once, and it's filled with violent killing intent, so I'm going to need some time to refine it," Weeping Soul replied, then immediately sat down with her legs crossed.

Shi Chuankong flew over to Han Li's side with a complex mix of envy, admiration, and indignation in his eyes as he sighed, "I thought I had already been able to make very good progress of late, but you continue to leave me far behind, Fellow Daoist Han."

"I've merely been very lucky. Given your aptitude, you'll be sure to surpass me very soon," Han Li said with a faint smile.

Shi Chuankong rolled his eyes and turned his gaze elsewhere, while both Violet Spirit and Jin Tong were staring at Han Li in a stunned silence.

"Why are you two looking at me like that? It's like you've never seen me before," Han Li chuckled.

"I've never seen you like this before," Jin Tong replied with a smile.

"Alright, let's stop fooling around. Weeping Soul is going to need some time to refine the ghostly power of that bleak soul, so we'll have to wait for her for now," Han Li said.

Jin Tong and Violet Spirit nodded in response before sitting down together, and Shi Chuankong also sat down with his legs crossed as he turned to Han Li and said, "With you on our side, we have nothing to fear!"

Right at this moment, Gui Wu's voice suddenly rang out beside Han Li's ears.

"Fellow Daoist Han, can you tell me just how powerful you are right now? I thought I had already given you quite a lofty appraisal, but it appears that I'm still underestimating you."

"I'm not going to answer that. You can think whatever you like," Han Li replied in an indifferent manner, and Gui Wu gave an awkward chuckle before falling silent.

Two days passed by in a flash, and during this time, there were many more ghostly beast attacks, but no more bleak souls appeared.

Weeping Soul's disorderly aura was quickly settling down, and after another day, her eyes abruptly sprang open as he let loose a long cry that sounded like a cross between the call of a phoenix and the roar of a tiger.

Everyone was snapped out of their meditative states as their attention fell upon her, and it was clear from her aura that she had made very significant strides in her cultivation during this short span of time.

Furthermore, a series of black patterns that resembled true spirit bloodline patterns had appeared over her skin, and a blurry, black shadow had also surfaced on her back.

It was unclear what the shadow was, and right as Han Li was pondering the matter, the answer was provided by Gui Wu.

"It looks like she's beginning to awaken the Xing Beast bloodline in her body."

"Is there a tribe of Xing Beasts in the underworld?" Han Li asked in an intrigued manner.

He had known for a long time that Weeping Soul was a Xing Beast, but he had never been able to find out exactly what a Xing Beast was.

"Of course. The Xing Beasts are a very mysterious tribe that resides deep in the underworld and are very rarely sighted, with the Infernal King having been the only exception to this norm. They're vastly renowned across the entire underworld for their extremely formidable innate ability. While it's true that your powers are very impressive, once Weeping Soul fully awakens her Xing Beast bloodline, you may not be able to withstand her innate ability," Gui Wu chuckled.

"Is that so? I'm certainly looking forward to seeing that," Han Li replied.

The long cry ringing out from between Weeping Soul's lips quickly subsided, and she rose to her feet with an apologetic expression as she said, "Sorry to have kept all of you waiting for me for three days."

"There's no need to apologize, Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul, it's only right for companions to look out for one another. I must offer you my congratulations," Shi Chuankong said with a smile, but internally, he was feeling quite glum.

Han Li's powers were far superior to his, and it appeared that Weeping Soul also had his measure.

As for Jin Tong, she hadn't displayed her powers this entire time, but it was clear that she was not to be underestimated, either.

"Let's go, we've already been delayed for quite some time here," Han Li said, and the group continued onward.

In the wake of Han Li's display of power, the group felt sufficiently confident to speed up in their travels, and after a few more days, they had already reached the central region of the Hundred Ghost Forest.

Along the way, they encountered some ghostly beasts that posed virtually no threat, and they also encountered another bleak soul that was slightly weaker than the previous one. Once again, it was slain by Han Li and devoured by Weeping Soul.

Thanks to the immense ghostly qi in the central region of the Hundred Ghost Forest, some spirit plants that were unique to the underworld had begun to appear.

However, collecting spirit plants was not their objective, so they continued onward without pause.

On this day, Weeping Soul found herself locked in battle against another bleak soul near a valley in the Hundred Ghost Forest.

This one was even more powerful than the previous two, and the two were clashing against one another over and over again, with the forces of their collisions creating countless spatial rifts around them.

The nearby forest had already been razed to the ground, while the clouds above had also been torn to shreds.

At this moment, Han Li and others were all passively observing nearby, having been requested by Weeping Soul to take no part in the battle.

"I didn't think that Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul would be able to take care of a bleak soul on her own," Shi Chuankong sighed.

"It's only because her abilities are particularly effective against all ghostly beings that she's able to accomplish such a feat," Han Li replied. "It looks like the battle is about to reach its conclusion..."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the black light up ahead suddenly reared up to dominate the opposing white light, and an indistinct, black shadow appeared within the black light.

The shadow was identical to the one that had appeared on Weeping Soul's back, but had become much clearer than before, and it was now possible to tell that it was a giant, black ape.

A panicked look appeared on the bleak soul's face as it turned to flee, but it was already too late as its head abruptly exploded, and an orb of white light flew out from within before being devoured by the black ape projection, following which the bleak soul's body exploded into ghostly mist that dissipated in all directions.

So this is the Xing Beast's innate ability. It seems to be able to directly strike at the target's soul, Han Li thought to himself.

"Soul Devourer... As expected of the most powerful spiritual attack under the heavens," Gui Wu praised.

Han Li could sense that this Soul Devourer ability of Weeping Soul's posed a potent threat to his own soul, and his brows furrowed slightly at this observation.

With his mastery over the laws of time, he was well equipped to deal with all manners of strange attacks, but spiritual attacks were an exception as they existed outside the realm of law powers.

His soul and spiritual sense were far more powerful than those of his peers, thanks to his mastery of the Spirit Refinement Technique, but it would still be very difficult for him to withstand such an attack from Weeping Soul.

Right at this moment, the black ape projection vanished in a flash, and it seemed that it wasn't able to linger for long.

Immediately thereafter, the black light formed by Weeping Soul transformed into a swirling, black vortex that released tremendous suction force, taking only seconds to devour all of the ghost qi in the air.

The vortex then rapidly shrank down to reform Weeping Soul, and her aura had swelled drastically once again.

Clusters of glowing, black spots appeared over her body, culminating in a total of eight hundred and thirty-nine, which indicated that she was at the pinnacle of the early-Great Encompassment Stage.

At the same time, the same black patterns as last time resurfaced over her body, and they were far clearer than before.

An ecstatic look appeared on Weeping Soul's face upon seeing this.

Han Li and the others flew over to join her, and Jin Tong immediately praised, "That was incredible! What was that black ape projection just now? It took down that bleak soul in an instant!"

"Do you need time to refine the ghostly qi that you've absorbed?" Han Li asked.

"Not this time. For some reason, the backlash from this bleak soul's ghostly power is not that strong, so I can suppress it. Let's not waste any more time," Weeping Soul replied with a shake of her head.

"Could it be because you've begun to awaken your Xing Beast bloodline? In any case, this is certainly a good thing," Han Li mused.

With that, the group continued onward, but they hadn't gone very far before Gui Wu suddenly made an exclamation of surprise and elation.

"What is it?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"You are the luckiest man alive, Fellow Daoist Han! Set off in the ten o'clock direction!" Gui Wu urged.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he did as he was told.

Shi Chuankong and the others were puzzled by this sudden change in direction, but they followed along without asking any questions.

Before long, they arrived at an area under the shadow of a black mountain.

There was a green pond here, and the water inside was giving off incredibly potent yin qi.

Growing beside the pond was a cluster of bamboo trees that were swaying gently in the wind.

"You made such a big fuss just for these bamboo trees?" Han Li asked.

These bamboo trees were very abundant with yin qi, but aside from that, there didn't appear to be anything special about them.

Chapter 1295: Forgetful Bamboo Boat

"You don't know anything! I'll seal away the power of these bamboo trees so that you can unearth them. Trust me, they're going to be very useful," Gui Wu urged, then emerged from the Soul Locking Box before opening his mouth to release a cloud of gray mist that encompassed the entire cluster of bamboo trees.

The cloud of mist quickly seeped into the bamboo trees, upon which a series of gray patterns immediately appeared over their surface.

Han Li immediately swept both sleeves through the air upon seeing this, and two bursts of crescent-shaped golden light flew out of the palms of his hands before digging up the bamboo trees and the surrounding soil before stowing them away into his Flower Branch domain.

"Sorry about that. These bamboo trees are quite useful to me, so I decided to take a detour," Han Li said to Shi Chuankong and the others.

"It's fine," Shi Chuankong said with a wave of his hand. "Who is this?"

"This is Fellow Daoist Gui Wu, a soul fragment that I encountered and saved earlier in the underworld," Han Li replied, refraining from revealing Gui Wu's identity.

"I see. It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu," Shi Chuankong said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Gui Wu took a glance at him, then nodded in response before flying back into the Soul Locking Box, and the group set off once again.

With Han Li and Weeping Soul on their side, the rest of the journey through the Hundred Ghost Forest went by very smoothly, and they finally emerged from the forest after over a month of travel, arriving on a boundless, gray plain.

"How far away are we from the Yellow Springs?" Han Li asked.

"We're already there. You should be able to see a red area up ahead, that's where the Yellow Springs are," Gui Wu replied.

Sure enough, on the distant horizon was an area that was enshrouded in what appeared to have been a cloud of red vapor.

He immediately set off in that direction, followed closely by Violet Spirit and the others.

There was an indescribable smell in the air here that struck one with a sense of asphyxiation, and the closer they drew to the red area, the more pronounced this feeling of asphyxiation became.

Before long, the group arrived at an enormous lake that was almost comparable in size to an ocean.

It stretched as far as the eyes could see, and the surface of the water near the shore was as smooth as a mirror, with not even the slightest ripple to be seen.

In the sky above the central region of the lake was a dense blanket of crimson clouds, which was connected to the chaotic cloud of vapor down below to form a huge area in which visibility was severely hampered.

The sky to the north of the lake looked as if it had been torn open by something, and a crimson waterfall was pouring out of the gash, forming a red ribbon that trailed down from the heavens.

The waterfall appeared to have been crashing down with tremendous force, but it fell onto the lake with no more impact than a feather, presenting a very strange sight to behold.

Constructed along the bank of the lake at set intervals were stone dark red, stone forts that were each over a thousand feet tall, and there were giant banners that bore different totems hanging from them.

"This is where the four major tribes are stationed," Gui Wu declared, and Han Li immediately released his spiritual sense toward the stone forts.

After a brief inspection, he turned to everyone else and declared, "They're all empty."

"You see? Do you believe me now?" Gui Wu asked.

"The absence of the four major tribes will spare us of a great deal of trouble. Where is the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate right now?" Han Li asked.

Gui Wu rose up from the pouch hanging from his waist like a plume of smoke, then pointed toward the center of the lake as he replied, "It's right there?"

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this, and he asked, "Didn't you tell me that the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate is situated on the bank of the Yellow Springs? Why is it in the center all of a sudden?"

"I... I was worried that you wouldn't dare to go if I told you that it was the center of the Yellow Springs," Gui Wu replied in a sheepish and fearful manner.

Han Li had no idea what kind of place the Yellow Springs were supposed to be, nor was he aware of the dangers that it harbored, so even if Gui Wu had revealed the truth, he wouldn't have backed down anyway.

"Does this mean that the Yellow Springs are a dangerous place?" Han Li asked.

"Allow me to explain," Gui Wu said. "Littered throughout the bottom of this lake are soul-devouring springs that can suck in the souls of the living. Once one's soul is sucked into one of these springs, it will fall into the cycle of reincarnation, while their physical body is left to slowly rot on the lakebed and become one with the lake."

"Then can't we just fly over the lake to avoid such a fate?" Jin Tong asked.

"Indeed, as long as you don't come into contact with the water in the lake, you won't be sucked into the soul-devouring springs. However, the problem lies in those crimson clouds above the lake," Gui Wu replied.

"What about them?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"The clouds themselves pose no threat, but the wind blowing out of them is an entirely different story," Gui Wu replied.

"Hurry up and get to the point!" Jin Tong snapped in a disgruntled manner.

"I was getting there. The wind blowing out of the crimson clouds are none other than Six Paths Gale winds, and they're not very strong at the moment, so it's almost impossible to see them. However, they're present over the entire lake, and if one is swept up within them, then their flesh will be stripped away in a matter of seconds, and that applies even to Great Encompassment cultivators," Gui Wu explained.

"What's even worse is that the Six Paths Gale will blow you into the water below, at which point your soul will be forcibly cast into the cycle of reincarnation," Han Li added with tightly furrowed brows.

"Can't we just travel over the lake by boat? As long as we take care to avoid the Six Paths Gale winds, we should be able to reach the center of the lake without too much trouble," Weeping Soul said.

"That's not going to work. The water in this lake cannot even support the weight of a single feather or leaf, so nothing will be able to make it across the lake without sinking in the process," Gui Wu cautioned.

Jin Tong flipped a hand over to produce a handful of white fur upon hearing this.

The fur belonged to Xiaobai, but it was unclear when she had plucked it from his body.

She blew onto the handful of fur to send it drifting down onto the surface of the lake, and sure enough, it didn't take long before the strands of fur sank into the water, much to her disappointment.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but a thought then suddenly occurred to him, and he swept a sleeve through the air to summon the bamboo trees that he had uprooted earlier before asking, "You asked me to gather this bamboo because it can be used to cross the lake, right?"

"Indeed! You are truly as sharp as a knife, Fellow Daoist Han! To my knowledge, the only thing capable of floating on the surface of this lake is Forgetful Bamboo. Hence, we must fashion a boat out of this bamboo in order to cross the lake," Gui Wu replied with a nod.

Han Li tossed a length of bamboo through the air, and it fell onto the surface of the lake in complete silence and without even the slightest splash.

The length of bamboo bobbled up and down momentarily, then began to float in a still and stable fashion on the surface of the lake.

"Alright, now that we have the materials required to cross the lake by boat, what do we do about the Six Paths Gale winds?" Han Li asked.

"It appears as if the entire surface of the lake is completely enshrouded in Six Paths Gale winds, but after several hundred thousand years of past observation, I discovered that there's actually an obscure channel within them. All we need to do is guide the boat through the channel, and we'll be able to avoid the Six Paths Gale winds and reach the other side," Gui Wu revealed.

Han Li immediately flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip, then tossed it at Gui Wu as he instructed, "Use your spiritual sense to create a map of the Six Paths Gale winds over this lake, and mark out the channel that you're referring to."

Gui Wu caught the jade slip with a slightly awkward look on his face, then gave a sheepish smile before closing his eyes and doing as Han Li instructed.

Meanwhile, everyone else began laying out the Forgetful Bamboo trees in preparation to craft the boat required to cross the lake.

"I presume this channel isn't going to be very wide, and there's also not enough bamboo here to craft a large boat. Hence, I suggest we use them to craft two small boats, each of which only needs to be large enough to carry one person. I'll travel on one of the boats on my own, while all of you can stay in my domain treasure, and the other boat will be kept as backup in case of unforeseen mishaps," Han Li proposed.

"As usual, you always have everything so well thought out, Fellow Daoist Han," Shi Chuankong praised.

Jin Tong and Weeping Soul exchanged a smile with each other, seemingly feeling very proud on behalf of their master, while Violet Spirit was also gazing upon Han Li with a faint smile on her face.

Before long, a pair of small, bamboo boats that were around thirty feet in length and six feet wide had been constructed, and the map of the Six Paths Gale winds over the lake was also ready.

Chapter 1296: Ghostly Palace

"The lake is too vast, so the map that I've created only encompasses an area in a radius of several hundred kilometers of our current location," Gui Wu said in a slightly feeble voice, and it seemed that he had overexerted his soul power.

Weeping Soul extended a hand toward the Soul Locking Box upon seeing this, enveloping it in a burst of red light, and only did Gui Wu's condition improve slightly, upon which he extended some words of gratitude to Weeping Soul.

After examining the contents of the jade slip for a moment, Han Li cast his gaze forward as he activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

The Six Paths Gale winds were virtually invisible to the naked eye, but Han Li was able to see them as clear as day with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

The winds closer to shore were smaller and more difficult to discern, while the winds near the center of the lake were far more formidable and pronounced, and they were particularly powerful directly beneath the crimson clouds.

Just as Gui Wu had said, the distribution of Six Paths Gale winds over the lake was extremely chaotic, with no patterns to be found, nor was he able to see the channel that Gui Wu had mentioned.

"Fellow Daoist Gui Wu, the distribution of Six Paths Gale winds here seems to be different from what's presented on your map," Han Li remarked with slightly furrowed brows.

"The Six Paths Gale winds here are constantly changing, and my map only depicts the state of the Six Paths Gale winds when the channel is present. Once the winds here match what's shown on my map, the channel will appear," Gui Wu explained.

"How long will we have to wait?" Han Li asked.

"Judging from the state of the crimson clouds above the center of the lake, we shouldn't have to wait too long. If we're lucky, perhaps a month, but definitely no longer than a year," Gui Wu replied.

"In that case, let's wait," Han Li decided, and with that, the group temporarily settled in one of the stone forts beside the lake.

Over half a year flew by in a flash.

On this day, the Six Paths Gale winds over the lake were more ferocious than ever, and the giant gusts of wind that had originally been confined to the center of the lake had spread over almost the entirety of its surface, reaching no more than several dozen kilometers away from shore.

"This is it! We have to go now!" Gui Wu exclaimed in an urgent and ecstatic manner.

"Now? Are you kidding me? The conditions are clearly worse than ever!" Shi Chuankong exclaimed, and everyone else was also looking at Gui Wu with apprehensive and skeptical expressions.

"These are precisely the right conditions," Gui Wu insisted. "The smaller the Six Paths Gale winds are, the more pervasive they are. Right now, many of the smaller gusts of wind have combined to create larger gusts, but they've also become more spaced out as a result, and only then will the hidden channel appear."

Han Li carefully inspected the conditions with his Infernal Devilish Eyes, and sure enough, the current distribution of Six Paths Gale winds over the lake was identical to what was presented in Gui Wu's map.

"I can see the entrance of the channel," Han Li declared.

"We have to make haste, fellow daoists! At the very most, these conditions will only last for several hours, so we can't afford any delay," Gui Wu urged.

"Weeping Soul and I will cross the lake by boat with Fellow Daoist Gui Wu, while all of you can stay in my domain treasure, and we'll reconvene once we reach our destination," Han Li said.

No one raised any objections to this, so Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light, and everyone quickly filed into the Flower Branch domain through it.

Violet Spirit was the last one to step through, and right before she did, she turned back to take a glance at Han Li as she cautioned, "Be careful."

Han Li gave her a smile and a reassuring nod, and after closing the door of silver light, he turned to Weeping Soul as he said, "Let's set off."

He then switched to voice transmission as he continued, "I'll steer the boat, while you keep an eye on our surroundings and on Gui Wu. If he tries anything funny, kill him right away. I have a way to get us out of here if anything goes wrong, so we won't be stranded even without him to guide us."

Now that he had reached the pinnacle of the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, he was feeling a lot more confident.

Weeping Soul raised no objections to this arrangement, and Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to summon one of the bamboo boats that was crafted earlier.

Upon landing on the surface of the lake, the boat bobbled up and down ever so slightly before stabilizing itself, and Han Li and Weeping Soul quickly leaped onto it.

"We're about to set off, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu. If there's anything that I need to take note of along the way, make sure to notify me in a timely fashion," Han Li said.

Gui Wu emerged from the Soul Locking Box with a smile as he said, "Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Han. We are in the same boat right now, both literally and figuratively, so I'll be sure to do everything in my power to help you."

Han Li nodded in response, then swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a fierce gust of wind, sending the boat racing over the surface of the lake like a speeding arrow.

The boat traveled extremely quickly, and it seemed to have been gliding over the surface of the lake in a completely frictionless manner, heading directly toward a cluster of Six Paths Gale winds.

Han Li hurriedly summoned a bamboo pole upon seeing this, then plunged it into the lake to forcibly alter the trajectory of the bamboo boat so that it just barely glanced past the cluster of Six Paths Gale winds.

"Be careful!" Gui Wu yelled in an alarmed manner.

Han Li slowed down the boat slightly, after passing through a narrow path between two gusts of Six Paths Gale winds, it officially entered the hidden channel.

Initially, the going proved to be quite smooth, but as they continued onward, the Six Paths Gale winds became stronger and stronger, making it very difficult to control the bamboo boat.

Hence, Han Li was forced to focus solely on steering the boat while relying on Gui Wu for navigation.

After steering the boat to the left past a giant cluster of Six Paths Gale winds, they arrived before an enormous wall of red clouds that completely blocked the way forward.

Han Li hurriedly plunged the bamboo pole vertically into the water to stop the boat cold in its tracks.

"What's going on here?" he asked, but Gui Wu was also looking completely incredulous.

"This is impossible! There's supposed to be a way through here!" Gui Wu exclaimed in a frustrated manner, while Weeping Soul was standing behind him with a hostile expression, prepared to strike at a moment's notice.

Han Li could see that he didn't appear to have been putting on an act, and a perplexed look appeared on his face. Could it be that some type of unexpected change really had arisen?

Right at this moment, something caught his attention, and he cast his Infernal Devilish Eyes toward the wall of crimson clouds up ahead with an intrigued expression.

"Have you discovered something, Fellow Daoist Han?" Gui Wu hurriedly asked.

"The channel is still there, it's just been concealed by this cloud," Han Li replied.

Gui Wu hurriedly cast his gaze toward the base of the wall of clouds up ahead, and sure enough, it was nowhere near as dense and thick as the crimson clouds elsewhere.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li steered the boat forward once again, and it plunged headfirst into the wall of clouds.

Inside the cloud, it was impossible to see anything, and even breathing had become a very difficult task, but it only took an instant for the boat to emerge on the other side, much to Gui Wu's elation.

Han Li quickly inspected the surrounding area to discover that the channel was lined by two walls of crimson clouds on either side, and these clouds had been dragged down from the heavens by the surrounding Six Paths Gale winds.

At the moment, it was as if they were traversing through a canyon between a pair of cliff faces, and extra vigilance had to be exercised.

"You can relax a little for now, Fellow Daoist Han. Now that we're in the Safe Passage Channel, things should go much smoother for a good portion of the journey ahead," Gui Wu said in a relieved manner.

"What is this Safe Passage Channel?" Han Li asked.

"I named it myself on a whim. It's more so for good luck than anything else," Gui Wu replied.

......

Meanwhile, at the center of the Yellow Springs was a vast, isolated area that was completely surrounded by a circular wall of incredibly dense crimson clouds.

The area itself was completely serene and tranquil, with no more Six Paths Gale winds present, and at its center sat an island that resembled the shape of a wagon wheel.

There were six mountain ridges on the island that were pointed at its center from different directions, looking much like the spokes of a wagon wheel from above.

Even though the entire island was devoid of vegetation, it didn't appear bleak or desolate at all as it was riddled with structures like stone staircases and simple pavilions.

At the center of the island stood a majestic, stone palace constructed from giant blocks of gray stone, and the palace was surrounded by a series of flat and level plazas of different shapes and sizes, all of which were being patrolled by ghostly guards.

Chapter 1297: Reincarnation

In front of the main entrance of the palace was a large horde of ghostly guards, led by a pair of extremely physically imposing ghostly generals.

One of them possessed a human body, but an enormous and sinister-looking cow's head, and he was clad in a suit of black, metal armor while wielding an iron staff, half of which was red, while the other half was blue.

His companion also possessed a human body, but a long and hideous horse's face. He was clad in a suit of bright red armor, and in his hands were a crystalline, red chain and a skin-peeling ghostly claw with some specks of dried blood on its surface.

The two of them were standing in a completely still, statuesque manner outside the palace, giving it an even more eerie and forbidding appearance.

There was no plaque hanging above the entrance of the palace, and its gates were also currently tightly shut.

Deep in the ground beneath the palace was a massive, underground space that was brightly illuminated by a large number of lit braziers, and at its center was a hexagonal, stone platform that was over ten thousand feet in size and around three feet tall.

Its surface was as smooth as a mirror, and at its center was a hexagonal pond that was filled with some type of dark red liquid.

Hovering directly above the pond was a ball of dark red light, within which was a massive, hexagonal plate that was riddled with complex patterns, and it was giving off bursts of peculiar energy fluctuations and a unique aura that signaled an integral connection between the plate and the entirety of heaven and earth.

Standing on the edge of the pond beneath the hexagonal plate was a tall, black-robed man whose face was completely concealed within a veiled, conical bamboo hat.

The man's aura was completely restrained, but he had a mountainous presence that dwarfed even that of the hexagonal plate.

At this moment, the man's head slightly lowered, and he seemed to have been lost in thought.

All of a sudden, the sound of footsteps rang out from afar, and two women approached the stone platform.

One of them was none other than Wyrm 3, and she was accompanied by the woman referred to as Rushuang by the cultivators of the Reincarnation Palace.

Rushuang was identical in appearance and disposition to Nangong Wan, and the reality was that she really was Nangong Wan.

Wyrm 3 was holding gently onto Rushuang's arm, and the latter's skin was slightly cold to the touch, presenting a stark contrast with the feverishly hot palm of Wyrm 3's hand.

At this moment, Wyrm 3's mind was a complete mess, and she couldn't help but sneak the occasional glance at Rushuang as they walked alongside one another.

After learning that Rushuang was her mother, Wyrm 3 found herself unable to regard her in the same way that she had in the past. However, Rushuang seemed to have been oblivious to her gaze as she strode calmly toward the center of the stone platform.

"Palace Master," Wyrm 3 greeted as she extended a curtsey upon arriving at the edge of the hexagonal pond, and Rushuang did the same.

"You can go in now," the Reincarnation Palace Master said as he turned to face them, and Wyrm 3 latched onto Rushuang's hand before guiding her to the edge of the pond.

Rushuang took a hesitant glance at Wyrm 3, and the latter gave her an encouraging smile while gesturing for her to enter the pond.

Rushuang lifted up the hem of her dress, then made her way down the steps on the edge of the pond toward its center.

The water in the pond wasn't too deep, and it was only chest-high at the center.

She had only just reached the center of the pond and was about to turn around to look back at Wyrm 3 when she suddenly fell back in an unconscious state.

She floated on the surface of the pond on her back, and Wyrm 3 wasn't surprised to see this, as if she had already been informed that this would happen.

"Why did you ask me to bring my mother here, Palace Master? And why does she have no recollection of me?" Wyrm 3 asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"Your mother has already passed through the cycle of reincarnation, so she naturally has no memory of you," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"What does that mean?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"What I'm saying is that she was your mother in her past life. Her name was Gan Rushuang, and in this life, her name is Nangong Wan. In order for her to remember you, we have to help her recover her memories from her past life," the Reincarnation Palace Master explained.

"Gan Rushuang... Did I take after my mother's surname?" Wyrm 3 asked.

Countless questions had sprung into her mind at once.

How did my mother die in her previous life? Where is my father? Is this still my mother if she's already gone through the cycle of reincarnation?

Ultimately, she chose one of those countless questions to ask: "Why don't I remember my mother, either?"

"Your mother died on the same day as you were born, so you only ever got to see her once," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"Did my mother die because of me?" Wyrm 3 asked as the color drained from her face.

"No," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"But..."

"You're asking too many questions, Jiuzhen!" the Reincarnation Palace Master snapped. "Save your questions until after she recovers her memories."

Wyrm 3 fell silent upon hearing this, while the Reincarnation Palace Master made a hand seal and began chanting an incantation.

His robes began to billow around him despite the absence of wind, and dark red law power fluctuations surged out of his body as he pointed a finger at the hexagonal plate above, releasing a pillar of red light into it.

The hexagonal plate immediately began to revolve, and as time passed, it only sped up in its revolution.

The red light around it also began to revolve, and a beam of red light came shining down upon Nangong Wan.

Her brows furrowed slightly in her unconscious state, and her eyeballs began to roll around erratically beneath her eyelids, as if she had been cast into a chaotic dream.

However, it didn't take long before she fell completely still again, and she slowly sank down to the bottom of the pond.

......

In the Yellow Springs, Han Li's group had already emerged from the canyon of crimson clouds.

"Once we emerge from this area, we won't be far away from the center of the lake," Gui Wu said, and Han Li nodded in response.

The journey had been quite smooth thus far, indicating that this channel pointed out by Gui Wu was indeed a safe route.

Around an hour later, the boat suddenly emerged into an open area that was completely devoid of crimson clouds and Six Paths Gale winds.

"Why is there a calm zone here?" Gui Wu exclaimed.

"Isn't this a good thing?" Weeping Soul asked.

"Not necessarily. The fact that there's a calm zone here indicates that there's been a change in our projected route, which means that the channel up ahead could be blocked. If that's the case, then we'll be trapped here," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

Right at this moment, he suddenly cast his gaze toward the wall of crimson clouds on the other side, and the wall had suddenly begun moving into the calm zone.

Immediately thereafter, an enormous shadow appeared behind it, and a peculiar look appeared on Weeping Soul's face upon seeing this.

A gargantuan, black beast that resembled a snapping turtle had emerged on the horizon between the Yellow Springs and the crimson clouds above.

The creature had four enormous flippers that were stirring up black whirlwinds, providing it with the buoyancy that it required to keep its body aloft in mid-air.

"How is this thing unaffected by the Six Paths Gale winds?" Weeping Soul exclaimed.

Gui Wu was even more astonished than Weeping Soul was.

"This is impossible! These Floating Underworld Turtles went extinct several hundred thousand years ago!"

"There are people on its back," Han Li said, and sure enough, there was a group of seven or eight figures standing atop the creature.

The group was led by a white skeleton that was dressed in a gray robe, and standing behind the skeleton was none other than Xue Li.

There were several more people standing behind Xue Li, one of whom was Yin Luo, the leader of the ghostly army that had pursued Han Li's group earlier.

At this point, the group had noticed Han Li as well, and a hint of killing intent flashed through Xue Li's eyes as he sprang up into the air before swinging his ax down upon Han Li.

Chapter 1298: Bone Emperor

"Xue Li, stop!" Gui Wu yelled, but it was already too late.

A crimson ax projection that was tens of thousands of feet in length came crashing down from the heavens with almighty power, slicing open numerous giant spatial rifts as it descended upon Han Li.

Han Li remained completely unfazed, and he didn't even bother to spare a glance at Xue Li as he casually swept a sleeve through the air, conjuring a shimmering, golden palm projection to oppose the ax projection.

His gaze had been focused on the white skeleton this entire time as its aura was the only one that he was unable to glean out of the group of figures standing atop the giant turtle.

The palm projection was no more than ten feet in size, and it was made to appear utterly diminutive in the face of the mountainous ax projection.

However, the ax projection instantly shattered violently upon contact, while the palm projection remained unscathed and continued to ascend into the heavens, quickly vanishing into the distant sky as a speck of golden light.

An astonished look appeared in Xue Li's eyes as he stared after the golden palm projection that was racing away into the distance.

The white skeleton also took a glance in the same direction, then directed its gaze toward Han Li.

"What the hell is wrong with you, Xue Li? Can't you see that the Infernal King and I are on this boat?" Gui Wu yelled in a furious manner.

"Gui Wu, is that you? I thought you were dead!" Xue Li exclaimed.

Gui Wu paid no heed to him as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute, then extended a deep bow toward the white skeleton from afar.

"Junior Gui Wu pays his respects to Senior Bone Emperor."

Bone Emperor nodded in response, then asked, "What are you doing with these cultivators from the True Immortal Realm?"

His voice had an ethereal quality to it, like countless voices layered on top of one another, making it impossible to tell where it was coming from.

"We are here to hunt down the Reincarnation King," Gui Wu hurriedly replied. "I presume that you must be here for the same purpose, Senior Bone Emperor. If that's the case, then please allow us to join you."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this. He had never agreed to go after the Reincarnation King with Gui Wu. Instead, he had only come here for the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate.

However, he didn't dare to raise any objections in the presence of this Bone Emperor, seeing as he was clearly someone that was very much feared and respected even by Gui Wu and Xue Li.

"In that case, I'm willing to set our past differences aside," Xue Li said. "What do you think, Senior Bone Emperor?"

"It makes no difference to me," Bone Emperor replied in a nonchalant manner.

Clearly, Han Li and the others were nothing in his eyes.

"I don't recall this being in the terms of our agreement, Fellow Daoist Gui Wu," Han Li said in a cold voice through voice transmission.

"Think about it this way, Fellow Daoist Han. The Six Paths Reincarnation Plate is in the possession of the Reincarnation King, so if we want to claim it for ourselves, then a battle against him is entirely unavoidable. I guarantee you that you'll be able to use the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate as long as we can defeat the Reincarnation King," Gui Wu urged.

Han Li weighed up his options for a moment, and he ultimately decided that he still wanted no part in this.

He had no intention of getting involved in the conflicts of the underworld, particularly when he knew next to nothing about the people that he was going to be working with.

However, before he had a chance to respond, Gui Wu continued, "Senior Bone Emperor is a true Dao Ancestor, and he won't hesitate to kill anyone that he doesn't like the look of, so do not go against him. I'm making this proposal for your own safety. In a way, this is a positive development. With Senior Bone Emperor on our side, the Reincarnation King won't pose any threat to us!"

"I think it's best to avoid a conflict here, Master," Weeping Soul chimed in through voice transmission.

After a brief silence, Han Li finally nodded in agreement, and Gui Wu was ecstatic to see this.

With that, they stowed the bamboo boat away, then flew onto the giant turtle's back to travel to the center of the lake with Xue Li and the others.

Before long, the group arrived near the island at the center of the lake, but they were stopped in their tracks by the wall of crimson clouds around the island.

"Allow me, Master Bone Emperor," a dark-skinned man said as he stepped forward from behind Bone Emperor.

Outside of Xue Li, the other six members of Bone Emperor's entourage were all also at the Great Encompassment Stage, with the dark-skinned man possessing the loftiest cultivation base at the pinnacle of the mid-Great Encompassment Stage.

Among the remaining five cultivators, there was a wraith-like black-robed figure who was also at the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, while the rest were all at the early-Great Encompassment Stage.

Bone Emperor raised no objections, so the dark-skinned man brought his hands together in front of himself to form a profound seal.

A giant, black projection with two heads and four arms emerged behind the man, and it quickly took on a substantial form, transforming into a massive ghostly entity clad in a suit of black armor.

Its armor was riddled with complex patterns and encompassed the entity's entire body. Even its two heads were obscured, so it's true appearance was concealed, but it was giving off a tremendous aura that was even more powerful than that of the dark-skinned man himself.

The ghostly entity threw its head to the heavens and let loose a thunderous roar, upon which a storm of black light erupted out of its body to force back the nearby gusts of Six Paths Gale winds.

Violet Spirit was almost blown away by the storm, but she was steadied by Han Li's firm hand.

"Thank you, Brother Han," she said, and Han Li waved a hand in response before giving a slight shake of his head at the sight of the attack unleashed by the ghostly entity.

Sure enough, the storm of black light was only able to raise some faint ripples over the wall of crimson clouds, but aside from that, the wall remained completely unmoved.

A stunned look appeared on the dark-skinned man's face upon seeing this, and right at this moment, around a dozen thick bolts of crimson lightning shot out of the wall of clouds without any warning.

The bolts of lightning pierced through the armorclad ghostly entity's armor and body with ease, and it let loose an agonized wail before disintegrating into a cloud of black smoke.

The dark-skinned man shuddered violently, and he stumbled back close to twenty steps before falling to one knee and throwing up a mouthful of blood.

"Useless!" Bone Emperor harrumphed coldly, and the dark-skinned man hurriedly began kowtowing for mercy.

At the same time, he was kicking himself for his failed attempt at currying favor with his master.

"This is a barrier formed by Six Paths Gale winds manipulated by the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate, so you never had any chance against it," Bone Emperor harrumphed coldly, then raised a hand before making a grabbing motion.

A gargantuan, bone claw appeared out of thin air, then grabbed down onto the wall of clouds, and where the dark-skinned man had failed catastrophically, Bone Emperor succeeded with ease, tearing a huge hole into the wall as if it were nothing more than a papier-mache structure.

"Your power is truly unmatched, Senior Bone Emperor!" Xue Li praised.

"The Reincarnation King's luck has finally run out!" Gui Wu chortled with glee.

He was well aware of the Reincarnation King's power, so he had been a little concerned, but his concerns had been completely put to rest by this display of power from Bone Emperor.

At the same time, Han Li was also looking at Bone Emperor with a hint of wariness in his eyes.

He had witnessed Dao Ancestors in action on several past occasions, but on all of those occasions, he possessed nowhere near the cultivation base required to truly comprehend the might of Dao Ancestors, and only now was he truly able to understand what he was witnessing.

Bone Emperor was able to call upon the power of the Great Dao of heaven and earth with every single one of his movements, and this almighty power was truly not something that a Great Encompassment cultivator could hope to oppose.

A pleased look flashed through Bone Emperor's eyes upon hearing Xue Li and Gui Wu's praise, and the giant turtle flew into the hole in the wall of crimson clouds at his behest.

"Who goes there?"

The guards on the island immediately gathered to oppose Bone Emperor and his entourage, and at the same time, the alarm had been raised to gather all of the other guards elsewhere on the island.

"Leave them to me," Xue Li roared as he lashed out with his giant ax, and dozens of ghostly guards were instantly sliced into two, while the seven ghostly cultivators behind Bone Emperor also sprang into action.

Han Li and Weeping Soul couldn't just stand by and watch, so they entered the fray as well.

All of the ghostly guards on the island were very powerful, and even though there were no Great Encompassment cultivators among them, there was certainly no lack of High Zenith cultivators. Furthermore, they were present in huge numbers, so even though Han Li and the others had gained a firm upper hand, they were unable to immediately overwhelm their adversaries.

"Get back!" Bone Emperor snapped in a disgruntled manner, and a burst of white light erupted out of his body, instantly sweeping over the entire island.

The bodies of the ghostly guards on the island that came into contact with the white light were instantly torn open as their skeletons emerged from within on their own before exploding violently.

Explosions rang out incessantly over the entire island as appendages were sent flying in all directions, presenting an extremely gruesome sight to behold.

Almost all of the guards on the island were instantly eradicated, with only a small number of them near the gray palace surviving the ordeal.

At this moment, the entire stone palace was encompassed within a hemispherical, dark red light barrier.

The two statuesque ghostly generals standing at the entrance of the stone palace finally began to move, commanding the remaining ghostly guards to defend the entrance while sending people inside to report the intrusion.

Chapter 1299: Heavenly Secrets

There was a strange continent called the Heavenly Prayer Continent in the Middle Earth Immortal Region.

The local cultivators of the continent didn't spend their time cultivating or refining pills and treasures. Instead, everyone was enamored with the art of divination.

Through their divination, they gleaned the fates of others, predicting the course of their Great Dao and the future heights that they could potentially reach.

In the mortal world, divination had been used to find those who were blessed with a regal destiny, and those people could be supported into fulfilling their destiny of founding mortal empires, thereby granting their backers tremendous profits.

As for those in the cultivation world, they used divination to find bright prospects with an aptitude for cultivation, and some who were particularly skilled in this art were even able to take a child that hadn't yet begun cultivating and glean the heights that they would ultimately be able to reach. Equipped with this skill, these people helped immortal sects search for cultivation prodigies in exchange for handsome compensation.

The prosperity of the Heavenly Prayer Continent could be in large part attributed to the largest sect on the continent, a sect by the name of the Heavenmend Sect.

Just this one sect alone presided over half of the Heavenly Prayer Continent, and the sect had been in existence for countless years, with countless disciples under its prestigious manner.

It was no exaggeration to say that all of the divination techniques under the heavens could have their origins traced back to this sect.

Additionally, the Heavenmend Sect also had a secret technique that involved using quintessential divine rocks to refine various objects with clairvoyant abilities, the most renowned of which was the Chaotic Myriad Spirit Roll, an object that was able to predict the emergence of Profound Heavenly Treasures. [1]

Before the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword first appeared in the Spirit Realm, the Chaotic Myriad Spirit Roll had already displayed a premonition and even pointed out the area in which the Profound Heavenly Treasure was set to emerge.

Whenever cultivators of the Heavenmend Sect left their sect to travel the world, they often concealed their own identities, or posed as cultivators of other sect to avoid the attention of those who wished to force them to use their powers of clairvoyance against their will.

The sect was situated in the eastern region of the Heavenly Prayer Continent, and it encompassed the Resting Dragon, Heavenly Cycle, and Hundred Aid Mountain Ranges. Of those three, the Resting Dragon Mountain Range was the main foundation of the sect.

The Heavenmend Sect had been situated in the Resting Dragon Mountain Range back when it was first founded, and its main peak, the Rising Dragon Peak, had since become a restricted area of the sect, one that was accessible only to the sect leader and several grand elders.

The Heavenly Inquiry Peak that neighbored the Rising Dragon Peak was where the sect's core disciples cultivated, and the mountain was littered with heavenly observation altars for disciples to observe the heavens from.

At this moment, there were several Heavenmend Sect disciples standing behind an authoritative-looking elderly man on an altar that extended out of the mountain, and one of them, a demonic disciple with the body of a human and the head of a goat, cupped his fist in a salute as he asked, "We are about to travel to the immortal regions for our training. Do you have any instructions for us, Elder Fu Feng?"

"Once you reach the immortal regions, you'll most likely be assigned with the task of manning the Ascension Platforms. Remember not to take any ascended cultivator lightly. All of them must possess certain extraordinary traits to have allowed them to ascend from their respective lower realms," Elder Fu Feng said.

"We'll be sure to keep that in mind, Elder Fu Feng," the disciples answered in unison.

"Also, when it comes to cultivators who have ascended from those legendary lost realms, do not perform divination on them lightly. If you can befriend them, then do so, but if you can't, then make sure to completely sever all karmic ties with them," Elder Fu Feng continued.

The disciples were a little perplexed to hear this, but they all gave affirmative responses, nevertheless.

Following their departure, a reminiscent look appeared in Elder Fu Feng's eyes as he cast his gaze into the distance and murmured to himself, "I wonder how high he's ascended right now."

Many years ago, he had met an ascended cultivator from a lost realm while serving at an Ascension Platform in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region under the alias of Gao Sheng from the Stone Ditch Palace.

At the time, his curiosity had driven him to use his divination techniques on the ascended cultivator, and even though he was only able to glean fragmented glimpses of the latter's future, that was enough to alter his image from that of a handsome young man to his current elderly appearance, and no rejuvenation techniques were able to reverse the transformation.

Hence, during the attack on the ascended cultivator, he had slipped away after faking his own death to sever all karmic ties before returning to the Heavenmend Sect.

Since then, he hadn't left the Middle Earth Immortal Region even once, nor had he had told anyone about what had happened back then.

To this day, the outcome of that bout of divination continued to weigh heavily on his mind, and it was something that he still thought about quite regularly.

Right at this moment, his expression suddenly changed slightly as he cast his gaze toward the Rising Dragon Peak, where a swirling cloud vortex had suddenly descended upon its summit from the heavens above.

For some reason, the protective array that encompassed the entire mountain failed to activate.

Fu Feng then cast his gaze toward a palace at the foot of the mountain to discover that the grand elder inside hadn't raised the alarm, and a peculiar look appeared on his face, but he knew not to pry into such matters.

......

The entire summit of the Rising Dragon Peak was enshrouded in a cloud of dense mist, within which a lush forest of peach trees could be seen.

At the center of the forest was an octagonal, black, stone altar that was no more than thirty feet in size, and each side of the altar bore an engraving of the eight trigrams.

At the center of the altar was a black vortex that seemed to have been giving off boundless suction force, and within the vortex was an elderly man with a set of twisted facial features.

Almost his entire body had been devoured by the black vortex, leaving only his head, one of his arms, and his neck exposed.

The man had a head of disheveled, white hair, and one of his eyes was completely white, clearly indicating that it was blind. On top of that, his entire face was riddled with patches of dark brown discoloration, giving him a very hideous appearance.

His other eye wasn't blind, but at this moment, it was half-closed in a weary manner, and it seemed as if he was standing on death's door.

Right at this moment, the vortex of clouds descended silently beside the altar, and a figure emerged from within it.

It was a tall and fair-skinned man with a pair of long and thin eyes. His nose wasn't particularly pronounced, and he had a pair of very thin lips. Overall, there was an air of grace and serenity about him, but he was seated on a white jade wheelchair.

He was dressed in a long, white robe, and there was a golden belt around his waist, hanging from which was a nine dragon jade pendant and a golden tassel.

As soon as he appeared, the elderly man's eye immediately sprang wide open to reveal a burst of radiant, golden light within, and he said in a hoarse voice, "You've finally come..."

"Indeed," the man on the wheelchair replied in a calm manner.

"I suppose you were always bound to come," the elderly man said with a wry smile. "What do you want from me this time?"

"I want you to carry out divination for me, Chen Tuan," the wheelchair-bound man replied.

The man that was almost fully submerged in the black vortex was none other than the founder of the Heavenmend Sect, Patriarch Chen Tuan. Who could've imagined that this hideous elderly man that was on the verge of being devoured by the Heavenly Dao would be the vastly renowned Clairvoyance Dao Ancestor of the Heavenly Court?

"I promised you thirty-six heavenly divinations and seventy-two earthly divinations. You have already requested one hundred and six divinations from me, leaving two heavenly divinations left, but I can only perform one more for you," Patriarch Chen Tuan said.

"I want to ask you to look into the Reincarnation Palace Master again. If he isn't eliminated, he'll continue to remain a potent thorn in our side," the wheelchair-bound man requested.

"The Reincarnation Palace Master has mastered the laws of reincarnation, allowing him to hide in the cycle of reincarnation, so my divination no longer works on him. The past seventy-two divinations that I've conducted at your request have all been on him, with not a single one yielding any outcome. Are you sure you want me to try and peer into his future again?" Chen Tuan asked.

"I'm certain," the wheelchair-bound man replied in a categorical manner.

Chen Tuan wasted no more time with words as he made a hand seal with his only remaining hand while chanting an incantation, and a beam of golden light surged out of his lone eye before projecting into space up ahead.

The space there instantly warped into a black vortex that sucked in the beam of golden light, and it seemed to have become connected with the black vortex that Chen Tuan was situated in.

Several minutes later, the beam of golden light faded away, as did the black vortex.

At the same time, translucent black threads suddenly extended out of the vortex behind Tuan Jing, then wrapped themselves around his only remaining arm before slowly dragging it into the vortex.

"How did it go?" the wheelchair-bound man asked.

"The Reincarnation Palace Master remains completely untraceable, but I've caught a glimpse of someone who's never appeared before, but has very deep ties to him," Tuan Jing replied, and he didn't appear alarmed at all by the fact that his arm had just been devoured by the vortex behind him.

A ball of translucent light flew out of his glabella as he spoke, then drifted down onto the wheelchair-bound man's hand before fading away.

The wheelchair-bound man nodded in response, then prepared to depart.

"I can only carry out one more heavenly divination before I am completely devoured by the Heavenly Dao. When is your plan going to bear fruit?" Chen Tuan asked.

"Soon," the wheelchair-bound man replied before rising up into the sky and vanishing out of sight.

Chen Tuan looked up into the heavens as he heaved a forlorn sigh, then closed his eyes to rest once again.

[1]. For more information on the Chaotic Myriad Spirt Roll, please refer to https://a-record-of-a-mortal-is-journey-to-immortality.fandom.com/wiki/Chaotic_Myriad_Spirit_Roll

[Back]

Translator's Thoughts

Chapter 1300: Battle for the Reincarnation Plate

Deep within the gray stone palace in the Yellow Springs.

The Six Paths Reincarnation Plate was revolving rapidly at the Reincarnation Palace Master's behest, and a beam of red light shot out of its center, then spread over Nangong Wan's body to form a red light barrier.

At this point, Nangong Wan's entire body had already risen up out of the pond to be suspended in mid-air, and there was a film of hazy, white light over her entire body. Countless flashing images could be seen within the film of light, and they seemed to have been depicting different memories.

If Han Li were present, he would be able to identify those images as ones that depicted Nangong Wan's past, and there were many that featured him.

The Reincarnation Palace Master swept his gaze over the flashing images, then cast an incantation seal into the center of the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate.

All of the runes on the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate instantly lit up, and at the same time, six glowing, black holes appeared on its surface.

The holes were pitch black with no bottom in sight, as if they were connected to some mysterious place.

With a sweep of his other sleeve, a burst of dark red light shot out of the Reincarnation Palace Master's hand, then transformed into a hand projection that reached into one of the black holes.

Moments later, the hand returned with a cloud of rainbow light held in its grasp, and within the cloud were countless more flashing memories.

A hint of elation flashed through the Reincarnation Palace Master's eyes upon seeing this, and he cast the cloud of light into Nangong Wan's body.

Nangong Wan shuddered violently, and a layer of dreamy, orange light surfaced over her body to join the layer of white light, and the two layers of light began revolving around her, while the Reincarnation Palace Master used the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate to try and assist the layer of orange light in subjugating the white one.

However, the layer of white light proved to be very resilient, and it continued to firmly occupy its own territory.

Nangong Wan's eyes were firmly shut, and her brows were tightly furrowed in agony, while Wyrm 3 looked on with a tense expression.

The Reincarnation Palace Master's brows furrowed slightly as he stopped what he was doing for a moment.

"Is there something wrong, Palace Master?" Wyrm 3 asked in an apprehensive manner.

"Your mother's physical constitution in this lifetime is very compatible with the laws of reincarnation. As a result, her memories are proving to be more stubborn than I anticipated, and they're very difficult to suppress. If I do so by force, I'm worried that I'll harm her in the process," the Reincarnation Palace Master explained.

"Is there any other way?" Wyrm 3 hurriedly asked in a concerned manner.

The Reincarnation Palace Master was just about to respond when he suddenly cast his gaze outside, right as the sounds of a battle began to ring out.

"Are we under attack?" Wyrm 3 exclaimed with a surprised expression.

"It's Bone Emperor. He put on an act and pledged his subordination to me all those years ago, but it seems like he's still not willing to give up on the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate. Oh? He's here as well. What a coincidence," the Reincarnation Palace Master remarked with a hint of surprise in his voice.

"Who's he?" Wyrm 3 asked.

The Reincarnation Palace Master offered no response.

"Right now, the majority of our forces have already evacuated due to the Six Paths Gale winds, and we don't have many people on Yellow Springs Island," Wyrm 3 said with a concerned expression.

"It's fine. I've already made preparations for this scenario, and it'll serve as a good opportunity for me to eradicate some disloyal subordinates. It's just a pity that fewer people have turned up than what I expected. Use this Reincarnation Badge to support the array outside and keep Bone Emperor at bay for now, I'll be with you as soon as I'm done here," the Reincarnation Palace Master said as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a ball of dark red light.

Within the ball of light was a strange, hexagonal badge that resembled a miniature Six Paths Reincarnation Plate, and there were countless specks of dark red starlight shimmering on its surface.

Wyrm 3 caught the badge and immediately flew out of the palace, while the Reincarnation Palace Master murmured to himself, "It's been a very long time since I've displayed my powers. Perhaps everyone has already forgotten about me and is only aware of Gu Huojin now."

......

Han Li descended near the stone palace with Bone Emperor and the others, and an intrigued look appeared on his face at the sight of the dark red light barrier around the palace.

The light barrier was imbued with extremely formidable reincarnation law powers, and for some reason, it struck him with a sense of familiarity.

"He's trying to keep me out with this Reincarnation Array? What a joke!" Bone Emperor sneered as he swept a sleeve through the air once again, and a vast expanse of white light instantly appeared over the entire sky.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the heavens were split into two, and a gargantuan, white, bone claw descended from above before grabbing down onto the dark red light barrier below.

This bone claw was over ten times more powerful than the previous one, and the entire island was split into pieces by its unfathomable power.

The pieces of the island sank into the Yellow Springs, leaving only the gray palace and the surrounding light barrier hovering in mid-air.

At this moment, the dark red light barrier was trembling violently, and even though it was able to keep the bone claw at bay, it clearly wasn't going to be able to resist for much longer.

Right at this moment, a ball of dark red light flew out of the stone palace before vanishing into the surrounding light barrier, and it was instantly bolstered to its original state.

At the same time, a layer of dark red light appeared over the surface of the entire Yellow Springs, and the dark red light also rose up into the air to clash against the white light above.

The Six Paths Gale winds above the Yellow Springs were swept aside with ease in the face of the clash between the two bursts of tremendous power, and the nearby space became completely pulverized, forming countless spatial rifts that threatened to tear heaven and earth apart.

Immense suction force surged out of the surrounding fractured space, and Han Li's group of five immediately banded together upon seeing this, summoning their protective immortal treasures to form a barrier around themselves.

Xue Li and the others had also gathered around Bone Emperor, and after a brief hesitation, Gui Wu drifted over to Bone Emperor's camp.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, but made no attempt to stop him.

Thanks to the Reincarnation Array, the Yellow Springs down below had also been preserved instead of being devoured by the fractured space.

Right at this moment, a petite figure flew out of the palace, and Han Li was surprised to discover that it was none other than Wyrm 3.

She had also noticed Han Li's group as well, and she was clearly surprised to see them, but the situation was too urgent for her to acknowledge their presence.

She began chanting an incantation while making a string of hand seals, and a radiant, dark red light surged out of her body to form a wheel-like projection.

The dark red light spread over the Yellow Springs also began to transform, taking on the form an enormous wheel that overlooked the entirety of the Yellow Springs with the gray palace at its center.

A dark red array that was over a hundred feet in size had also appeared over the light barrier around the palace, and there were countless tiny, dark red runes dancing within it.

A burst of dull rumbling rang out as a pillar of dark red light that was several hundred feet thick erupted out of the array before piercing straight into the heavens.

The pillar of light was filled with countless flashing, dark red runes, and it was giving off an incredibly heavy, yet simultaneously peerlessly sharp aura.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and a deafening boom rang out as the giant, white bone claw was sent flying back through the air, while Bone Emperor himself also shuddered slightly before taking several involuntary backward steps.

Xue Li and the others were gathered around Bone Emperor, and they were sent flying like fallen leaves in a fierce storm.

His four early-Great Encompassment Stage subordinates were struck by the power of the pillar of dark red light, and they didn't even get a chance to cry out before their bodies exploded violently.

The rest of Bone Emperor's entourage was able to get away just in time to avoid suffering the same fate, but somehow, Gui Wu was also able to save himself, even though he should've been the most vulnerable one of the group, given that he was only a soul fragment.

As for Han Li's group, they had been standing quite far away to begin with, and Han Li had led everyone on a retreat as soon as the pillar of dark red light appeared, so they remained completely unscathed.

"Isn't that Wyrm 3, Master? What is she doing here? Isn't this supposed to be the Reincarnation King's territory?" Weeping Soul asked through voice transmission.

"Perhaps this Reincarnation King has something to do with the Reincarnation Palace," Jin Tong speculated.

"That's definitely a possibility. In any case, let's just stand by and observe for now," Han Li said, and Weeping Soul and Jin Tong nodded in response.

Han Li then also instructed Shi Chuankong and Violet Spirit to stay put, and neither of them raised any objections, but at the moment, there was a rather grim look on Shi Chuankong's face.

He and Violet Spirit had only been released from the Flower Branch domain not too long ago, and only then had he learned that Bone Emperor and his entourage were also after the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate.

Given the current situation, not only had his chances of securing the treasure become very slim, he seemed to have also been swept up in a conflict that he wished to take no part in.

In contrast, Violet Spirit was looking quite calm, and it seemed that she was content to follow Han Li's lead.

Han Li could sense Shi Chuankong's unease, and he turned his gaze back to the stone palace down below as he said, "If anything goes wrong, all of you should return to the Flower Branch domain."

Whatever attack that Wyrm 3 had just unleashed had been so formidable that it had managed to even force back Bone Emperor, so it was most likely the case that the array around the stone palace had been set up by none other than the Reincarnation Palace Master himself.

With that in mind, it was clear that the Reincarnation King and the Reincarnation Palace Master were one and the same.

At this moment, Wyrm 3 was confronting Bone Emperor on her own without displaying any fear, so could it be that the Reincarnation Palace Master was in the stone palace behind her?

Chapter 1301: Just in the Nick of Time

Even though Wyrm 3 had managed to force back Bone Emperor using the surrounding restriction, a pained look had appeared on her face, clearly indicating that operating the array was proving to be quite a strenuous task for her.

Bone Emperor was furious to have been knocked back by a Great Encompassment Stage junior, and he paid no heed to the demise of his four subordinates as he thrust his fist forward.

The giant, white bone claw also clenched itself into a fist before racing through the air at an extraordinary speed, crashing into the dark red light barrier with unstoppable might.

Wyrm 3 immediately drew up on the power of the surrounding array to oppose the attack, but her reactions were far slower than Bone Emperor's, and she was only able to draw upon a part of the array's power.

The two bursts of light, one white and one red, clashed against one another before exploding violently, creating a massive storm of power that swept away everything in the surrounding area.

The storm was particularly lethal as it was interspersed with countless fragments of white and dark red light, every single one of which was like an incredibly sharp dagger that tore even more gashes into the already severely ravaged space.

A burst of golden light instantly erupted out of Han Li's body to encompass Shi Chuankong and the others, following which he sped away into the distance to evade the spreading storm.

Xue Li and the others also hurriedly fled the scene, but they were a little slower to react than Han Li.

Despite this, Xue Li was still able to get away just fine, relying on his tremendous cultivation base to rush to safety as a rapid streak of crimson light.

However, the dark-skinned man, the black-robed wraith, and Gui Wu were not so fortunate, and they were swept up by the almighty storm.

The dark-skinned man had already been severely wounded by the restriction around the island earlier, and a hint of panic surfaced in his eyes as he let loose a wild roar and transformed into a black skeleton that stood at several hundred feet in height with two heads and four arms.

However, there were many fractures all over the skeleton's body, most likely a result of the injuries that had been inflicted upon it earlier.

A layer of black flames emerged over the skeleton's body, and it was able to ward off the surrounding storm as it fled into the distance.

Meanwhile, the black-robed wraith's body rapidly elongated until it resembled a semi-transparent, black snake, and it also shot forth into the distance, traveling even faster than the black skeleton.

Some of the sharp fragments of white and dark red light passed straight through its body, but despite its wraith-like appearance, it did not remain unharmed, and its body was rapidly shrinking, while its aura was also quickly on the wane.

Right as it was about to fly out of the storm, a streak of gray light suddenly shot out from the side. It was none other than Gui Wu's soul fragment, and it vanished into the black snake's body in a flash.

A horrified human face appeared at the front end of the black snake, and it opened its mouth in a silent scream.

A layer of gray light rapidly spread over the surface of the black snake's body, while the human face on its front end also transformed into that of Gui Wu.

Immediately thereafter, the gray light over the black snake's body faded away, and it reverted back to its original appearance.

All of this had unfolded in the blink of an eye, and the black snake continued to flee, flying out of the storm in an instant.

Only after ensuring that it had reached a safe distance away from the storm did the black snake revert back into the form of the black-robed wraith.

Xue Li, the dark-skinned man, and the black-robed wraith reconvened, and Xue Li asked, "Where's Gui Wu?"

"I didn't see him. Maybe he perished in the storm," the dark-skinned man said in an expressionless manner, having also reverted back to his humanoid form.

Xue Li cast his gaze toward the gray palace to discover that the storm was still raging there, annihilating everything within it.

At this point, Han Li's group had also gotten to safety, and they turned to look back at the stone palace.

Even through the storm, they were able to see that the dark red light barrier around the stone palace had been whittled down significantly once again.

However, it remained intact by the skin of its teeth as it continued to stand resiliently against the giant, white bone fist.

Inside the light barrier, Wyrm 3's complexion had turned deathly pale, and blood was trickling down from the corner of her lips, clearly indicating that she had sustained severe internal injuries.

Even so, she was still doing everything in her power to stabilize the light barrier and the surrounding array.

A cold sneer appeared on Bone Emperor's face as he stabbed a finger forward, and one of the fingers of the giant bone fist exploded violently to form a wave of white light that swept toward the dark red light barrier.

The wave of white light was able to infiltrate the light barrier, but it was significantly weakened in the process.

Wyrm 3 hurriedly flew back in retreat with an alarmed expression upon seeing this, and at the same time, streaks of dark red light shot out of the surrounding light barrier to protect her.

However, the wave of white light was traveling far too quickly, and it caught up to her in the blink of an eye. It was weakened once again by the obstructive streaks of dark red light, but it was still able to sweep over her, and a string of gruesome cracks and pops instantly rang out from within her body, while blood came gushing out of her mouth.

All of her bones had been shattered, and her internal organs had also been severely damaged.

If it weren't for the fact that she had managed to ward off some of the law powers within the wave of white light with her own reincarnation law powers, her body would've already exploded on the spot.

She took a deep breath as she forcibly steadied herself, but right at this moment, another one of the bone fist's fingers exploded.

A second wave of white light surged into the dark red light barrier before sweeping toward her, and a look of despair surfaced in her eyes upon seeing this.

It was proving to be an immense struggle for her to simply remain standing, let alone defend herself. For some reason, in her moment of despair, she turned her gaze to Han Li with a complex mix of emotions in her eyes.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

Right at this moment, the two ghostly generals down below rose up into the air to shield her, and the one with the cow head yelled, "We'll hold him off, you go and alert the palace master!"

Immediately thereafter, he swung his iron staff through the air, unleashing a flurry of staff projections to form a staff mountain.

All of the staff projections were giving off bursts of crimson and blue light, which intertwined with one another to form a bouquet of red and blue flowers that raced toward the oncoming wave of white light.

At the same time, the horse-faced ghostly general lashed out with his crystalline chain and skin-peeling ghostly claw to conjure up a wall of chains, in front of which was a mountainous, white ghostly claw that was enveloped in a layer of white bone flames.

Both of the ghostly generals were at the Great Encompassment Stage, and their combined powers were nothing to be scoffed at, but the mountain of staff projections and the ghostly white claw were both instantly eradicated upon contact with the wave of white light, and the wall of chains was also breached without being able to offer any resistance.

The two ghostly generals had already anticipated that their attacks wouldn't be very effective, but they were still stunned to see just how ineffective they had proven to be.

However, as opposed to backing down, both of them chose to self-detonate in a final, self-sacrificial act to defy the oncoming wave of white light.

Unfortunately, the wave of white light was traveling so quickly that it swept over their bodies before they were able to self-detonate, and a string of gruesome sounds instantly rang out from within their bodies, following which they were reduced to piles of mincemeat.

The wave of white light continued onward without pause, reaching Wyrm 3 in the blink of an eye.

The two ghostly generals hadn't bought her much time at all, and she was still in no condition to be defending herself.

A defeated look appeared on her face as she closed her eyes and accepted her fate.

Right at this moment, a burst of golden light erupted onto the scene, encompassing the entirety of the gray palace.

The wave of white light was instantly slowed down to a crawl.

Far away in the distance, an enormous, golden spirit domain had taken shape around Han Li, and Weeping Soul and the others were nowhere to be seen.

Wyrm 3's eyes sprang open as an ecstatic look appeared on her face, and she flew arduously to the side to just barely evade the wave of white light.

"I knew you were up to no good, you little rat! If it isn't for the fact that your special physical constitution could help me ward off the assimilation of the Heavenly Dao, I would've already killed you on the spot!" Bone Emperor harrumphed coldly as he reached out in Han Li's direction, and another gargantuan, white bone claw appeared in the heavens above before making a grab for him.

All of the air, space, and the world's origin qi beneath the giant claw instantly became as hard as a rock, sealing everything within the area.

However, right before the emergence of the bone claw, a path of golden light had already appeared beneath Han Li's feet, and he had vanished from the spot before the bone claw had a chance to seal the space around him.

The path of golden light extended all the way to the dark red light barrier, where it was stopped in its tracks, and Han Li appeared upon it, seemingly out of thin air.

This path of golden light was the Ubiquitous Path ability of the True Mantra Sect, and it had been passed down to him by Patriarch Miro in the Yama Manor.

"Let me in, Wyrm 3!" Han Li called out in an urgent manner through voice transmission.

He had no confidence in his ability to oppose Bone Emperor on his own.

Wyrm 3 faltered slightly upon seeing this, then immediately snapped back to her senses before casting an incantation seal toward the dark red light barrier.

"You think you can just get away? Get back here!" Bone Emperor roared, and the bone fist that was pressed against the light barrier spread itself open at his behest, then came grabbing down upon Han Li.

A burst of incredibly formidable law powers erupted out of the bone claw before directly infiltrating Han Li's body, and he felt his own skeleton begin to rattle uncontrollably, as if it were about to tear its way out of his body.

Chapter 1302: Joining Forces

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face as the golden light within the spirit domain around him instantly became brighter by severalfold, and his five time law treasure manifestations also appeared before revolving rapidly around him.

His Mantra Treasured Axis was hanging high up in the sky like a radiant moon, and his Time Severing Torch transformed into a dazzling sea of stars, while a winding river of time flowed out of his Clear Time Vial.

At the same time, his Illusory Dawn Hourglass transformed into a vast, golden desert, upon which a lush oasis took sharp in the form of the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree.

All of these time law treasure manifestations were substantial entities, and it was as if a small world had appeared around the gray palace.

Five bursts of tremendous time law powers instantly intertwined with one another to dispel the strange law powers surging out of the bone claw, and as Han Li continued to channel his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra with all his might, the power of his spirit domain became more potent, but it didn't expand any further.

The larger a spirit domain became, the more scattered its power would be.

Bone Emperor cast an incantation seal into the giant bone claw, and the two fingers that had previously exploded instantly reformed, following which all five fingers came crashing heavily down upon Han Li's spirit domain like five giant blades.

Five huge gashes were instantly torn into Han Li's spirit domain, almost splitting it into six sections, but it was able to resiliently hold itself intact.

Right at this moment, a streak of dark red light shot out of Wyrm 3's fingertip before vanishing into a section of the light barrier near Han Li, and an opening appeared before him.

Han Li immediately pounced on the opportunity, channeling his Reversal True Axis ability to fly into the light barrier at an incredible speed.

At the same time, his time spirit domain shrank down to only several hundred feet in size, and it sealed the opening in the light barrier to prevent anyone from sneaking in after him.

However, before Wyrm 3 had a chance to close the opening, a streak of white light shot forth from afar, and it tore its way into Han Li's spirit domain with ease before appearing within the opening, revealing itself to be a white bone spear that was several dozen feet in length.

There were countless twisted runes flowing over the spear, and it was giving off an incredibly formidable deathly aura, coupled with immense penetrative power.

Having just hurled the spear into the opening in the light barrier from afar, Bone Emperor immediately came racing onto the scene from afar.

Han Li knew that Bone Emperor had to be kept out of the light barrier at all costs, and a flurry of time law threads instantly shot out of his body before fusing into the time spirit domain at his behest.

All five time law treasure manifestations began to glow even more radiantly than before, and five bursts of time law powers surged through the spirit domain, giving everything a hazy and indistinct appearance.

The bone spear was instantly stopped cold in its tracks, and its aura was rapidly waning.

At the same time, Han Li channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, and all 1,799 of his profound acupoints lit up at once.

Simultaneously, he channeled all twelve of the true spirit bloodlines in his body, then threw an almighty punch at the bone spear.

Twelve true spirit projections emerged around him before instantly fusing back into his body, and a vast expanse of black light erupted out of his body before transforming into a massive, black vortex that gave off a burst of tremendous suction force.

The nearby space trembled violently as one spatial passageway after another appeared, and bursts of pure energy surged out of them in a frenzy.

There was energy of all types of attributes, but it predominantly consisted of devilish qi, and there was also a particularly formidable burst of energy surging out of the gray palace.

All of the energy converged toward Han Li before surging into his body, and a faint cracking sound rang out as a bright speck of light emerged over his glabella.

Back on Eight Plains Mountain, he had opened 1,799 of his 1,8000 profound acupoints using the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, but the final one had proved unexpectedly stubborn.

In this dire situation, Han Li was channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and all twelve of his true spirit bloodlines at once in a reckless act of desperation, and it proved to be the catalyst that was required to finally carry him to the summit.

A layer of dark purple scales surfaced over his entire body, and he swelled to over a hundred times his original size, transforming into a dark purple devilish giant that was over a thousand feet tall.

In this form, he possessed twelve heads, each of which was displaying a different emotion.

At the same time, eleven additional pairs of arms had sprouted from his body, and they were all making different hand seals as well.

A burst of dark purple light erupted out of his gargantuan body, and it swept through the surrounding area with immense power, causing the dark red light barrier to shudder violently.

Han Li was overjoyed by this transformation, but he had no time to celebrate as his fist dealt the bone spear an almighty blow.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the spear was shattered into countless specks of white light, all of which were sent hurtling out of the opening in the dark red light barrier, allowing it to close again.

Bone Emperor arrived outside the light barrier just a split second too late, and he let loose a roar of fury and frustration.

A relieved look appeared on Wyrm 3's face upon seeing this, but more blood then came gushing out of her mouth, and it seemed that she reaggravated her injuries.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air upon seeing this, releasing a burst of golden light that enveloped Wyrm 3 to steady her while also injecting a torrent of energy into her body.

This burst of energy seemed to have a very potent healing effect, and most of her injuries were instantly healed.

An elated look appeared on her face as she hurriedly made a string of hand seals, and the dark red light barrier was instantly bolstered significantly, while the dark red array reappeared over its surface.

Countless tiny runes surged out of the array, followed by a flurry of thick chains, all of which swept toward Bone Emperor in unison.

In response, Bone Emperor swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a crescent-shaped streak of white light with countless white runes dancing within it.

This streak of light possessed a far more formidable aura than the bone spear from earlier, and it stirred up the nearby world's origin qi into a frenzy as it crashed into the oncoming dark red chains.

A faint crack rang out as the streak of white light sliced through the dark red chains like tofu, and it continued to descend toward the dark red light barrier with unmatched power.

The light barrier instantly began trembling violently while Wyrm 3 did everything in her power to stabilize it, but given her injuries, she was unable to draw upon the full power of the surrounding Reincarnation Array.

As a result, the dark red light barrier was rapidly being whittled down by the streak of white light.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he pointed a finger in Wyrm 3's direction, upon which a beam of golden light that was giving off tremendous time law power fluctuations shot out of his fingertip before vanishing into her body.

The reincarnation law powers within her body resonated with his time law powers, and the dark red light around her instantly brightened significantly.

The surrounding Reincarnation Array was connected directly to her, and it also began to glow brightly as it stabilized the trembling light barrier, allowing it to hold its own against the streak of white light.

Right at this moment, all of the severed chains suddenly wrapped themselves around Bone Emperor like a nest of agile spirit snakes, forming a cocoon of chains in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, Wyrm 3 made a hand seal, and the cocoon of chains exploded into a radiant, dark red sun.

Devastating shockwaves were sent sweeping through the air in all directions, and an alarmed look appeared on the dark-skinned man's face as he yelled, "Master Bone Emperor!"

The body of the black wraith that had been taken over by Gui Wu also rippled slightly, but he remained silent.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3 made another hand seal, and countless swirling patterns appeared over the dark red light barrier, instantly forming a giant vortex.

A burst of immense devouring force surged out of the vortex, and the streak of crescent-shaped white light was instantly sucked into it.

Only then did Wyrm 3 allow herself a faint sigh of relief, following which she turned to Han Li with a slightly hesitant expression as she said, "Thank you for your help, Fellow Daoist Han, but what were you doing with those people earlier? Could it be that you share the same objective as them?"

"Those are not allies of mine, I encountered them through sheer coincidence," Han Li replied as he quickly reverted back to his human before withdrawing his time spirit domain.

"That's good to hear," Wyrm 3 said with a relieved expression.

However, she then noticed that Han Li was staring intently at the dark red sun in the distance with his brows tightly furrowed, and a sense of foreboding instantly welled up in her heart upon seeing this.

Chapter 1303: Arrival of the Palace Master

Before either Han Li or Wyrm 3 had a chance to do anything, the dark red sun suddenly began to tremble violently, and at the same time, it was beginning to expand and shrink erratically as if it had become a living creature.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of white light erupted out of its surface, following which the entire sun was split into two before dissipating into specks of dark red light.

As a result, Bone Emperor was revealed, and he was completely unscathed.

The ghostly flames in his eye sockets were dancing with fury, but he didn't immediately lash out again.

Having already been thwarted on several occasions, he had learned that these two opponents had to be taken seriously.

Even though both of them were only Great Encompassment cultivators, this Reincarnation Array was so powerful that it allowed them to oppose him on near equal terms.

Xue Li, the dark-skinned man, and the black-robed wraith flew over to Bone Emperor from afar, and the dark-skinned man asked in a concerned manner, "Are you alright, Master Bone Emperor?"

Bone Emperor offered no response as he swept a sleeve through the air, and a ball of blinding white light erupted out of the palm of his skeletal hand.

Countless bursts of white light instantly descended from the heavens, and they combined to form an enormous wave that swept toward the stone palace.

The gray palace and the surrounding light barrier began to tremble once again, resembling a fragile raft in a turbulent sea.

Han Li and Wyrm 3 instantly raised their hands in unison to combine their law powers in an attempt to stabilize the Reincarnation Array, but after conjuring up that wave of white light, Bone Emperor didn't unleash any further attacks.

Instead, he turned to the black-robed wraith with a cold expression as he said, "Drop the act, Gui Wu, I know you've possessed Hei Pao's body."

"I knew I wouldn't be able to fool you, Senior Bone Emperor," the black-robed wraith chuckled, then transformed into the gray-robed Gui Wu, much to the astonishment of Xue Li and the dark-skinned man.

"My soul fragment was about to be destroyed in the earlier storm, so I had no choice but to possess Fellow Daoist Hei Pao in order to save myself. I hope you'll forgive me, Senior Bone Emperor," Gui Wu said as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute.

"I'll let this slide if you can kill that human cultivator for me. I'm sure you've already collected a seed of his aura during the time that you spent with him," Bone Emperor said in a cold voice.

"That's not a problem at all. Seeing as he's chosen to ally himself with the Reincarnation King, he is now an enemy of our underworld, so it's only right that I take him out of the picture," Gui Wu replied with a smile, then opened his mouth to release a gray, humanoid puppet that was several inches in size and devoid of facial features.

After that, he flipped a hand over to summon a gray talisman that seemed to have had some type of sealing restriction inscribed upon it, and at its center was a ball of golden light that was giving off Han Li's aura.

Gui Wu plastered the talisman onto the puppet's face, and it immediately disintegrated into countless gray runes that surged into the puppet's body along with the ball of golden light.

Han Li's facial features instantly appeared on the puppet's featureless face, and it began to tremble violently as if it were about to spring to life.

A cruel smile appeared on Gui Wu's face as he raised his other hand, and seven black needles appeared over the palm of his hand, giving off a menacing, black glow.

With a flick of his finger, all seven of the black needles shot forth in unison, piercing into seven of the puppet's vital regions.

Blood instantly came spurting out of the puppet's body and trickling out of its mouth, and the injuries that it had suffered were mirrored on Han's body as well.

Not only that, but a burst of excruciating agony speared through his consciousness as seven indistinct, black needle projections pierced into his soul.

He immediately threw up a mouthful of blood as his aura waned drastically, and an alarmed look appeared on Wyrm 3's face as she yelled, "What happened to you, Fellow Daoist Han?"

Han Li offered no response as he closed his eyes with an agonized expression.

At this moment, there were seven bursts of destructive force crashing through his consciousness with the intention of eradicating his soul.

He felt as if his head were on the verge of exploding, and the pain was almost too much to bear.

Thankfully, his tremendously powerful soul saved him from being killed on the spot, and his entire body was instantly enveloped in a layer of golden light.

The seven wounds that had been inflicted immediately stopped bleeding, and the seven needle projections in his consciousness also became much fainter than before, while his pain was significantly alleviated.

He heaved a faint sigh of relief as he opened his eyes before sweeping a sleeve through the air, and Weeping Soul and the others emerged amid a flash of silver light.

"All of you, go and help Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3," he instructed, then hurriedly closed his eyes once again, channeling his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra and his Spirit Refinement Technique to refine the seven bursts of destructive power in his mind.

Without the support of Han Li's time law powers, the Reincarnation Array was significantly weakened, causing the dark red light barrier to begin trembling unsteadily once again.

Wyrm 3 hurriedly made a string of hand seals as she did everything in her power to stabilize the light barrier, but there was only so much that she could do on her own.

Weeping Soul and the others didn't know how to help her, so they could only resist the power infiltrating the light barrier to the best of their abilities in order to take some pressure off her shoulders.

Outside the light barrier, Gui Wu was staring at the puppet in his hand with tightly furrowed brows.

The puppet had already stopped bleeding, and Han Li's facial features on it had become much dimmer, but they hadn't vanished.

"He survived? How?" Gui Wu murmured to himself in a stunned manner, while Xue Li looked on with a cold sneer.

"We've already wasted too much time here! Everyone, attack at once to destroy this Reincarnation Array!" Bone Emperor ordered, and a hint of urgency had crept into his voice.

An enormous mountain formed by countless skeletons appeared behind him, giving off bursts of incredibly formidable law power fluctuations.

Immediately thereafter, a giant bone claw tore its way out of the bone mountain before grabbing down upon the dark red light barrier.

Xue Li also sprang into action as a vast expanse of crimson light erupted out of his body to form an enormous crimson cloud.

With a swing of his giant ax, the crimson cloud instantly converted to a single spot, forming a gargantuan, crimson ax projection with arcs of lightning flashing over its surface, presenting a fearsome sight to behold.

As Xue Li swung his ax downward, the giant, crimson ax in the sky also came crashing down onto the light barrier.

At the same time, the dark-skinned man transformed into a ghostly giant with two heads and four arms once again, then unleashed a barrage of countless fist projections that came raining down upon the Reincarnation Array.

Gui Wu wasn't very proficient at unleashing physical attacks like his companions, but he had also sent a streak of black light blasting into the dark red light barrier.

Their attacks fell upon the light barrier in unison with a deafening boom, and Wyrm 3 shuddered violently as blood came spurting out of all of her orifices.

However, her eyes remained as bright as ever, and she continued to power the array with all her might, displaying no fear or regard for her own safety.

Before long, the dark red light barrier had been whittled down to a thin layer, and cracks had also appeared over the surface of the palace down below, looking as if it were on the verge of collapse.

Right at this moment, a burst of immense power surged out of the palace before injecting itself into the Reincarnation Array.

The entire array instantly began to glow radiantly, as if it were celebrating the return of its master.

As a result, the dark red light barrier also became even thicker and more resilient than before, and countless bursts of dark red light erupted out of it to force back the attacks unleashed by Bone Emperor and the others.

Bone Emperor shuddered violently as he stumbled back a couple of steps in retreat with a stunned look on his face, while Xue Li and the others fared even worse as they were sent flying back through the air.

A combination of relief and elation surfaced in Wyrm 3's eyes upon seeing this, and she was unable to suppress her injuries any longer as she came tumbling out of the sky.

A ball of dark red light appeared out of thin air to catch her, following which the Reincarnation Palace Master emerged by her side.

"Palace Master... Have you done everything that you need to do?" Wyrm 3 asked in a feeble voice.

"I have. You've done very well, Jiuzhen. Take a good rest and leave everything else to me" the Reincarnation Palace Master replied in a gentle voice, then swept a sleeve through the air to send a surge of warmth spreading through Wyrm 3's entire body.

Her injuries were instantly healed, while close to half of her immortal spiritual power reserves had also been replenished, and she sprang to her feet with an elated expression.

Weeping Soul and the others were feeling rather apprehensive after witnessing the Reincarnation Palace Master's immense power, and they flew over to Han Li's side to form a tightly knit formation.

Han Li also rose to his feet as the golden light around him faded away, and he turned to the Reincarnation Palace Master with a slightly dazed look in his eyes.

The Reincarnation Palace Master's facial features were concealed under his hood, but for some reason, Han Li was struck by a sense of familiarity at the sight of him.

The Reincarnation Palace Master took a glance at Han Li, then cast his gaze toward Bone Emperor as he said, "Long time no see, Bone Emperor."

"I've always really wanted to see you, but the opportunity has never arisen," Bone Emperor said in a cold voice.

"Isn't this a good opportunity?" the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"It's more than just good, this is a brilliant opportunity! Your cultivation base is inferior to mine, and you must be exhausted, having just used the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate, so there's no way you can hope to oppose me!" Bone Emperor declared.

"You're as greedy as ever, Bone Emperor. It seems like the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate really does pose a very alluring temptation to you," the Reincarnation Palace Master remarked as he flew out of the dark red light barrier.

Chapter 1304: Path of No Return

"You've already had the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate for far too long, it's far overdue for a switch of hands!" Bone Emperor harrumphed coldly, then extended his arms horizontally to either side of himself before twisting one hand upward and the other hand downward, following which he began making a string of strange hand seals.

At the same time, the two flames in his eye sockets began to glow as radiantly as the sun, while aura swelled to unprecedented heights. Furthermore, his entire skeletal body had become even fairer and more translucent than before, but for some reason, some cracks had also appeared over its surface.

Immediately thereafter, an enormous, white spirit domain appeared behind him, then continued to spread outward, with its boundaries instantly vanishing out of sight.

In the blink of an eye, the entire surrounding area in a radius of several million kilometers had been encompassed within the spirit domain, and it was still continuing to expand.

The spirit domain was so vast that it encompassed the Black River, Infernal, and Yama Regions, and it was still rapidly expanding, as if it fully intended to encompass the entire underworld!

At the same time, the entire sky was torn apart as bursts of light in the shape of lengths of bones emerged, and it was as if the Heavenly Dao itself had descended.

Within this all-encompassing spirit domain, some of the more powerful ghostly cultivators were able to somewhat protect themselves, while the weaker ones had their skeletons torn straight out of their bodies before fusing with the spirit domain.

Not only that, but the spirit domain had even seeped into space and descended upon some of the lower realms, and it was as if a cataclysmic natural disaster had befallen them.

In the blink of an eye, billions upon billions of living beings exploded as their skeletons flew out of their bodies to form vast rivers of bones that came together to form an unfathomably massive vortex.

Countless bones converged from all directions before fusing into Bone Emperor's spirit domain, forming a colossal bone mountain that came crashing down from above.

Only now was Bone Emperor truly putting his power as a Dao Ancestor on full display.

Inside the Reincarnation Array, Violet Spirit fainted on the spot, but she was caught by Han Li before she could fall.

Shi Chuankong and Weeping Soul's legs had given out from under them, and their complexions had turned deathly pale, while Jin Tong was able to fare slightly better, but she was also swaying unsteadily on her feet.

Han Li was struck by a rush of dizziness as his soul trembled within his consciousness, and he hurriedly channeled his time law powers and Spirit Refinement Technique to steady himself.

At the same time, a look of astonishment appeared in his eyes at just how incredibly fearsome the might of a Dao Ancestor was.

In contrast, the Reincarnation Palace Master remained completely unfazed as he thrust a palm forward with a composed smile on his face, and a projection of a hexagonal plate that took up the entire sky appeared before him.

Countless figures of all descriptions were rapidly emerging from the projection, which was also giving off an indescribably vast aura.

In this instant, it was as if he had become the master of the cycle of incarnation across all of the countless realms.

In his presence, no humans, devils, ghosts, or any living beings would be able to escape the fate of being cast into the cycle of reincarnation.

All it took was a slight turn of the hexagonal plate projection, and the descending bone mountain instantly stopped cold in its tracks before exploding into countless scraps of bone like an egg.

With the bone mountain destroyed, Bone Emperor was revealed, and most of his body had already shattered. He let loose a horrified screech as he turned to flee, but he was completely immobilized.

"I'm sure you've heard about how all of the Dao Ancestors who challenged me in the past were either cast into the cycle of reincarnation or pledged their subordination to me. Unfortunately for you, both of those paths have been closed to you," the Reincarnation Palace Master sighed as he swept a sleeve through the air, and a burst of tremendous suction force erupted out of the hexagonal plate projection to suck in both Bone Emperor and the vast expanse of bone scraps hanging in the sky.

Shortly thereafter, the hexagonal plate projection also faded away, and with it spelled the demise of a Dao Ancestor.

Xue Li and the others were completely flabbergasted by what they had just witnessed.

Never had they imagined that this would be the outcome of their quest for revenge against the Reincarnation King.

"My avatar spared you your lives all those years ago. Now that you've been freed, you should've been more appreciative of your second chance at life, instead of taking it for granted like this," the Reincarnation Palace Master said as he turned his gaze to Xue Li's group.

"Please spare us..."

Xue Li and the others immediately fell to their knees as they began kowtowing for mercy.

"It seems that repentance only ever comes in one's final moments," the Reincarnation Palace Master remarked, then swept a sleeve through the air to release what appeared to have been a wave of crimson smoke.

As soon as the crimson wave swept over Xue Li and the others, their flesh and blood were instantly reduced to ashes, leaving only their skeletons behind, still kowtowing on the ground.

However, their skeletons were only able to linger for an instant longer before they disintegrated into nothingness as well.

Looking on from the side, Han Li was just as astonished by the Reincarnation Palace Master's unfathomable power as Xue Li and the others had been.

Right at this moment, the Reincarnation Palace Master suddenly turned to Han Li as he said, "It was about time that we met, so you've saved me the trouble of searching for you. Come with me."

A peculiar look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this, but he duly obliged, carrying Violet Spirit in his arms as he turned to follow the Reincarnation Palace Master toward the stone palace, while Weeping Soul and the others trailed along behind him.

"You and Wyrm 3 can come in with me, but everyone else is to wait outside," the Reincarnation Palace Master instructed, then made his way into the stone palace.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this before passing Violet Spirit to Weeping Soul. He then gave everyone a nod of reassurance before making his way into the stone palace.

Wyrm 3 took a glance at him with a complex mix of emotions in her eyes, then followed him into the stone palace.

The palace gates slowly swung shut, creating a dark and shadowy environment.

Han Li looked around to discover that the interior of the palace was quite spacious, and that there was a giant, black, stone plaque at the back of the palace with the word "Reincarnation" inscribed upon it in bold, red characters.

It seemed that the reason why the Reincarnation Palace had managed to remain hidden from the Heavenly Court all this time was because it was concealed within the underworld.

Furthermore, even though the mysterious Reincarnation Palace Master appeared to have only been at the late-Great Encompassment Stage, his true power had somehow already far exceeded that of the average Dao Ancestor.

With all this in mind, Han Li's interest in the Reincarnation Palace Master had been well and truly piqued.

For some reason, he was unable to shake the lingering sense of familiarity that arose whenever he laid eyes upon the Reincarnation Palace Master.

Right at this moment, a dark red spirit domain emerged from the Reincarnation Palace Master's body before quickly expanding to encompass the entire palace.

Standing within the spirit domain, Han Li didn't feel any discomfort, but he could clearly sense that his connection with the outside world, including with Weeping Soul and the others, had been completely severed.

"Han Li, you've been involved in much of our Reincarnation Palace's past affairs, and you've also assisted Wyrm 3 greatly on many occasions. For that, I should be thankful to you," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

"There's no need to be grateful to me, Wyrm 3 has also helped me greatly in exchange," Han Li replied.

"I can see that you've already mastered the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique. Has Wyrm 3 informed you of the drawbacks of pursuing this cultivation art?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked.

"I am aware of the drawbacks," Han Li replied. "Once I decide to pursue this cultivation art, I must continue to cultivate it and attain full mastery within a set amount of time. Otherwise, I will be driven to a deranged state and reduced to a mindless savage."

"That's correct. However, I presume that you're unaware of why this cultivation art comes with such a drawback. I can reveal the answer to you now," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

Han Li nodded in response, then waited patiently for the Reincarnation Palace Master to continue.

"The Spirit Refinement Technique is a secret technique that I created with the power of reincarnation as its basis. It enhances one's soul by drawing upon one's spiritual sense from their future lifetimes. Once you begin cultivating it, you cannot stop. The more you progress, the more of the spiritual sense of your future incarnations you'll exhaust in order to enhance your spiritual sense in this lifetime," the Reincarnation Palace Master explained.

"Surely doing something like that would incur catastrophic repercussions!" Han Li exclaimed.

"If one cannot attain full mastery of the Spirit Refinement Technique, then they'll suffer backlash from the souls of their future incarnations, thereby driving them to insanity. However, upon reaching full mastery, a new equilibrium will be achieved, and you'll be able to avoid such a fate," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"So you're saying that as long as I can attain full mastery of the Spirit Refinement Technique, it won't have any drawbacks?" Han Li asked.

"That's correct, at least for this lifetime. However, due to how severely you've exhausted the spiritual sense of your future incarnations, if you enter the cycle of reincarnations, then your future incarnations will possess no aptitude for cultivation due to their lacking spiritual sense, and there's a very good chance that they'll be born with severe mental impairments," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"It sounds like I've gone down a path of no return," Han Li remarked with a wry smile.

Chapter 1305: Another Me

"Given how you're currently progressing in your cultivation, attaining full mastery of the Spirit Refinement Technique should not be an issue. Here are the final two levels of the cultivation art.

“Once you've attained full mastery, you'll no longer have to be concerned about being driven to insanity by spiritual sense backlash, but on the flip side, you'll be robbing all of your future incarnations of their cultivation aptitude, so the decision is up to you," the Reincarnation Palace Master said, and he swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke to send a streak of light flying toward Han Li.

Han Li caught the streak of light to discover that it was a white jade slip, which contained the final two levels of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

"There really is only one path that I can take, and that's to keep cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique. If I were just a mortal, perhaps I would be able to enter the cycle of reincarnation once I meet my demise. However, as a cultivator, if I am to perish someday, there may not even be an opportunity for me to enter the cycle of reincarnation," Han Li sighed.

"That's a very pragmatic way of looking at things," the Reincarnation Palace Master said, then fell into a hesitant silence as he looked at Han Li with his hands clasped behind his back.

Han Li was the one to break the silence as he said, "There's been a question that's been on my mind for a very long time. Would you be able to enlighten me, Senior?"

"Go ahead," the Reincarnation Palace Master prompted.

"Back when I was with Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3 in the Nine Origins Temple, I encountered a woman who looked extremely similar to an acquaintance of mine. May I ask where that fellow daoist is right now, and would I be able to see her?" Han Li asked.

"What you want to know is whether that woman is Nangong Wan, right?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked.

Han Li was shaken to the core by this question, but he did his best to maintain a composed facade. Never had he imagined that the Reincarnation Palace Master would be so direct and straightforward.

"That's right," Han Li confirmed, and in the wake of the question raised by the Reincarnation Palace Master, he was already certain that the woman was indeed Nangong Wan.

"The person that you're referring to is here as we speak, but she's not Nangong Wan. To put it more accurately, she's not your Nangong Wan," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and a hint of animosity had already begun to surface in his eyes.

It seemed that the Reincarnation Palace Master didn't harbor any ill intent toward him, and he had even given him the final two levels of the Spirit Refinement Technique free of charge, but this was a matter that concerned Nangong Wan, so he was not going to back down.

Over the course of his cultivation journey, he had made countless sacrifices and let many people down, but there were certain compromises that he absolutely refused to make.

Otherwise, he would no longer be himself, and no matter how lofty his cultivation base became, it would hardly matter.

"If she's here, then why not allow me to see her? As for whether she's by dao partner or not, I'll be able to tell that myself," Han Li said.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a figure suddenly emerged from behind the stone plaque at the back of the palace.

Han Li was instantly entranced by the sight of the familiar figure. Her fair skin, her delicate nose, her clear and alluring eyes... All of those things had appeared in his dreams countless times, and he felt his own heart melt a little as the figure in the blue palatial dress came into view.

However, for some reason, Nangong Wan's aura had swelled drastically since their previous meeting, and on top of it, it seemed to have been a little unstable. What was even stranger to Han Li was the look on her face as she gazed upon him.

There was confusion, guilt, and regret, but she didn't display any of the joy that Han Li was experiencing at their reunion.

"What did you do to her?" Han Li asked as he turned to the Reincarnation Palace Master with a cold expression.

"Don't be angry, Fellow Daoist Han. The palace master merely helped Mother recover her memories from her previous life," Wyrm 3 said as she took a step toward him.

"Mother? Who's your mother?" Han Li asked with a perplexed expression, then strode directly toward Nangong Wan.

The Reincarnation Palace Master made no effort to stop him, while Wyrm 3 reflexively reached out, but ultimately followed the Reincarnation Palace Master's lead.

Right as Han Li was about to grab onto Nangong Wan's hand, the latter suddenly took a step back as she gave him a stern glare.

Han Li was instantly rooted to the spot, and he cast an incredulous gaze toward her as he asked, "Why, Wan'er?"

A reminiscent look surfaced in Nangong Wan's eyes upon hearing Han Li's pet name for her, and a dazed expression appeared on her face as she stared at Han Li with the memories of a previous life flashing through her eyes.

"Mother..."

Right at this moment, Wyrm 3 suddenly called out to her, snapping her out of her daze.

Wyrm 3 then stroked a hand over her own face to reveal a black mask, and for the first time, she revealed her true appearance in its most authentic and undisguised form.

Tears instantly began to stream down Nangong Wan's face as she hurried over to Wyrm 3 and exclaimed in elation, "Jiuzhen!"

She could sense the bloodline connection between the two of them.

Wyrm 3 nodded vigorously as tears began to flow down her cheeks as well, while Han Li looked as if he had been dealt a heavy blow.

He turned to the Reincarnation Palace Master, barely able to contain his own rage as he asked, "What did you do to her?"

"Nothing, I merely returned her lost memories and cultivation base to her," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied in an indifferent manner.

Wyrm 3 had never seen Han Li display such raw and violent emotions before, and she hurriedly interjected, "The palace master used the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate to help her recover her memories from her past life. She was my mother, Gan Rushuang."

"That has nothing to do with me! All I know is that she is my dao partner and my wife, Nangong Wan!" Han Li roared in a furious voice, and at the same time, his time spirit domain erupted out of his body with such tremendous might that both Wyrm 3 and Nangong Wan were forced back an involuntary step.

However, the Reincarnation Palace Master remained completely unmoved, and with a casual sweep of his sleeve, Han Li's time law powers were instantly stifled, while his time spirit domain vanished into thin air.

All of a sudden, Nangong Wan shuddered violently as the memories of two lifetimes began clashing in her mind, and her face instantly became twisted with agony as she collapsed to the ground with her hands clawing at her own head.

Han Li immediately turned to rush to her side, but the Reincarnation Palace Master was faster, appearing behind her in the blink of an eye before gently caressing a hand over the top of her head.

The pained look on Nangong Wan's face gradually faded away, and she fell into a deep sleep.

"It looks like recovering her past memories and cultivation base at once is too much for her to bear. She'll need some time to complete the acclimation process," the Reincarnation Palace Master said

"Her previous life is all in the past, so what gives you the right to force those memories upon her?" Han Li asked as he clenched his fists in a white-knuckled grip.

"Because she is also my wife and my only dao partner," the Reincarnation Palace Master countered in a cold voice.

A stunned look appeared on both Han Li and Wyrm 3's faces.

"Jiuzhen, you've always wanted to know who your father is, right?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked as he turned to Wyrm 3 with a benevolent expression, then removed the conical bamboo hat that he perpetually wore to reveal his true appearance.

In the instant that his true appearance was revealed, both Han Li and Wyrm 3 were completely rooted to the spot in shock.

Wyrm 3 had always guessed that the Reincarnation Palace Master would have the appearance of an elderly man, yet to her utter astonishment, his face was completely identical to Han Li's!

"Who are you?" Han Li asked in an alarmed voice as he released his time spirit domain once again.

He had witnessed countless bizarre and inexplicable things over the course of his cultivation journey, but never had he been rendered so astonished and incredulous by anything.

His dao partner had suddenly become someone else's dao partner, and that person was completely identical in appearance to himself.

He could sense that the Reincarnation Palace Master hadn't manipulated his own appearance in any way to mirror his, so it was no wonder that he had always felt so familiar to him.

If it weren't for the fact that the Reincarnation Palace Master possessed completely different law powers to his, Han Li would've been convinced that he was looking at an avatar of himself.

"I am me, and you are you. I am Han Li, and you are also Han Li," the Reincarnation Palace Master sighed.

"What is happening?" Wyrm 3 asked with a dazed expression, and she felt as if all of the strength had been drained from her body as she held the unconscious Nangong Wan in her arms.

"I am also Han Li, but a version that went back in time and abandoned the laws of time to cultivate the laws of reincarnation instead," the Reincarnation Palace Master revealed, but his explanation only served to further confound Wyrm 3.

"If you're Han Li, then who am I?" Han Li asked.

His mind had been reduced to an irrational mess, making it impossible for him to assess this situation with any degree of calmness or objectivity. He was unable to make sense of what he was seeing, but at the same time, he could feel a strange connection to the Reincarnation Palace Master, one that told him that the Reincarnation Palace Master was indeed another version of himself, rather than an avatar or a severed corpse soul.

Even though they had mastered completely different law powers, there was no mistaking this undeniable connection.

Chapter 1306: Two Lifetimes in One

"You are you, and I am me. Just like you, I was born in that rural village in the mortal realm, and I shared the same family and experiences as you. In the end, I was also able to ascend to the True Immortal Realm after overcoming countless hardships and transcending countless tribulations," the Reincarnation Palace Master revealed.

At this point, Han Li had finally managed to somewhat compose himself, and a possibility occurred to him.

"There's no way there can be two Han Lis in this world. Could it be that you went back in time to take a different path from mine through transmigration?"

In Han Li's eyes, the only possible explanation for this scenario would be if a future version of himself traveled back to this point in time through transmigration. However, that begged the question of how this supposed future self of his had mastered the laws of reincarnation.

Before the Reincarnation Palace Master had a chance to reply, Han Li shook his head as he shot down his own theory.

"No, that can't be right. If you had transmigrated back to this time period, then you'll inevitably be forced to return to your time period once you've exhausted your law threads, so there's no way you can be a future version of me."

"That's right. You and I are sharing two lifetimes in one, and you are a product of my transmigration," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

A puzzled look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this, but his befuddlement then quickly turned to rage.

Even though his cultivation journey had spanned countless millennia up to this point, he still recalled everything that he had experienced in the mortal realm and the Spirit Realm.

Memories of all of the people that he had encountered and the things that he had experienced were etched deep into his mind, yet if he were a product of the Reincarnation Palace Master's transmigration, then wouldn't that mean that he had been living a lie this entire time?

"There's no way any of that is true! You're cultivating the laws of reincarnation, so how could you possibly be capable of space-time transmigration? You must be lying to me! In fact, all of this must be an illusion!" Han Li yelled as he activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes to scrutinize his surroundings, but there was nothing to indicate that what he was witnessing was anything less than reality.

"Senior Vial Spirit, get me out of here! Transmigrate me to anywhere, just not here!" Han Li yelled internally, and he felt as if he were only just barely clinging onto a shred of sanity.

"Han Li!"

Right at this moment, the vial spirit's voice rang out in his mind in an authoritative manner, and Han Li was immediately snapped back to his senses.

"He's not lying to you. Technically speaking, I am also a product of his space-time transmigration. He transmigrated tens of millions of years back into the past, where another Han Li was born in that village, and that is who eventually grew up to become you," the vial spirit said, and hearing it corroborate the Reincarnation Palace Master's story felt like a stab to the heart for the Han Li.

"How did this happen?" he murmured in a dazed manner, having never so lost in his life.

"Just like you, I was born in the mortal realm with four spirit roots, and I was able to eventually reach the pinnacle in my cultivation of time law powers. In doing so, I was deemed a threat by Gu Huojin, and in our final showdown, I was defeated.

“Right as I was about to be killed, I injected all of the time law powers that I had accumulated throughout my lifetime into the Heaven Controlling Vial, and for the first time, it was truly able to reverse time, taking me all the way back to the very beginning," the Reincarnation Palace Master recounted with a reminiscent look in his eyes.

"It was thanks to this enormous influx of time law powers that I was able to attain sentience. However, at the time, I was only barely sentient, and it was only after the passage of an immeasurable period of time that I finally became the vial spirit that I am today," the vial spirit added.

At this point, Han Li had finally managed to compose himself, and he was silent for a long while before summarizing, "So that means that you and I are both separate, yet also one and the same, and we embarked on completely different cultivation journeys."

"You can think of it that way. It seems like due to my existence, many of your experiences diverged significantly from my own. For example, the Gan Rushuang that you should've encountered turned into Nangong Wan, and your ties with the Devil Realm, the Gray Realm, and the primordial land are far deeper than mine were.

“Ever since you reached the Immortal Realm, our experiences have diverged further and further, so it can almost be said that we've lived two different lifetimes," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

"How did you become the Reincarnation Palace Master?" Han Li asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"I transmigrated to the extremely distant past, long before you were born. I had lost all of my time law powers, taking me back to square one, and what was even more disheartening to me was that Gu Huojin was already the Time Dao Ancestor even back then.

“If I had continued to cultivate the laws of time, I would've only suffered the same fate, so I pursued the laws of reincarnation instead, and that's how I became who I am today," the Reincarnation Palace Master explained.

"Then what about me and my mother?" Wyrm 3 asked, and she was every bit just as shaken as Han Li.

The Reincarnation Palace Master turned to her and Nangong Wan, and a gentle look appeared in his eyes as he explained, "Gu Huojin found us not long after you were born, and your mother sacrificed herself in order to buy us time to get away. Before that, she sealed part of her reincarnation law powers in your body, while I used my time law powers to seal you in a jade pendant immortal treasure for your protection.

“In the end, Gu Huojin proved too formidable an adversary for me to overcome, so I injected all of my time law powers into the Heaven Controlling Vial, hoping to detonate it to take down Gu Huojin with me."

"I was with you at the time?" Wyrm 3 asked in an incredulous manner.

"You were. Back then, I had already lost all hope, yet right as I thought that you and I were going to perish, the vial spirit was born, alongside the Heaven Controlling Vial's ability to transmigrate through space and time. As a result, I was able to truly transmigrate to the distant past and avoid what had seemed like my inevitable fate," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"Did Wyrm 3 transmigrate with you?" Han Li asked.

"She did," the Reincarnation Palace Master confirmed with a nod.

After a long silence, Han Li exclaimed, "This is a completely ridiculous story! How do you expect me to believe any of this?"

Wyrm 3 also turned to the Reincarnation Palace Master with an incredulous expression.

"If Wyrm 3 had transmigrated all the way to the distant past with you, surely she would already be at a far superior cultivation base at this point, given her aptitude. Also, Gu Huojin is the one who stands at the pinnacle of the laws of time. If you're able to transmigrate through space and time, why is he unable to do the same?" Han Li interrogated.

"Before I answer your questions, let me raise a question to you: do you know exactly what the Heaven Controlling Vial is?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked.

Han Li was stumped by this question. It was one that he had been searching for an answer to for as long as the Heaven Controlling Vial had been in his possession.

"Truth be told, even to this day, I still don't know exactly what type of treasure the Heaven Controlling Vial is, and it contains more than just time law powers. Otherwise, even with all of time law powers injected into it, there's no way that it could've given rise to a vial spirit, and it certainly wouldn't have been able to gain an unheard-of ability like space-time transmigration," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

"You're telling me that even though Guo Huojin has reached the pinnacle of time law powers, that alone isn't enough to allow him to transmigrate through space and time, is that right?" Han Li asked.

"As the name itself entails, space-time transmigration incorporates both the powers of time and space, and even the power of reincarnation plays a role. Hence, I'm almost certain that the Heaven Controlling Vial is the only thing in all of the realms capable of space-time transmigration, which means that as long as the Heaven Controlling Vial remains in your possession, you'll be the only one capable of transmigrating through space and time," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

Even without raising any questions to the vial spirit, Han Li was already mostly convinced that the Reincarnation Palace Master's assertions were correct.

"As for Jiuzhen's fate, that concerned another Dao Ancestor by the name of Chen Tuan," the Reincarnation Palace Master continued.

Han Li had never heard of this name before, and a puzzled look flashed through his eyes.

"The Heavenly Court is led by the Time Dao Ancestor, Gu Huojin, and he and six other Dao Ancestors rule over the True Immortal Realm together, collectively known as the Seven Heavenly Dao Lords. Among them, the only other one that you've heard of is most likely Li Yuanjiu of the Nine Origins Temple.

“Chen Tuan is the Clairvoyance Dao Ancestor, the most mysterious figure of the seven," the Reincarnation Palace Master explained.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

All he knew about the laws of clairvoyance was that they were extremely mysterious and difficult to cultivate, so he had never imagined that there would be a Dao Ancestor of clairvoyance law powers.

"Following my transmigration, I lost all of my power, rendering me unable to use the Heaven Controlling Vial, and as a result, it was lost in the river of time. Without the protection of my law powers, I exhausted all of my immortal spiritual power warding off space-time turbulence, and I also became separated from Jiuzhen.

“I returned to a time period tens of millions of years before you were born, while Jiuzhen ended up in a time period close to the time of your birth. I had no choice but to settle down in a secluded mortal realm, and at the time, I had been stripped of my powers and treasures, reducing me to a mortal. Thanks to my past cultivation experience, I was able to embark on a new cultivation journey, and after what felt like an eternity, I was finally able to track down Jiuzhen and rescue her.

“At the time, I had already cultivated the laws of reincarnation to the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage and founded the Reincarnation Palace, so I undid her seal and sent her to carry out various missions across the immortal regions as Wyrm 3," the Reincarnation Palace Master recounted.

"Why didn't you tell me?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"If I had revealed to you that you were my daughter, then our fates would've become intertwined, and from that point onward, whenever Chen Tuan looked into my future, he would see you as well. The Heavenly Court is unable to find me, so they would've been sure to hunt you down instead to use you as leverage against me," the Reincarnation Palace Master explained as he turned to Wyrm 3 with a guilty look in his eyes.

Chapter 1307: Decision

Wyrm 3 was overcome by a myriad of emotions in the wake of this stunning revelation.

Many of the questions that had perplexed her over the years had finally been answered. She understood why the palace master had offered her so much care and guidance, why she had been given so much support by the Reincarnation Palace, and why her cultivation journey had been so smooth up to this point.

As it turned out, she had never been an orphan, and her father had always been by her side, caring for her from the shadows.

With that in mind, tears began to stream down her face, and Han Li was also slightly moved by this touching sight.

He couldn't imagine the pain of being unable to acknowledge one's own daughter over the course of tens of millions of years.

The Reincarnation Palace Master turned to Han Li as he sighed, "The same applied to you and Rushuang as well. I didn't dare to establish close ties with any of you for fear of Gu Huojin finding out."

"Then why have you suddenly revealed the truth and forced Rushuang's memories upon Wan'er?" Han Li asked.

"Things are different now. There's no need for me to hide the truth any longer. You've already witnessed my power just now. Once I've had time to make some preparations, I will exact my vengeance on Gu Huojin. Given how pragmatic and opportunistic you are, I'm sure you would've only been willing to join me after I've shown you my power," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

"You can get me involved all you want, but you should've never gotten Wan'er involved in this mess!" Han Li countered with a furious expression.

A cold look appeared in the Reincarnation Palace Master's eyes upon hearing this, and he said, "She is my wife and Jiuzhen's mother. I want her to see the demise of Gu Huojin and the "Heavenly Court with her own two eyes! I want to show her that the sacrifice that she made wasn't in vain!

"She's not Gan Rushuang! She is Nangong Wan, the one and only Nangong Wan in this world!" Han Li snapped.

"What right do you have to say that? Throughout my entire life, Rushuang has been the only woman I've held dear to my heart, yet what about you? You already have Violet Spirit, so don't go telling me about how Nangong Wan is your one and only!" the Reincarnation Palace Master countered in a cold voice.

Han Li had no response to this.

The Reincarnation Palace Master's demeanor softened a little as he said, "Right now, she still has Nangong Wan's memories, and she's only gained Rushuang's memories on top of that. Once she's witnessed my victory over Gu Huojin, I can take back Rushuang's memories and return her to Nangong Wan."

"It shouldn't be up to you or me whether she becomes Gan Rushuang or returns to being Nangong Wan. Instead, the decision should be hers," Han Li said.

"In that case, we'll let her make the decision when the time comes. The clairvoyance of the Heavenmend Sect is not to be underestimated. The fact that both of us are present in the same lifetime goes against the natural order, and you may be able to remain hidden for now, but that will no longer be the case once you reach the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage.

“Once Gu Huojin sets his sights on you, you'll be forced to make a decision of your own, whether to flee and hide, or to join me and defy our fate together," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

"With my current powers, getting involved in your conflict with Gu Huojin would be no different from committing suicide. There's a good chance that I'll meet my demise before I even reach the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage," Han Li said.

"Our experiences may be different, but both of us have experienced the same hardships, and even our personalities are very similar. On our little sister's wedding day, I returned to the village, but didn't reveal myself to anyone. It was on that day that I decided to sever all of my past karmic ties and dedicate myself solely to the path of cultivation," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

A reminiscent look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this. Many, many years ago, he had also returned to the village to witness the scene of his little sister stepping into her bridal sedan chair, and he had made the same resolution to himself.

He and the Reincarnation Palace Master were the same person, but it was as if they had become two different people. Despite that, some mysterious force, perhaps fate, had guided him to the True Immortal Realm and led him to also pursue the laws of time.

In the wake of all of these revelations, Han Li was left at a loss for how to assess his relationship with the Reincarnation Palace Master.

"I understand that this is all very difficult to process, but I've lived your life before, and I know what's in your future. Of course, your future may be very different due to my existence, but you know what happened to Miro. I tried to convince him to join our Reincarnation Palace, but he thought that he would be safe as long as he kept to himself. In other words, by helping me, you are also helping yourself," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

Han Li's mind was feeling very muddled, and after a long silence, he replied, "There are some things that I have to think through on my own."

"In that case, I won't keep you any longer," the Reincarnation Palace Master said. "Let's see what Rushuang chooses to do once she awakens. If she wants to go with you, then I won't force her to stay, but do you currently possess the ability to protect her?"

"There's no need to wait. Now that Wan'er has already gotten involved in all of this, I won't be able to protect her, so she'll be safer with you," Han Li said with a shake of his head.

"Alright," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

Han Li took a wistful, longing glance at Nangong Wan, then turned to depart.

"You came here to use the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate, did you not? Why not use it before you leave?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked, and Han Li turned back to face him upon hearing this.

"Jiuzhen, leave with your mother for now," the Reincarnation Palace Master instructed.

"Yes, Father," Wyrm 3 replied before making her way into the inner hall with Nangong Wan cradled in her arms.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the Reincarnation Palace Master withdrew his spirit domain, then said, "You can bring them in now."

Han Li immediately notified Weeping Soul and the others to come in through voice transmission, and by the time they entered the palace, he had already put on his conical bamboo hat again, reverting back into the mysterious Reincarnation Palace Master.

"Come with me," he said, then made his way toward the back of the hall.

Han Li made no effort to explain to Weeping Soul and the others what had happened, merely gesturing in silence for them to follow along.

Violet Spirit could tell that Han Li was not in a good mood, and Weeping Soul could also sense that something was amiss, but neither of them asked any questions.

Meanwhile, Shi Chuankong was struck by a sense of familiarity at the sight of the Reincarnation Palace Master, but he couldn't think of where they could've possibly met in the past.

Everyone followed the Reincarnation Palace Master to the back of the hall before entering that spacious underground area.

Upon arriving on the stone platform, everyone was greeted by the sight of the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate hovering up above and the dark red pond down below.

"The Six Paths Reincarnation Plate is not something that everyone can benefit from using. If one becomes excessively immersed in it and caught up in their past lives, then they could be weighed down by the burden of the cycle of reincarnation, thereby potentially resulting in a drop in cultivation base. Hence, it's up to you whether you want to use it," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

Hesitant looks appeared on the faces of Violet Spirit and the others upon hearing this, while for some reason, Jin Tong was looking overjoyed.

"I do not wish to be burdened by the memories of my past life, so I'm not going to use the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate," Weeping Soul declared, and everyone was rather taken aback to hear this.

The Reincarnation Palace Master took a glance at Weeping Soul, and a hint of approval flashed through his eyes.

After a brief hesitation, Violet Spirit stepped forward as she requested, "I wish to use the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate, Senior."

The Reincarnation Palace Master made no comment on her decision, and he merely pointed at the pond below the reincarnation plate as he instructed, "Go in there."

Violet Spirit strode over to the edge of the pond, then took a deep breath and lifted up the hem of her dress before slowly making her way inside.

To her surprise, the water wasn't very cold, and it quickly reached all the way up to her chest.

Violet Spirit felt her vision begin to blur, following which she fell back to float on the surface of the pond in an unconscious state.

The Reincarnation Palace Master joined his palms in front of his own chest as he began chanting an incantation, then cast an incantation seal onto the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate, upon which a burst of vast reincarnation power spread over its surface.

The Six Paths Reincarnation Plate began revolving rapidly as it released a pillar of red light to encompass Violet Spirit, and she slowly sank into the pond.

......

Around fifteen minutes later, a string of bubbles suddenly arose over the surface of the pond, and Violet Spirit sprang out from within before landing not far away from the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate.

Her entire body was soaked, and she was rooted to the spot as she stared blankly into space with a pair of unfocused eyes, as if she were peering into another lifetime.

Han Li appeared behind her in a flash, then laid a hand down onto her shoulder as he called out her name in a gentle voice.

Violet Spirit shuddered slightly as she turned to him before carefully scrutinizing his face as if she were seeing him for the very first time, and only then did her pupils slowly regain their focus.

"Han Li..." she called out in a gentle voice before suddenly throwing her arms around her and burying her face into his chest.

A myriad of emotions welled up in Han Li's heart as he looked down at her, and he reciprocated her embrace, encircling his arms around her in a delicate act of reassurance.

At this moment, Violet Spirit's clothes were soaked and pressed tightly against her skin, and upon noticing this, a faint blush immediately appeared on her face as she extricated herself out of Han Li's embrace, following which a burst of light flashed over her body to instantly dry out her waterlogged clothes.

Chapter 1308: Jin Tong’s Past Life

"Sorry about that," Violet Spirit apologized in an embarrassed manner.

"It's fine. How do you feel?" Han Li asked.

A slightly dejected look appeared on Violet Spirit's face in response to his question, and only upon seeing this did he notice that her cultivation base had plummeted from the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage back down to the mid-High Zenith Stage.

"Your cultivation base!" he exclaimed.

"It's fine," Violet Spirit said with a shake of her head, and she didn't appear overly surprised by this outcome.

"Her cultivation base was forcibly elevated, so her foundation wasn't very stable. Hence, it's no surprise that she's lost some ground after taking a trip through the cycle of reincarnation," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

Han Li cast an inquisitive gaze toward Violet Spirit upon hearing this, and she explained through voice transmission, "Daoist Xie used a secret technique to strip cultivators using similar cultivation arts to ours of their law powers before forcibly injecting those law powers into our bodies. That's how Shi Chuankong and I were able to make such significant strides in our cultivation. Hence, this is not necessarily a bad thing."

Han Li nodded in response, but at the same time, he couldn't help but wonder exactly what past memories she had seen through the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate. Whatever she had seen, it had to have had quite a profound effect on her to cause this drop in her cultivation base.

"Who's next?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked.

"I'll pass this time," Shi Chuankong said with slightly furrowed brows.

Han Li knew that Shi Chuankong's cultivation base had been elevated through the same illegitimate means as Violet Spirit, so he cautioned through voice transmission, "Brother Shi, I know that both you and Violet Spirit had your cultivation bases enhanced through the same method.

“With such an unstable foundation, your future cultivation could be compromised, so I don't think it's a bad idea for you to take this opportunity to consolidate your foundation, even if it means losing some cultivation base in the short term."

"If I accept a regression in my cultivation base now, who knows when I'll be able to return to the Great Encompassment Stage? Daoist Xie has told me that as long as I continue to work hard in my cultivation, I'll be able to gradually consolidate my newfound cultivation base over time, so that's what I plan to do."

Han Li made no further attempt at persuasion after hearing this.

"It looks like I'm the only one left then," Jin Tong said.

"You are the one who's most justified in using the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate out of everyone here," the Reincarnation Palace Master remarked.

Jin Tong wasted no time with words as she waded into the pond in an excited manner, and before long, she had also slipped into an unconscious state.

All of a sudden, she erupted out of the water with a loud gasp, only to discover that she was hovering in the air above a turbulent sea.

Immediately thereafter, she heard a thunderous, rumbling noise, and it was as if the entire surrounding space were about to be shaken apart.

Even though there were no true shockwaves sweeping toward her, she was still left feeling a little shaken and dazed.

Right at this moment, a cold and authoritative voice rang out in the heavens above like rumbling thunder.

"There's nowhere left for you to run, Qu Lin! If you continue to refuse to surrender, then you will be erased from existence!"

Jin Tong's ears were ringing from the deafening sound, and she hurriedly looked up to discover a gargantuan man standing several hundred kilometers away.

The man's entire body was as green and translucent as jade, and he stood hundreds of thousands of feet tall.

He had a head of short hair and a body of rippling muscle, while behind him was a yellow halo that was giving off a fiery glow, as well as bursts of earth law power fluctuations more formidable than any Jin Tong had ever felt before.

Looking at the gargantuan figure from afar, she was struck by the feeling that was staring at an almighty, ancient deity, one that possessed the power of all of the mountains under the heavens combined.

Is that a Dao Ancestor?

Jin Tong felt as if she had been plunged into a glacial pit, and for the first time in her existence, she learned what true pressure felt like. However, as opposed to evoking any fear, this sense of pressure only pushed her into an enraged state.

Right at this moment, a goading voice rang out from the other side of the sea.

"Come get me, Xuanyuan Jie! Try as you might, you'll never get me to submit to your Heavenly Court! If you didn't have all these pesky flies to hide behind, I would've already eaten you up like a snack!"

Jin Tong hurriedly cast her gaze in the direction that the voice was coming from, and right as she did so, the surface of the sea there bulged as an enormous entity rose up from the depths, raising gargantuan waves hundreds of thousands of feet tall.

Jin Tong was swept up by the massive waves, and she hurriedly rose up to a higher altitude.

From there, she was greeted by an astonishing sight.

As it turned out, what she had thought to have been the sea was actually a lost continent that was drifting through space, and the edges of the continent were very jagged and uneven, clearly indicating that it had been broken off by force.

All that remained of the clouds in the sky was a thin layer, and beyond that was a boundless, pitch-black space with thousands of powerful Heavenly Court cultivators littered throughout, all of whom were giving off tremendous earth law power fluctuations.

There was a layer of azure light around all of them, forming a gargantuan city in the heavens that looked as if it had been chiseled out a single, colossal piece of jade.

There were hundreds of incredibly thick chains hanging down outside the four sets of city gates, and they trailed all the way down to the broken continent below to connect it to the jade city.

This was an unfathomably powerful subjugation array, and it had clearly been set up as part of a meticulous plan.

Right at this moment, bursts of thunderous rumbling came ringing out incessantly from the continent down below, and the giant bulge that had emerged over the surface of the sea began to turn extremely murky.

At the same time, a series of enormous cracks began to appear on the edges of the broken continent, and it began to disintegrate bit by bit.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the continent finally completely shattered, and a golden beetle that was over a hundred thousand feet in size burst out of the giant bulge in the sea.

Its six golden wings were flapping incessantly, sending almighty whirlwinds sweeping through the air in all directions.

Jin Tong was immediately able to tell that this golden beetle was also a Gold Devouring Beetle, just like herself, but it possessed the cultivation base of a Dao Ancestor.

However, at the moment, the Gold Devouring Immortal's golden exoskeleton was severely ravaged and broken, and large chunks of its wings were missing. At the same time, enormous, jade chains were wound around all parts of its body, and they were the very same chains hanging down from the city above.

As soon as the golden beetle appeared, the chains hanging down from the jade city in the sky instantly stretched taut, and the entire city began to descend upon it.

At the same time, the azure giant by the name of Xuanyuan Jie stepped forward and raised a fist, and bands of green light converged from all directions, forming an enormous, green vortex that came crashing down upon the golden beetle.

The golden beetle remained completely unfazed as it rose up in a fearless manner to bite down onto Xuanyuan Jie's gargantuan fist.

A loud crack rang out as half of Xuanyuan Jie's arm exploded violently, and the jade chains bound to the golden beetle's body clattered and rattled incessantly from the resulting shockwaves.

At the same time, the jade city finally fell upon the golden beetle, upon which it began to glow with blinding, azure radiance.

The golden light around the golden beetle's body exploded, and countless golden scraps began peeling rapidly off its body like scraps of paint from an old and dilapidated wall, presenting a miserable sight to behold.

"Xuanyuan Jie, you're dreaming if you think you can claim my body! The day I return to the Heavenly Court is the day that you and those six other scoundrels meet your collective demise!" the golden beetle chortled as a burst of blinding, golden light appeared over its body, and a burst of incredibly fearsome shockwaves erupted in all directions.

A series of cracks appeared over the surface of the jade city as the almighty, golden shockwaves swept over it, and the hundreds of Heavenly Court cultivators within the city instantly perished as their bodies exploded into countless pieces.

"You're not getting away!" Xuanyuan Jie roared.

At this point, his destroyed arm had already fully regenerated, and he raised both hands to conjure up a huge, green net that encompassed the vast expanse of golden light.

Right at this moment, a tall and elegant woman appeared within the golden light, then raised her hands to the heavens before bringing them apart, tearing open the giant net and the jade city above.

Even the broken sky was parted by her almighty power, creating a gargantuan spatial rift.

Countless tiny rays of light that held swarms of infantile Gold Devouring Beetles surged into the spatial rift like a golden river, where they were then scattered in all directions by the spatial turbulence within the rift.

These beetles were like dandelion seeds, and no one knew where they were going to drift to.

Jin Tong could feel her own blood boiling in her veins as she witnessed this sobering scene. Only now had she come to learn that her previous incarnation had been forced to detonate her own body and scatter herself across the realms as individual swarms of Gold Devouring Beetles.

After the final ray of golden light faded away, the projection of the woman also began to gradually fade.

In a fit of fury, Xuanyuan Jie threw an almighty punch, unleashing a burst of unfathomably vast power that completely dashed the projection of the woman into smithereens.

The residual specks of golden light drifted down from the heavens on to Jin Tong before finally completely fading away.

Having just witnessed the tragic and unjust fate that had befallen her previous incarnation, Jin Tong was unable to contain her rage as she sped directly toward Xuanyuan Jie as a streak of golden light.

However, the space up ahead suddenly began to ripple and warp, and she flew headfirst into it, following which the entire world began to spin around her in an indistinguishable blur.

By the time she returned to her senses, she found herself floating face-up in the pond, and the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate above had come to a rest.

Chapter 1309: Parting Ways

Jin Tong silently stood up in the pond, and only after standing still on the spot for a moment did she emerge from the pond, following which a burst of golden light flashed over her body to instantly evaporate the water in her clothes.

To Han Li's astonishment, he discovered that she had reached the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, albeit, judging from her aura, her cultivation base was still a little unstable.

Furthermore, what was even more alarming to him was the immense killing intent that had crept into her aura.

"It looks like you've seen how your past incarnation met her demise," the Reincarnation Palace Master remarked.

Jin Tong instantly turned to him upon hearing this, and her eyes were like a pair of daggers as she asked, "You know about my past?"

Her voice had become far lower and more mature than before.

"How do you feel right now, Jin Tong?" Han Li asked.

"My name is Qu Lin!" she snapped as she turned a cold gaze to Han Li.

Her expression then softened a little as she sighed, "At least, that was once my name."

"Dao Ancestor Qu Lin was once the ruler of all arthropods across the True Immortal Realm, but she was slain by the Earth Dao Ancestor, Xuanyuan Jie, for her refusal to submit to the Heavenly Court. Right before she passed, she split her own body into countless Gold Devouring Beetles, which were scattered across all of the realms," the Reincarnation Palace recounted.

Everyone was very much taken aback to hear about this chapter in Jin Tong's past.

"Xuanyuan Jie is one of the Seven Heavenly Dao Lords, right?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"That's right. He is Gu Huojin's most loyal subordinate, and after slaying Dao Ancestor Qu Lin, he instructed his forces to hunt down all of the arthropods in the True Immortal Realm. The nine arthropod monarchs under Dao Ancestor Qu Lin were all killed by him, and in the wake of his campaign, what little remained of the arthropods was forced to flee to the lower realms. Since then, countless eons have passed, and they've already faded into legend."

"Xuanyuan Jie, you'll pay for what you've done!" Jin Tong spat through gritted teeth as she clenched her fists tightly.

She then heaved a slightly deflated sigh as she said, "Forget it, just call me Jin Tong for now. Even though I've recovered my memories, I'm still not used to the name Qu Lin. I'll reclaim my name once I've slain Xuanyuan Jie."

Right at this moment, Shi Chuankong suddenly asked, "Why is it that Jin Tong has already reached the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, but she didn't have to sever a corpse soul to get there?"

Only then did everyone else come to realize that this was indeed the case, and they turned to the Reincarnation Palace Master for an explanation.

"She's different from the average cultivator in that she's a spirit insect that was nurtured by heaven and earth. On top of that, she was born with mastery over the laws of devouring, which allows her to elevate her cultivation base by devouring her brethren.

“Additionally, she's a part of a Dao Ancestor to begin with, so she doesn't need to sever any corpse souls. Once all of the Gold Devouring Beetles in existence come together again, she'll be able to regain her power as a Dao Ancestor," the Reincarnation Palace Master explained.

"What are your plans from here onward?" Han Li asked.

"I'm going to hunt down the rest of my brethren, then seek out vengeance against Xuanyuan Jie," Jin Tong replied without any hesitation, and Han Li nodded in approval of this plan.

He could see that Jin Tong no longer had the heart of a child that she once did.

Jin Tong hesitated momentarily, then continued, "This is where we part ways. I'll try to repay you for everything you've done for me if the opportunity arises."

Han Li knew that this separation was going to be different from their previous separations, and with that in mind, he couldn't help but feel a sense of sorrow.

Even so, he still nodded as he said, "I have my own path to walk as well, we are already very fortunate to have been able to accompany one another for so long. Make sure to look after yourself now that you're on your own."

Jin Tong nodded in response, then departed without another word.

Han Li watched her leave until she was out of sight, yet right as he was about to turn his gaze back to Weeping Soul and the others, Jin Tong's voice suddenly rang out from afar.

"I'll come back to you once I've recovered my powers and exacted my revenge, Uncle!"

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

"A mid-Great Encompassment Stage Gold Devouring Immortal is a powerful ally. You're not going to try to convince her to stay?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked.

"Why would I do that? She'll come back when she's ready," Han Li replied.

The Reincarnation Palace Master nodded in response, then said, "Now that all of you who wished to use the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate have had a chance to do so, it's time for you to leave."

Han Li did as they were told, and as they emerged from the underground palace, they discovered that the crimson clouds in the sky and the ever-present Six Paths Gale winds had all vanished.

"Let's go," Han Li said, and Violet Spirit and Shi Chuankong nodded in response before preparing to depart with him, but Weeping Soul remained where she was.

"Master, I want to stay in the underworld for a while," Weeping Soul said.

"Why is that?" Han Li asked.

"During my time with you, I've witnessed so many powerful cultivators, and the more I see, the more I come to realize just how inept I am. If I continue to remain by your side, eventually, you'll leave me far behind, and I'll become nothing more than a hindrance to you. The underworld is a place that's more suited to my cultivation, so I want to stay here and enhance my own powers before I return to your side," Weeping Soul replied.

"Don't think of yourself as a hindrance, you've been an incredible help to me ever since our reunion in the Gray Realm. Having said that, I agree that the underworld is better for your cultivation than the True Immortal Realm, so I'll allow you to stay here. I just hope that the day of our reunion won't be too far away," Han Li said with a smile.

"Thank you, Master," Weeping Soul said with an earnest bow.

Han Li strode over to Weeping Soul, then gently pressed a hand against her forehead as he said through voice transmission, "I'll leave a wisp of my spiritual sense with you. If you encounter any danger, activate that wisp of spiritual sense, and I'll be sure to come to your aid as quickly as I can."

"I can't constantly remain under your protection, Master," Weeping Soul protested. "Only by fending for myself can I..."

"Don't be so stubborn," Han Li interjected. "This is a matter of life and death, so there must be a safety net put in place."

Weeping Soul faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded firmly in response.

With that, Han Li's trio and Weeping Soul went their separate ways.

......

Several months flew by in a flash.

It was a serene and peaceful morning in the Black Wind Sea, but the entire area was enshrouded in a layer of white mist, giving everything an indistinct appearance.

No more than ten thousand feet away from this area of the Black Wind Sea was an entirely different scene.

There, the sky was filled with dark clouds, and enormous gusts of black yin wind were sweeping through heaven and earth, with the smallest ones only the size of houses, while the largest ones were hundreds of thousands of feet in size.

The sound of crashing waves and ghostly howls could be heard ringing out incessantly, and right at this moment, a spirit boat that was encompassed within a golden spirit domain slowly emerged from a vast tornado of black yin wind.

The passengers of the spirit boat were none other than Han Li, Violet Spirit, and Shi Chuankong, who had just returned from the underworld.

At the moment, all three of them were silent and lost in their own thoughts.

Right at this moment, Han Li raised an eyebrow ever so slightly.

Violet Spirit immediately noticed this and asked through voice transmission, "What's wrong, Brother Han?"

"We've been surrounded by enemy cultivators, and their leader is at least at the late-Great Encompassment Stage," Han Li replied.

Both Violet Spirit and Shi Chuankong maintained calm and oblivious facades as the latter asked, "What should we do?"

"There's no need to do anything, let's just keep going for now. When it comes time to make a move, I'll give a signal, and you two can take to the sky to see if you can break through the surrounding restrictions. If you can, then leave. If not, then do your best to get as far away from me as possible," Han Li replied.

"Alright," Shi Chuankong immediately replied.

"Make sure to be careful," Violet Spirit cautioned.

In the blink of an eye, the spirit boat had already flown several thousand more kilometers, at which point Han Li suddenly yelled, "Go!"

Shi Chuankong and Violet Spirit immediately abandoned the spirit boat as they sprang up into the air.

In the next instant, enormous waves suddenly began sweeping over the surface of the sea, which had been quite tranquil just a moment ago, and a dark shadow that was over a hundred thousand feet in size rose up from the depths like a mountain.

The shadow had been lurking in the sea for quite some time, and now that it had emerged, it immediately parted the sea to create an enormous trench.

Han Li's spirit boat was without a pilot, and it was situated directly above the trench, so it immediately fell inside.

"What a big fish..." Han Li remarked to himself as he looked down at the giant shadow below.

As it turned out, the shadow that had emerged from the depths was a gargantuan whale with black scales over its entire body. Its mouth was filled with sharp fangs, and deep within its oral cavity was a huge, black vortex that was giving off a foul stench.

There was also a corkscrew-shaped, black horn growing out of the whale's head, and it was giving off a metallic sheen.

A thin man in a suit of white armor was standing atop the whale's back, holding onto its horn with one hand and a blue spear in the other as he looked up at Han Li with a faint smile on his face.

Chapter 1310: Foul Mood

The man standing atop the giant whale's back had a very pale complexion with a head of long and slightly curly blond hair.

There was a hint of redness in his eyes, making it appear as if he were in need of some rest, but his aura was extremely formidable, putting his late-Great Encompassment Stage cultivation base on full display.

"By big fish, are you referring to me or this spirit pet of mine?" the young man asked with a cold grin.

Despite his rather effeminate appearance, his voice was quite masculine.

"You can think of it as whichever one you like," Han Li replied in a casual manner as he took a glance up at the sky.

Just as he had feared, Violet Spirit and Shi Chuankong were unable to get away, having been stopped in their tracks by a spirit domain and several hundred Heavenly Court cultivators, all of which appeared to have been immortal envoys.

"Whichever one it is, it doesn't change the fact that you're going to be gobbled up like a small fry," the young man said in an indifferent manner.

"May I ask your name, Fellow Daoist?" Han Li asked.

"My name is Shui Changtian, and I've been ordered to capture you. Are you going to surrender yourself or make me capture you by force? Before you make your decision, let me tell you that not a single person that's been captured by my water prison hasn't lived to regret it," the young man said with a smile.

"That's a fine name, fit for a fine burial at sea," Han Li remarked, [1] then swept a sleeve through the air to release his seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, all of which came raining down onto the sea below.

Countless arcs of golden lightning erupted out of the swords before coming together to form an enormous sword array with a sea of lightning crashing and churning within.

A deafening thunderclap rang out as countless pillars of lightning as thick as water vats came crashing down from the heavens, and the giant whale let loose a low call as it reflexively sank a little into the water, seemingly quite fearful of these pillars of lightning.

"There's no need to fear, it's just a bit of Cardinal Heavenly Lightning," Shui Changtian said in a reassuring manner, then released his spear before thrusting a palm down toward the surface of the sea below.

A burst of dull rumbling rang out from the seabed, and all of the seawater within a radius of hundreds of thousands of kilometers instantly converged toward this area in a frenzy.

Countless swirling water spouts rose up around Shui Changtian to clash against the pillars of lightning crashing down from above, and a string of deafening explosions rang out as the entire area was filled with violent seawater and explosive golden lightning.

Shui Changtian looked up into the sky to see a dazzling ball of golden light, standing within which was Han Li, who had his arms crossed and was looking down at Shui Changtian with a cold expression.

He then took a glance in Violet Spirit and Shi Chuankong's direction, and at this point, they had already flown to hundreds of thousands of kilometers away, with all of the Heavenly Court cultivators hot on their trail.

With both of them a safe distance away, Han Li turned his gaze back to Shui Changtian as he said in a cold voice, "I'm in a very foul mood right now, so you've come to me at a very unfortunate time."

Immediately thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the air to release his time spirit domain, which encompassed the entire surrounding area within a radius of thousands of kilometers.

A bright moon and a bed of stars instantly appeared in the sky, while an enormous mountain range rose up from the seabed. Growing atop the mountain was a lush forest, and there was also a winding river that flowed into the sea.

However, the water in the river was fundamentally different from the water in the sea, and the former floated on top of the latter like a layer of oil on water.

Shui Changtian's brows furrowed tightly upon sensing the tremendous might of Han Li's Oneness Tier spirit domain, and he realized that he wasn't as well prepared as he should've been.

Having said that, this was hardly his fault, given that he had been told that Han Li was only at the early-Great Encompassment Stage, when in reality, he was clearly at the pinnacle of the mid-Great Encompassment Stage.

"I'm surprised that our Heavenly Court has allowed you to cultivate the laws of time to this extent, but unfortunately, you were doomed from the moment you embarked on this path," Shui Changtian said as a layer of blue light appeared over his body to ward off the power of Han Li's spirit domain.

He grabbed onto his spear again before swinging it through the air in a fluid motion, and his movements didn't appear to have been hampered at all by Han Li's time law powers.

With a flick of his wrist, the tip of his spear gently tapped against the surface of the sea below, and an enormous, blue halo instantly appeared before proliferating outward in all directions.

In the blink of an eye, the turbulent sea had become completely still, as if an almighty, invisible hand had just smoothed over its surface.

At the same time, the air currents flowing over the sea fell completely still, and even the flow of the world's origin qi in the area had become stagnant.

Han Li made a beckoning motion, and his seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly flew back to him before combining into one, and there were still arcs of golden lightning flashing over its surface, as if it were raring for more.

"Impressive. Somehow, you're able to emulate the power of spatial laws with your water law powers," Han Li remarked.

"I have the advantage of the natural environment on my side. This Black Wind Sea is far smaller than even the smallest sea in our Middle Earth Immortal Region, but I can still make use of it with my sea law powers, and it'll be more than enough for me to bring you down," Shui Changtian replied with a smile.

He then pointed his spear directly at Han Li from afar, and the entire sea was instantly split into two halves. The sea on Han Li's side remained as calm and still as before, while gargantuan, cataclysmic waves had appeared over the surface of the sea behind Shui Changtian, and they were crashing directly toward Han Li.

Han Li remained completely unfazed as he took a step forward before sweeping a sleeve through the air, and the massive mountain range behind him instantly rose up from the surface of the sea, then flew over his head before crashing into the oncoming barrage of enormous waves.

The waves crashed into the lush mountain range, and Han Li's time law powers instantly took effect, suspending the waves in mid-air to form an overhanging wall of water.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li rose up into the air to land on the tallest peak in the mountain range, then launched himself forward from there as he swung his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword through the air.

An enormous bolt of golden lightning came crashing down from the heavens, then transformed into a golden lightning sword projection that was dozens of kilometers in length before crashing down onto the surface of the sea below.

The sea was instantly parted down the middle to reveal the seabed below, and the golden sword projection didn't stop there as it cleaved an enormous, bottomless trench into the seabed, while gargantuan waves swept over the sea in all directions, quickly reaching tens of thousands of kilometers away.

The Heavenly Court cultivators had just surrounded Shi Chuankong and Violet Spirit, but their formation was thrown into a state of disarray by the oncoming waves.

Shi Chuankong and Violet Spirit immediately pounced on the opportunity to slay several immortal envoys and break free from the encirclement.

Violet Spirit took a glance in Han Li's direction to discover that an incredibly dense cloud of water vapor had taken shape in that direction, making it impossible for her to see him.

"Fellow Daoist Han should be fine on his own. Compared with him, we're the ones who need to be careful," Shi Chuankong cautioned.

Violet Spirit knew that he was right, but she still couldn't help but feel a little concerned for Han Li. Ever since they left the underworld, she could sense that he had been in a rather tumultuous state of mind.

Despite her concerns, she didn't dare to allow herself to get distracted, and she returned her full attention to the battle at hand. Otherwise, if they were overwhelmed and required Han Li to rescue them, then they would only be placing him in even more peril.

The sword strike unleashed by Han Li was extremely formidable, comparable in power to what he had previously been able to unleash using the Almighty Sword Array, but it had failed to strike its target as Shui Changtian was suddenly nowhere to be seen.

At this moment, it felt as if the entire sea were filled with Shui Changtian's aura, making it impossible for Han Li to track down his precise location.

Right at this moment, a gargantuan vortex suddenly appeared over the surface of the sea directly beneath Han Li, and it was giving tremendous suction force.

Han Li immediately rose up higher into the sky, but the vortex rose up along with him, threatening to devour him like the mouth of some colossal predator.

Swept up in the vortex, violent currents converged toward Han Li, exerting compressional force upon him from all directions.

A blue vortex had appeared around each of his hands and feet, and they were so powerful that Han Li was unable to struggle free from them. At the same time, the blue vortexes were moving away in different directions, attempting to tear his body apart.

Furthermore, tiny, corkscrew-shaped streams of water were surging into his orifices in a frenzy, and he was able to close his eyes and mouth to shut them out, but he was unable to cover his ears and nose with his hands, so the streams of water were able to force their way in.

Han Li felt a sharp pain in his ears and nostrils as streams of water that were imbued with sea law powers infiltrated his body.

[1]. Shui Chuangtian's surname 水 literally translates to water, hence the comment about how it's fitting for him to meet his demise at sea.

[Back]

Translator's Thoughts

Chapter 1311: Power of the Sea

Right at this moment, Shui Changtian reappeared in front of Han Li, and he rested the tip of his spear against Han Li's glabella as he said, "Seawater has already entered your internal organs, so surrender now, or I'll squeeze your heart to a pulp, then punch your liver, spleen, lungs, and kidneys full of holes. Trust me, that's something that you don't want to experience."

"Go ahead and try," Han Li challenged as he looked back at Shui Changtian with not even the slightest hint of fear in his eyes.

Shui Changtian's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he raised a hand before clenching it into a fist, but that did nothing.

"What's going on?" he exclaimed with a surprised expression.

"How much more seawater can you draw upon?" Han Li asked as he casually shook off the blue vortexes that were clinging onto him.

"It's that river!" Shui Changtian exclaimed as a look of realization appeared on his face.

The time law powers from Han Li's river of time had already seeped into the surrounding seawater, so it was naturally no longer under Shui Changtian's control.

Shui Changtian let loose a loud roar as a burst of blue light surged out of his body before flowing into his spear, and a ball of blinding, blue light shot out of the tip of the spear before exploding right in front of Han Li's head.

However, Han Li was prepared for this, having already channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, all one thousand eight hundred of his profound acupoints had lit up, while a layer of hexagonal scales had appeared over his skin.

A thunderous explosion rang out as all of the seawater within a radius of thousands of kilometers was instantly vaporized, while devastating shockwaves erupted through the air in all directions, sweeping up waves as tall as mountains while also scattering even the clouds in the sky.

Shi Chuankong looked up to discover that the spirit domain looming over the area had been withdrawn at some point, and he hurriedly grabbed onto Violet Spirit before teleporting both of them tens of thousands of kilometers away in the blink of an eye using a spatial secret technique.

The Heavenly Court cultivators were not so fortunate, and they were struck by the enormous waves before tumbling into the sea, with some of the weaker ones among them knocked unconscious on the spot.

On this day, the entire Black Wind Sea was thrown into a state of disarray. Even Dark Veil Island, which was almost on the other side of the Black Wind Sea, had been forced to deal with unprecedented tsunamis, and an immeasurable amount of damage would've been incurred had it not been for the timely activation of the island's protective array.

In the wake of the explosion, the seawater had evaporated to reveal the parched seabed down below, and there was a powerful wall of energy keeping the seawater from gushing back into the affected site.

Han Li was standing on the ridge of a broken mountain on the seabed, and the scales on his body were gradually receding. His forehead has been reduced to a mass of bloody and mangled flesh, making it appear as if he had suffered very severe injuries, but in reality, it was only a minor concern.

A projection of the Twin Births Tree appeared over his glabella, and the flesh on his forehead quickly began to heal.

Thousands of kilometers away, the mountain range formed by Han Li's spirit domain was still standing, and vines were sprouting out of the forest formed by the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree in a frenzy before wrapping themselves around Shui Changtian's ankles.

Veins were bulging on Shui Changtian's forehead as he struggled with all his might to free himself, but his movements had become extremely slow and sluggish.

As it turned out, the golden moon had descended to hover in the air behind him, and it was giving off countless rays of golden light.

Han Li flew over to Shui Changtian, then swung his sword down upon the latter's head without any hesitation.

"No! You can't kill me!" Shui Changtian yelled as a fearful look flashed through his eyes.

However, Han Li paid him no heed as he swung his sword down in a swift and forceful motion, and the blade of the sword sliced into Shui Changtian's body with ease.

However, in the instant that the sword made contact with Shui Changtian, his body suddenly liquefied before enveloping the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

Han Li harrumphed coldly upon seeing this, and a burst of formidable sword qi and golden lightning erupted out of the sword at his behest, instantly pulverizing Shui Changtian's liquefied body.

He then cast his gaze into the distance as he mused to himself, "As expected, late-Great Encompassment cultivators are not so easy to kill."

Thousands of kilometers away, a humanoid form began to take shape from the water vapor in the air, and in the blink of an eye, Shui Changtian was back.

"You've successfully enraged me, Han Li. I gave you the option to surrender, but that option is no longer open to you now," Shui Changtian declared with a furious expression.

"You're not very quick to catch on, are you?" Han Li scoffed.

Shui Changtian faltered slightly upon hearing this, then inspected his own internal condition to discover that there was nothing amiss aside from the fact that he had suffered some cultivation base regression.

"Quit trying to bluff me! I..."

All of a sudden, his voice abruptly cut off as an incredulous look appeared on his face.

"How could this be? How has my cultivation base regressed by this much? There shouldn't have been this much regression even if my body was destroyed by you once!" he exclaimed in an alarmed voice.

Han Li offered no explanation as he looked back at Shui Changtian with a cold sneer.

Having spent so much time in Han Li's Five Elemental Illusory World, his cultivation base was naturally going to suffer a severe regression.

"Regardless of what you've done, as long as we're still at sea, I can never be defeated!" Shui Changtian declared as he forcibly composed himself, then rose up into the air before making a strange hand seal.

A ring of blue light began to take shape around him, and a series of swirling vortexes began to converge toward him from behind.

At the same time, a wave was rapidly approaching from the distant horizon, and the giant black whale was racing along at the peak of the wave.

An almighty splash rang out as an enormous vortex of water appeared beneath Shui Changtian before rising up into the sky to surge into his body.

His body instantly turned a bright blue color, and a suit of blue water armor also appeared around him. At the same time, his aura was rapidly elevating, and he quickly regained all of the cultivation base that had been stripped from him by the Five Elemental Illusory World.

All of the seawater within a radius of close to a hundred thousand kilometers was sucked dry, leaving behind a vast expanse of parched earth that was littered with the dried and withered remains of marine demon beasts, including those of the black whale.

Absorbing power directly from the sea like this was clearly very strenuous on Shui Changtian, and he swelled to over a hundred thousand feet tall, but blue cracks had also begun to appear over his body.

His aura had already reached the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage, yet he still wasn't satisfied, continuing to draw upon more and more of the power of the sea, and Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this.

All of a sudden, bursts of golden ripples surged out of his body, instantly spreading over a radius of hundreds of thousands of kilometers.

A blazing fireball that was over a hundred thousand feet in size came plummeting out of the sky, and it was giving off such intense heat that the air temperature in the entire area was instantly raised by several thousandfold.

The seawater that was converging toward Shui Changtian was evaporated by the scorching heat before it was able to reach him, and the entire seabed was quickly reduced to a parched desert.

All of a sudden, Shui Changtian found himself unable to draw upon any more power from the sea, and his water-attribute law powers also began to rapidly dissipate in the unbearable heat.

"This has to be an illusion!" he exclaimed in an incredulous manner.

"An illusion? Sure, you can think of it as that if you want," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"No, that's not right. No illusion, no matter how powerful, would be able to affect my law powers! Aren't you cultivating the laws of time? How are you capable of something like this? " Shui Changtian exclaimed as a hint of panic began to creep into his voice.

Han Li offered no explanation as the gargantuan fireball continued to plummet toward Shui Changtian from above.

"So be it. It's not like you stand any chance against me at my current cultivation base anyway," Shui Changtian sighed, then brought his hands apart as if he were simulating the act of drawing a bow.

An enormous, blue bow instantly appeared in his grasp, with an equally enormous arrow nocked on its string. Upon closer inspection, it was clear that the arrow was actually the blue spear that he had been wielding earlier.

As he drew back the bowstring, bursts of immense law powers instantly began to surge into the arrow, and a vortex of blue light emerged from its tip.

The arrow was then let loose with a piercing whistling sound, leaving clusters of black spatial rifts in its wake.

The blazing fireball up above was torn apart and exploded into countless far smaller fireballs, while the arrow continued to race toward Han Li at an extraordinary speed.

Han Li made no effort to evade the arrow as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, and all his one thousand eight hundred profound acupoints lit up as he swung his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword through the air.

Countless arcs of golden lightning erupted out of the sword, forming a gargantuan, golden sword projection that clashed against the blue arrow.

An deafening boom rang out as both the arrow and the sword projection exploded upon impact, and a colossal spatial rift was left behind in the wake of the explosion, resembling the cavernous mouth of some unspeakable leviathan.

Right at this moment, Han Li flew through the air below the spatial rift with his sword aimed directly at the heart of Shui Changtian's giant body.

Chapter 1312: Seclusion in the Extraheavensphere

Shui Changtian was already prepared for an attack from Han Li, and in retaliation, he swung a palm down upon him, attempting to swat him out of the sky like a bug.

His palm descended with incredible speed and the fearsome power of a tsunami, but it failed to strike its target as Han Li abruptly vanished in a wraith-like manner before reappearing behind him in the form of a devilish deity with three heads and six arms, standing at over ten thousand feet tall.

It's six arms held terrifying power, and it swung its fists through the air in a rapidfire barrage.

Countless fist projections came crashing down upon Shui Changtian's body, producing a string of deafening booms rang out in such rapid succession that it culminated in one continuous and unbroken chorus of rumbling.

The barrage was so ferocious that Shui Changtian was unable to even get away, and his suit of blue water armor was instantly destroyed, while his enormous body toppled over like a mountain.

All that could be heard was the sound of Han Li's falling fists, and vast clouds of water vapor rose up from Shui Changtian's body, permeating throughout the entire surrounding area in a radius of hundreds of thousands of kilometers.

Violet Spirit and the others were already extremely far away at this point, yet the sound was still deafening even to them, and both sides reflexively stopped what they were doing to see what was happening.

After what seemed like an eternity, the rumbling finally died down.

As the dust settled, it was revealed that Han Li had already reverted back to his human form, and laying at his feet was a mangled body that was only just barely recognizable as one that belonged to a human.

In the face of Han Li's terrifying physical prowess, Shui Changtian's Great Encompassment Stage body had been pounded to a pulp.

After unleashing that ferocious barrage, much of the pent-up negative emotions in Han Li's heart had been vented, and he bent down to pick up a storage bracelet from Shui Changtian's body, then looked into the surrounding as he suddenly smiled and said, "So you still had one more trick up your sleeve."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the surrounding space warped slightly before a series of narrow streets began to take shape before his eyes, and it was as if he had been teleported to a mortal city.

The surrounding streets were very bustling and rowdy, and Han Li could even smell the aroma of freshly cooked steamed buns wafting out of a nearby shop.

"You've concealed yourself quite well," Han Li remarked with a smile, then suddenly inhaled deeply before blowing out a forceful breath.

A fierce gust of wind swept through the air, and the entire city dissipated like the illusion that it was.

Meanwhile, Shui Changtian's soul had already fled to tens of thousands of kilometers away.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li released a streak of golden sword qi that was enveloped in time law powers, and it instantly vanished into the distance.

Immediately thereafter, an anguished wail rang out, marking the demise of Shui Changtian.

The other Heavenly Court cultivators were horrified to see this, and they hurriedly fled the scene.

Shi Chuankong and Violet Spirit made no effort to stop them as they flew over to Han Li's side, right as his Mantra Domain faded away to reveal the seabed.

The surrounding seawater gushed inward, and by the time the chasm was filled, the sea level had noticeably dropped.

Violet Spirit was very relieved to see that Han Li was unharmed, and she sighed, "You've become more powerful than I could've ever imagined, Brother Han."

"It's still not enough," Han Li said.

"I didn't think we'd be ambushed as soon as we returned to the True Immortal Realm. It looks like there's going to be more trouble to come," Shi Chuankong said in a concerned manner.

"That's not really anything unexpected," Han Li said with a smile. "Do you have any plans from here?"

"I'm planning to return to the Devil Realm," Shi Chuankong sighed.

"There's been a great deal of unrest in the True Immortal Realm of late, so given your status, it would indeed be safer to return to the Devil Realm," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Why don't you come to the Devil Realm as well, Fellow Daoist Han? Uncle Xie has already left the Scalptia Spatial Domain and conquered close to half of the Devil Realm. Under his protection, you won't have to worry about being hunted by the Heavenly Court," Shi Chuankong suggested.

"It's fine, I can fend for myself. Right now, all I want is to find a place to cultivate in peace, and I have no desire to get swept up in any other conflicts," Han Li said as he took a meaningful glance at Shi Chuankong.

A slightly sheepish look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face. He had indeed invited Han Li to the Devil Realm with the intention of recruiting him as an ally.

"In that case, it looks like we'll have to part ways here as well, Fellow Daoist Han. What are your plans, Violet Spirit? Are you going to return to the Devil Realm as well?" Shi Chuankong asked.

Violet Spirit turned to Han Li, seemingly to ask his opinion on the matter.

"Like I said, the True Immortal Realm is a very unsafe place right now, so I think you should return to the Devil Realm with Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li said.

"What about you?" Violet Spirit asked.

"Wan'er is currently in the Reincarnation Palace, so that's where I'll go," Han Li replied.

"You're going back to the Reincarnation Palace?" Violet Spirit asked as her brows furrowed slightly.

"Please don't make any rash decisions, Fellow Daoist Han! The Reincarnation Palace is powerful enough to stand toe to toe with the Heavenly Court, and we've all personally witnessed the Reincarnation Palace Master's powers," Shi Chuankong hurriedly said in an alarmed manner.

"I won't do anything reckless. At the very least, I have to reach the late-Great Encompassment Stage before I make a move," Han Li replied.

Given that both of them were cultivating one of the three paramount laws, Han Li couldn't expect to overcome the Recinarnation Palace Master at an inferior cultivation base as he could with other cultivators.

The Reincarnation Palace Master himself was only at the late-Great Encompassment Stage, yet he had been able to crush Bone Emperor with ease.

The more Han Li pursued the cultivation of the laws of time, the more he came to understand just how fearsome time law powers were, and he had a feeling that he would undergo another drastic evolution upon reaching the late-Great Encompassment Stage.

"I want to stay with you," Violet Spirit suddenly said.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"It's not safe to be with me right now. You should..."

"I wasn't able to stay by your side in the mortal realm or the Spirit Realm, and that's always been something that I've regretted, so please let me stay with you from now on," Violet Spirit interjected with an imploring look in her eyes.

Han Li's expression softened a little upon hearing this, and he nodded in response.

He had also felt rather indebted to Violet Spirit as he had never been able to stay with her for an extended period of time.

A bright smile appeared on Violet Spirit's face upon seeing this, and the entire world seemed to have been lit up by her beauty.

"In that case, I'll return to the Devil Realm on my own, and I'll inform Uncle Xie of your decision. May we meet again," Shi Chuankong said as he cupped his fist in a salute, and a barely detectable hint of dejection flashed through his eyes.

"Look after yourself," Han Li said as he returned the salute.

Shi Chuankong's gaze lingered on Violet Spirit for a moment, following which he sped away as a streak of silver light.

Despite Shi Chuankong's best efforts to hide his feelings, Han Li and Violet Spirit had naturally caught on to some of the telltale signs.

"Fellow Daoist Shi has helped me a lot in the Devil Realm, but I have no entanglements with him," Violet Spirit said.

"Of course, I never suspected you in the first place," Han Li said with a faint smile.

He then looked around momentarily before suggesting, "Let's get out of here as well."

With a sweep of his sleeve, a burst of golden light was released to sweep up Violet Spirit, following which he flew directly up into the sky.

"Where are we going, Brother Han?" Violet Spirit asked in a surprised manner.

"To somewhere beyond the heavens," Han Li replied with a faint smile, and before long, the two of them had passed through the Ethersphere to reach the Astralsphere.

Countless gusts of astral wind were sweeping through the air, and Violet Spirit couldn't help but feel a little fearful upon seeing this.

However, Han Li remained completely unfazed as he continued to fly onward while telling Violet Spirit about the three spheres beyond the visible sky.

Waves of golden ripples were emanating from his body, and all of the astral winds that came into contact with them were instantly stopped cold in their tracks, allowing Han Li to fly along without any degree of deceleration.

Before long, the two of them had reached the Extraheavensphere.

The black space was filled with countless asteroids and all types of chaotic energy storms, presenting a spectacular sight that stunned Violet Spirit into silence.

After a long silence, she turned to Han Li with an amazed expression as she said, "I never imagined that a place like this existed beyond the heavens. Why did you bring me here?"

"We're going to cultivate in seclusion here. If any of the Dao Ancestors of the Heavenly Court or the Reincarnation Palace try to track us down, we won't be safe from them no matter where we go under the heavens. Only in the Extraheavensphere can we ensure that we won't be found," Han Li replied.

"I see, but this place looks fraught with peril. Can we really go into seclusion here?" Violet Spirit asked in a concerned manner.

"Leave that to me," Han Li said with a smile, then continued onward while scouring his surroundings with his tremendous spiritual sense.

Chapter 1313: The Missing Kind Corpse Soul

Han Li and Violet Spirit sped through the Extraheavensphere for several days before finally drawing to a halt among a cluster of asteroids.

This area was different from all the other ones in that the asteroids here were completely stationary, and it was also devoid of energy storms.

At the center of the cluster of asteroids was a massive, black ball that was tens of thousands of kilometers in diameter, and it was giving off all types of energy fluctuations and even law power fluctuations.

"This is the place. I didn't think we'd find it so easily," Han Li said.

"What's that black ball? And why is this place so peaceful?" Violet Spirit asked.

"You saw those all-devouring black vortexes on our way here, right?" Han Li asked.

"I did. Does this black ball have something to do with that?" Violet Spirit asked.

"Those black vortexes were formed by mutated spatial power, and they're capable of devouring all things, but their capacity is not unlimited. Once they've devoured up to their threshold, they'll transform into these black balls," Han Li explained.

This was only something that he had learned after doing some research following his previous trip to the Extraheavensphere.

"I see," Violet Spirit replied.

"All of these black balls are priceless treasures that contain tremendous amounts of energy, making them premium, natural ore veins. It's just a pity that they're too big to be stored in spatial treasures, and they're impossible to transport through the Astralsphere down below," Han Li said.

"That is indeed quite a pity," Violet Spirit replied with a thoughtful nod.

If one could transport such a vast wealth of resources to the True Immortal Realm, then that alone would be enough to support the founding of a sect.

"Due to the fact that enormous amounts of energy are devoured by these black balls, the area around them will be quite calm and safe for a very long time. On top of that, these balls contain immense world's origin qi, making them ideal to cultivate in, so let's go into seclusion here," Han Li said.

Violet Spirit naturally didn't raise any objections, so Han Li immediately sprang into action, digging out a cave abode into the black ball.

After setting up some restrictions in the cave abode, he and Violet Spirit entered the Flower Branch domain, where he then activated the Celestial Time Array, accelerating the flow of time in the Flower Branch domain to thirty thousand times the speed of the outside world.

"So this is your space of accelerated time? It's truly remarkable!"

Violet Spirit had already heard about the space of accelerated time from Weeping Soul and the others, but she still couldn't help but feel amazed now that she was seeing it for herself.

Han Li gave a faint smile in response, and after a brief chat, the two of them began cultivating in seclusion.

Inside the bamboo pavilion, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed, and he pulled out the white jade slip that had been given to him by the Reincarnation Palace Master, the one that contained the final two levels of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

After a brief hesitation, he injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip to begin inspecting its contents.

He required more power, even if it meant having to sacrifice the cultivation potential of all of his future incarnations.

With the experience that he had accumulated from cultivating the first five levels of the Spirit Refinement Technique, it didn't take him long to grasp the contents of the final two levels, at which point he commenced his cultivation.

At Han Li's cultivation base, multi-tasking was a simple feat, and while cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique, he summoned a collection of materials, then opened his mouth to release a burst of golden flames to envelop and refine them.

Half a month later, Han Li scattered the golden flames with a wave of his hand, and two golden puppets were revealed with hints of time law powers emanating from their bodies.

A faint smile appeared on his face, and he flipped a hand over to produce a pair of small, white vials, both of which were giving off some type of soul power fluctuations.

He then closed his eyes and began making a string of hand seals, and a layer of translucent, flashing light surfaced over his glabella.

Shortly thereafter, his eyes abruptly sprang open, and two beams of translucent light shot out from within like two arcs of lightning in the night.

At the same time, two specks of green light flew out of his glabella to form a pair of miniature, green figures, both of which were his soul avatars.

The two soul avatars each flew into one of the golden puppets at his behest, following which he cast a string of incantation seals into them as well.

The two puppets slowly opened their eyes, and they were looking much more animated.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, then made a beckoning motion, and two drops of golden spirit liquid flew out of the pair of white vials before fusing into the puppets' glabellas, and their eyes instantly became even brighter and more animated.

Han Li continued to cast more incantation seals into the golden puppets, and a layer of faint, golden light gradually began to appear over their bodies.

Over a year flew by in the blink of an eye.

The golden light emanating from the puppets had just faded, and at this point, their eyes were looking just as clear and intelligent as those of the average person.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he heaved a sigh of relief.

Over the past year, he had been using a type of Earthly Deity Avatar refinement technique from the True Mantra Sect. Even though cultivating as an Earthly Immortal had very severe drawbacks, it also had some unique advantages, and as the super sect that it had once been, the True Mantra Sect had naturally looked into this unique path of cultivation.

Both of these Earthly Deity Avatars contained time law powers, and they were far more intricate than the one he had refined in the Black Wind Sea.

Han Li hadn't refined these Earthly Deity Avatars as he wanted to begin cultivating as an Earthly Immortal, nor was he planning to plant them somewhere to gather power of faith. Instead, they were meant for his future corpse soul severances.

Having already used the Heavenly Fox Tribe's corpse soul severance technique once, he had taken a liking to it, and he was planning to use it for his next two corpse soul severances as well.

In order to be able to use an Earthly Deity Avatar for a corpse soul severance, a lengthy breaking in process was required to increase compatibility between avatar and host, but here in this space of accelerated time, time was not a concern.

With that in mind, Han Li sent the two Earthly Deity Avatars downstairs to cultivate on their own, while he closed his eyes to meditate.

Even with his tremendous spiritual sense, splitting his own soul twice to create those two Earthly Deity Avatars had left him feeling quite weary.

He sat in a statuesque manner for half a year, and by the time he reopened his eyes, he had made a full recovery.

With all of the preparations complete, it was time to officially commence his second corpse soul severance.

With that in mind, a look of concentration appeared in Han Li's mind, and a burst of radiant, golden light appeared over his body, while his spirit domain also instantly became several times brighter than before.

Bursts of immense world's origin qi surged into the spirit domain, and the density of world's origin qi in the Flower Branch domain instantly increased by severalfold.

Violet Spirit was snapped out of her cultivation upon sensing this, and an elated look appeared on her face.

She turned to take a glance at the pavilion that Han Li was in, then closed her eyes to continue cultivating.

Over two hundred thousand years flew by in a flash.

Strands of black light had intertwined themselves around her to form a cocoon-like object, and her aura had returned to the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage.

Even though her cultivation base had previously suffered a sharp decline, her cultivation foundation was still there, and thanks to the vast abundance of world's origin qi in the Flower Branch domain, she was finally able to return to her former cultivation base.

Furthermore, her cultivation foundation had been consolidated, so she was at no risk of suffering a drop in her cultivation base again.

Right at this moment, her eyes sprang open, and the strands of black light around her faded into her body.

A contemplative look appeared on her face as she flipped a hand over to produce a purple jade vial with a black talisman plastered to its surface.

The vial contained none other than True Profound Essence, and she was contemplating whether this was the right to attempt a breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage.

Right at this moment, the golden spirit domain suddenly faded away, and with it went the space of accelerated time as well.

Immediately thereafter, the doors of the pavilion swung open, and Han Li flew out from within with a frustrated look on his face.

Violet Spirit stowed her jade vial away, then made her way to his side.

The frustration in his eyes abated a little upon sensing Violet Spirit's aura, and he smiled as he said, "Looks like you've made very good use of your time here."

"Are things not going so smoothly on your end?" Violet Spirit asked.

"I didn't think severing my kind corpse soul would be so difficult," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"Senior Xie told me some things about corpse soul severance, but given that I was only at the High Zenith Stage, he didn't go into much detail with me. However, I heard from Weeping Soul that you were able to sever your wicked corpse soul without too much trouble, why is your kind corpse soul proving so difficult to sever?" Violet Spirit asked.

"Overall, the corpse soul severance process can be split up into two steps, the first of which is to sense the existence of the corpse soul within one's body, while the second step is to glean the fixations at the root of the corpse soul before severing it. I was able to sever my wicked corpse soul without too much trouble as Gui Lingzi's Corpse Severance Talisman allowed me to skip the first step.

“On top of that, I've killed many living beings in the past, so I'm quite well-versed with my wicked fixations, thereby making the severance quite a smooth process as well, but things are not so simple for my kind corpse soul severance," Han Li explained.

"Why is that?" Violet Spirit asked.

"It's no exaggeration to say that I've been killing virtually non-stop over the course of my cultivation journey. I wouldn't say that I've completely discarded my humanity, but my heart has grown cold and unfeeling over time. As a result, I wasn't even able to detect the presence of the kind corpse soul in my body over these past two hundred thousand years, let alone sever it," Han Li sighed.

Chapter 1314: Traveling the World

"Doesn't the same apply to all cultivators?" Violet Spirit asked.

"That's why the inability to sever one's kind corpse soul is a major obstacle keeping many cultivators from reaching the late-Great Encompassment Stage," Han Li sighed.

"What can we do then?" Violet Spirit asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"Right now, I'm at the pinnacle of the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, so there's no point for me to continue cultivating in seclusion. Instead, it may be better for me to seek inspiration elsewhere," Han Li replied.

"I heard from Senior Xie that for cultivators beyond a certain cultivation base, their mental state is often the key to breaking through bottlenecks. Come to think of it, I've never truly had a chance to see the True Immortal Realm, so you have to take me on a tour, Brother Han," Violet Spirit said with a bright smile.

Violet Spirit's mood was infectious, and Han Li also took a turn for the better under her influence.

"The True Immortal Realm is far more vast and diverse than the Devil Realm, so I'm sure you won't be disappointed. Now that you mention it, I haven't had much of a chance to explore the True Immortal Realm purely for leisure, either, so this is a good opportunity for both us."

With that, he latched onto Violet Spirit's hand before flying out of the Flower Branch domain.

......

The Northern Light Immortal Region was a small immortal region on the outskirts of the True Immortal Realm named for the aurora lights that often appeared in the sky there.

Among non-native cultivators, the immortal region was mostly known only to those at or above the High Zenith Stage. Those below the Golden Immortal Stage often went their entire lives without once leaving the immortal region that they were born in, so they would never get the chance to visit a place like the Northern Light Immortal Region.

In fact, even among cultivators at or above the High Zenith Stage, very few of them would be willing to abandon their cultivation to go on scenic tours of the True Immortal Realm. It was often the case that the loftier one's cultivation base, the more ambitious and focused one became.

In the northernmost region of the Northern Light Immortal Region was a continent that was encased in ice all year round, and on that continent was a mountain range with staggering peaks that reached all the way up into the clouds.

Due to the peculiar formation of the mountain range, the snow and ice that melted flowed down the mountains to form thousands of waterfalls of different sizes, presenting a spectacular sight to behold.

Whenever the aurora lights appeared, they would be reflected by the waterfalls, giving the entire mountain range a breathtakingly beautiful, dream-like appearance.

At this moment, Han Li and Violet Spirit were standing on the summit of one of the mountains while in disguise, appreciating the stunning scenery around them.

......

The Jade Lake Immortal Region's Heavenly Nest Lake was known for producing premium spirit jade, and the lake was enshrouded in a blanket of mist all year round. Furthermore, the mist would change color depending on the time of year, cycling between white, purple, and pink.

This color-changing mist and the premium spirit jade made the lake vastly renowned far and wide, and at this moment, a small boat was gliding over its surface with Han Li and Violet Spirit the sole passengers.

......

The Fire Bird Mountain Range of the Heavenly Fire Immortal Region was renowned for its many mountains that resembled soaring birds, and magma would often come spewing out of the peaks of the mountains from underground, making it appear as if it were a mountain range of countless giant, fire-spewing birds.

Han Li and Violet Spirit were standing together on an extinct volcano, watching the spectacular eruptions together.

......

The mysterious green mud swamps of the Flowing Wave Immortal Region, the red sun sea of the Vast Sea Immortal Region, the stormy mountain ranges of the Dark Wind Immortal Region...

Han Li and Violet Spirit visited all of these wondrous immortal regions one after another, and at Han Li's current cultivation base, it didn't take him long at all to traverse across the immortal regions.

Over the course of less than three hundred years, the two of them traveled through twenty to thirty immortal regions, witnessing countless spectacular sights and scenes.

However, the True Immortal Realm was far too massive, and they had still only explored a minute portion of it.

Given their apprehension of the Heavenly Court and the Reincarnation Palace, both of them had stuck to solely visiting small and medium-sized immortal regions, and they constantly changed their appearances from place to place. Thankfully, their efforts paid off, and they weren't recognized by anyone.

In the eastern region of the Soaring Wings Immortal Region was an undulating mountain range that was riddled with a type of crimson bamboo, presenting a majestic sight to behold from above.

Whenever a gust of wind swept through the area, the bamboo forest would rustle to produce a sound like crashing waves, and as a result, the forest was named the bamboo sea.

In a small city by the name of Jade Mountain City near the mountain range was a three-story restaurant, where Han Li and Violet Spirit were sitting at a windowside table.

They were drinking a type of bright red wine that was giving off a delectable bamboo fragrance, and it had been brewed using the roots of the crimson bamboo.

"The Crimson Bamboo Sea really does live up to its reputation. This Crimson Bamboo Wine is only a mortal wine, but it's not bad at all. I'm glad we made the trip here," Violet Spirit said before taking a sip.

Han Li finished his cup of wine in one go, then nodded in agreement.

At this point, it was no exaggeration to say that he was a wine connoisseur, and even he couldn't help but be impressed with this wine.

Han Li set down his cup before looking out the window at the bustling city streets down below.

During the two hundred thousand years that he had spent in the Flower Branch domain, he had made rapid progress in his Spirit Refinement Technique while simultaneously attempting to sense his kind corpse soul, and at this point, he had already mastered the sixth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

However, at the moment, he was choosing to see the city with his eyes rather than his spiritual sense.

Jade Mountain City was a mortal city that was filled with people from all walks of life, including officials, scholars, merchants, martial artists, farmers, and many beggars.

All types of voices filled with countless different emotions could be heard ringing out in the city, offering fleeting sneak peeks into the lives of the city's residents.

All of a sudden, Han Li heaved a faint sigh, then refilled his cup before downing its contents in one go once again.

"What's wrong?" Violet Spirit asked.

"Nothing. It's just occurred to me that no one can be truly free from the mortal coil of life, regardless of whether it be mortals or cultivators like us," Han Li replied.

"Even as immortals, we are still unable to fully transcend beyond our emotions and desires," Violet Spirit said as she heaved a faint sigh.

Han Li cast his gaze into the distance in silence.

"Have you made any progress in sensing your kind corpse soul?" Violet Spirit asked.

Han Li shook his head with a glum look in his eyes.

"You've already traveled with me for over two hundred years, and I couldn't be more satisfied, so how about you go into seclusion again starting from tomorrow? Maybe all of the things that we've seen over the years will make a difference," Violet Spirit suggested.

"A corpse soul severance is not something that can be achieved solely through the accumulation of time. Otherwise, it wouldn't be regarded as such a stern obstacle to so many cultivators. I have a feeling that the key to my breakthrough to the late-Great Encompassment Stage is in the mortal world, so let's keep going and try our luck," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

A faint smile appeared on Violet Spirit's face upon hearing this.

Han Li refilled their cups, and they shared another drink together.

"Immortal Ling Yun summoned his flying sword, and its radiance outshone even the light of the moon. The wretched dragon was so horrified to see this that it immediately turned to flee, but its fate was already sealed. In the blink of an eye, one of its front claws was severed, and the pond instantly ran red with its blood."

The sound of a storyteller's voice rang out within the restaurant, and it was an elderly man telling a story of a sword immortal slaying an evil dragon.

In the Soaring Wings Immortal Region, there was great emphasis placed on the distinction between mortals and immortals, and immortals were strictly prohibited from appearing in mortal areas, thereby lending them an air of mystique in the eyes of commoners, making them perfect storytelling subjects.

The elderly storyteller was very good at his job, and there were many restaurant customers gathered around him, eagerly awaiting the story's continuation.

However, instead of immediately continuing the story, the elderly man cleared his throat before taking a sip of tea.

At the same time, a fair young maiden who appeared to have been around fifteen to sixteen years of age stepped forward from beside him while holding a copper dish, and she extended a curtsey toward everyone with a bright smile.

She didn't say anything, but it was clear what she wanted. The story was quite riveting, and the young maiden was also a sight for sore eyes, so there were quite a few customers willing to pay to hear the continuation of the story, much to the appreciation of the elderly storyteller.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Back when he was living in the rural village that he grew up in, he had never had the chance to hear a storyteller perform their craft. At the very most, he could hear some stories of the outside world from those who had previously left the village.

At the time, he had been filled with curiosity and longing toward the unknown world of immortals and deities, just like the customers in this restaurant.

The young maiden bent down to collect the money offered up by the customers, revealing a section of her fair and delicate neck in the process, and several rowdy troublemakers immediately began making lewd remarks at her expense.

The young maiden was very shy, and a deep blush instantly appeared on her face, but she didn't stop collecting the money offered to her. As she continued, she used the copper dish to cover her face, but that only seemed to make the troublemakers more keen on harassing her.

The young maiden could sense their ill intentions, and she hurriedly gathered up the rest of the money before backing away.

However, right at this moment, a young man dressed in lavish clothing suddenly stood up and grabbed onto her wrist, immediately eliciting a scream from her.

The young man was clearly already quite inebriated, and he reached out to stroke the young maiden's chin as he slurred, "Where're you from, pretty girl? Let me treat you to a fine meal..."

The young maiden immediately began yelling for help with a panicked expression, and the elderly storyteller rushed over to try and help her, only to be pushed aside by the young man.

The young man seemed to have been a martial artist, and he possessed formidable strength, pushing the elderly man straight through a railing, upon which he fell to the ground as blood came spewing out of his mouth.

"Grandpa!" the young maiden yelled through her sobs as she struggled with all her might, but was completely unable to break free.

Meanwhile, some of the more timid customers in the restaurant were already beginning to sneak out of the establishment.

A hint of displeasure flashed through Han Li's eyes, but he remained seated.

Things like this happened all the time in the mortal world, so this wasn't anything remarkable.

Chapter 1315: An Act of Kindness

A waiter made his way onto the scene and said, "Please restrain yourselves and take a seat, esteemed customer. Our restaurant is a proper establishment, so please be civilized."

Another hoodlum immediately jumped up and grabbed the waiter by the collar as he yelled, "Who the hell do you think you are? We're paying customers, are we not? What gives you the right to tell us what to do?"

The waiter was completely unfazed as he said, "You are indeed paying customers, but it'll be bad for our business if you cause trouble and scare away all of our customers. I don't recall seeing you around these parts, so you must be foreigners, right? The owner of our restaurant is the esteemed Official Jin, and he's not someone you want to mess with around these parts."

The group of hoodlums collectively turned to the young man in opulent attire.

"Official Jin? You're talking about that bastard, Jin Fugui, right? He's nothing more than a mere administrator of our Golden Dragon Faction, yet you speak of him like he's some kind of god!" the young man sneered while maintaining a firm grip on the young maiden.

"You're from the Golden Dragon Faction?" the waiter asked as a hint of panic surfaced in his eyes.

The hoodlum that was holding onto the waiter's collar pushed him to the ground as he yelled, "You're looking at the only son of the faction leader, you blind dog!"

The waiter had completely lost his composure, and he was trembling incessantly as he sat on the ground with a fearful expression.

The young man turned his gaze back to the young maiden, and in his drunken state, he was barely able to suppress his lust.

He had seen many women before, but such a shy and pure beauty was certainly a rare sight.

"Everyone else, get out of here before I make you!" the young man yelled, and all of the remaining customers immediately fled the restaurant in a hurry.

Before long, Han Li and Violet Spirit were the only two left.

"Piss off!" one of the hoodlums yelled.

Violet Spirit had disguised herself as an average-looking woman, so she hadn't attracted the attention of the hoodlums.

A cold look appeared in Han Li's eyes. Listening to the storyteller had triggered some distant memories of his, and he was just beginning to derive some inspiration from that, only for these scoundrels to spoil everything.

"What a bunch of eyesores," he harrumphed coldly as he flicked the chopstick container on the table with his finger, and the container shuddered ever so slightly before falling still again.

All of a sudden, blood came spraying out of the hands of all of the hoodlums, and their wrists had all been pierced through by chopsticks.

They immediately began screaming in agony, and the young man in the lavish robe involuntarily released the young maiden from the excruciating pain.

The young maiden was dazed for a moment, then hurriedly rushed over to the elderly storyteller's side before helping him to his feet.

"Let's go," Han Li said as he stood up and placed a small silver ingot onto the table, then began to make his way downstairs, followed by Violet Spirit.

The storyteller and her granddaughter also hurriedly rushed downstairs for fear or retaliation from the hoodlums, who were in too much pain to stop them.

Han Li and Violet Spirit had only just emerged from the restaurant when they heard the storyteller call out after them.

"Please wait a moment."

Han Li stopped in his tracks, and the storyteller immediately fell to his knees as he said, "Thank you for helping us. If Xiao Cui had fallen into the hands of those people, then she would've surely died!"

The young maiden also fell to her knees before kowtowing to Han Li in gratitude.

All of a sudden, a peculiar look flashed through Han Li's eyes at the sight of the duo.

"Brother Han?" Violet Spirit called out in a gentle voice.

Han Li immediately snapped out of his reverie, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of invisible force that helped the two back to their feet as he said, "There's no need to thank me, I didn't really do much."

A hint of awe and veneration appeared in the duo's eyes as they gazed upon Han Li.

"It sounded like those people have some powerful backers behind them, so I suggest you leave this place as quickly as you can. I've saved you once, but I can't always be around to save you," Han Li said.

"Those people are from the Golden Dragon Faction, which has a stranglehold on the entirety of Tiezhou. If they want to exact vengeance on us, there's nowhere safe for us to run," the storyteller said with a look of despair on his face.

"Your dialect is a little different from the residents of Jade Mountain City, so you must be from elsewhere, right? Where is your home?" Han Li asked.

"My grandfather and I are from Qingzhou, and we fled here to escape the famine in our hometown," the young maiden replied.

"Qingzhou? That's the place where two large rivers meet, right?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

The young maiden faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded as she replied, "That's right."

"Where in Qingzhou is your hometown? And tell me about the environment near your home as well," Han Li said.

The young maiden and the elderly storyteller exchanged a hesitant glance with one another, then divulged the information requested by Han Li.

"I see, so that thatch hut next to that large willow tree is your home," Han Li chuckled.

Both the young maiden and her grandfather were stunned to hear this. They hadn't made any mention of that willow tree, so they had no idea how Han Li was aware of its existence.

"Come, I'll take you two back home," Han Li said with a sweep of his sleeve, releasing a burst of golden light that enveloped the duo.

The two of them instantly felt as light as a pair of feathers as they rose up into the air, and in the next instant, they returned to solid ground as the golden light around them faded away.

However, as opposed to Jade Mountain City, they found themselves in a lakeside village, while Han Li and Violet Spirit were nowhere to be seen.

Directly ahead of the two of them were three thatch huts with a lush willow tree growing nearby.

"This is our home..."

The young maiden and her grandfather were completely flabbergasted by what they were witnessing.

"It looks like the famine in your hometown has already passed. Here's some silver, you can live here in peace from now on."

Han Li's voice rang out from overhead, following which a silver ingot fell out of the sky and into the elderly man's grasp.

"Thank you, esteemed immortal! We'll be sure to set up a plaque for you and worship it day and night!" the elderly storyteller hurriedly said as he fell to his knees and kowtowed toward the approximate direction that Han Li's voice had come from, while his granddaughter immediately followed suit.

Meanwhile, Han Li and Violet Spirit were standing together high up in the sky.

"I didn't think you'd go so far for their sake, Brother Han," Violet Spirit said with a faint smile.

However, Han Li offered no response. Instead, he seemed to have been sensing something with his eyes closed and a hint of elation on his face.

"What's gotten you in such a good mood, Brother Han?" Violet Spirit asked with an intrigued expression.

"I seem to have found a catalyst for severing my corpse soul," Han Li replied as he opened his eyes with a pleased smile.

"Really? What is it?" Violet Spirit exclaimed in an ecstatic manner.

Han Li offered no reply, merely pointing a finger down at the two people below.

"Are you saying that helping others is helping you sense your kind corpse soul?" Violet Spirit asked.

Han Li nodded in response.

After saving those two from those Golden Dragon Faction troublemakers, he had felt some intangible thing wrap around him as the duo was expressing their gratitude to him, and he could intuitively sense that this was a step in the right direction as far as his kind corpse soul severance was concerned.

As for bringing the duo back to their hometown, Han Li had done this as an experiment, and sure enough, as the two of them expressed their gratitude again, another burst of the same intangible force had descended upon him, but for some reason, it was far lesser than the first one.

"I suppose that makes sense. After all, helping others is certainly an act of kindness. You told me that you're unable to sense your kind corpse soul due to your lack of understanding of the true meaning of kindness, so perhaps you can glean this true meaning by helping others," Violet Spirit analyzed.

"That's precisely what I'm thinking. Now that I've found a way forward, I should finally be able to make some progress toward my kind corpse soul severance," Han Li said with a faint smile, then released his tremendous spiritual sense in all directions.

Having mastered the sixth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, his spiritual sensory range had swelled to such an extent that he was able to see close to half of the entire Soaring Wings Immortal Region at once.

On top of that, his spiritual sense had also become far more exhaustive than before, allowing him to see precisely what everyone in his spiritual sensory range was doing, and it didn't take long before he locked onto his next target.

All of a sudden, the two of them vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning.

......

On a certain mountain path, a convoy of carts that were carrying valuable goods had been intercepted by a group of masked bandits, and a fierce battle was taking place.

The bandits severely outnumbered the guards of the convoy, and they had sprung a perfect ambush, so it didn't take long before the number of guards was whittled down to the final three.

Before long, two more fell, and all that remained was an imposing elderly man.

A grief-stricken look flashed through his eyes, but he continued to swing his large saber with all his might, keeping the surrounding bandits at bay.

"All of your comrades are dead, Xiang Zong. If you kneel and kowtow to us now, perhaps we'll spare you your life," the leader of the bandits chortled.

The elderly man's left arm was already bloody and injured, but he remained as resilient as ever as he roared, "Cut the chit-chat, Liu Sandao! I won't ever bow my head to bandits like you!"

"Your resolve is as impressive as ever, Xiang Zong, but that's not going to do you any good when you're dead! Seeing as you're clearly so intent on passing on to the afterlife, I'll give you a helping hand!" Liu Sandao sneered as he raised a hand, and several of the bandits standing beside him stepped forward before each pulling out a giant crossbow that was around three feet in length.

Each crossbow cartridge contained close to twenty arrows, and they were fired in rapid succession to send over a hundred arrows raining down upon Xiang Zong at once.

Chapter 1316: Spree of Kindness

Xiang Zong was too busy defending himself against the polearm weapons wielded by the bandits around him, yet right as it appeared as if he were about to meet his demise from the volley of crossbow arrows, a sweeping arc of lightning descended from the heavens to instantly vaporize the arrows.

Immediately thereafter, the arc of lightning split up into countless tiny arcs that struck every single one of the bandits with unerring accuracy.

A resounding thunderclap rang out as the bandits were sent flying back through the air, then tumbled to the ground while screaming and twitching spasmodically, but not a single one of them was killed.

Xiang Zong had been spared by the golden lightning, and he looked on with a dazed expression, unable to believe what he was seeing.

The golden lightning quickly dissipated, and the bandits clambered to their feet before looking around with fearful expressions.

Right at this moment, an authoritative voice rang out from the heavens above.

"Get out of here! I won't be so gracious if I see you robbing others again!"

The bandits immediately fled in a blind panic, while Xiang Zong stared after them with a look of intense resentment in his eyes, but he didn't pursue them.

He was already very advanced in age, and he had suffered severe injuries, so he didn't have the strength to pursue them.

Right at this moment, Han Li and Violet Spirit appeared in mid-air before him.

"Immortals!" Xiang Zong exclaimed with an awestruck expression.

"I could see that you were not destined to meet your demise here. The fact that we crossed paths means that we were brought together by fate, and that's why I saved you," Han Li said, then flicked a finger through the air to release a burst of azure light into Xiang Zong's body.

Xiang Zong felt a surge of warmth flow through his entire body, and all of his fatigue was drained away, while his injuries were rapidly healing, much to his shock and elation.

"Thank you for saving me, esteemed immortals! Words cannot even begin to express my gratitude!" Xiang Zong said as he extended a deep bow, and by the time he looked back up again, Han Li and Violet Spirit were already nowhere to be seen.

......

A large ship was traveling over a giant lake in the Soaring Wings Immortal Region, but at this moment, the ship was caught in the grasp of a series of black tentacles that had risen up from within the lake.

Thankfully, the ship had been constructed from very resilient materials, and it held firm against the crushing force exerted upon it by the constricting tentacles.

There were currently what appeared to have been several dozen tourists gathered in the cabin of the ship, and they were huddled together while trembling in fear.

A giant, black squid emerged from the turbulent lake, and all of the ship's passengers began to scream and sob in horror.

Right at this moment, a bolt of golden lightning descended from the heavens to strike the giant squid.

A huge gash was instantly torn into the squid's body, and it let loose a terrified screech as it immediately released the ship before hurriedly retreating into the depths of the lake.

The passengers of the ship were so moved by this act of divine intervention that they burst into tears.

All of a sudden, Han Li and Violet Spirit appeared in mid-air, and there were still arcs of golden lightning flashing over Han Li's hands.

Someone from inside the ship's cabin caught sight of Han Li and Violet Spirit, and they exclaimed, "We've been saved by immortals!"

Everyone else in the cabin immediately came rushing out to kowtow to them in gratitude, and the two of them lingered for a moment before vanishing into thin air yet again.

......

After a consecutive month of heavy rainfall, a mountain collapsed violently, resulting in an avalanche that threatened to inundate an entire village.

All of a sudden, a burst of blue light descended from the heavens, and the entire mountain and the avalanche were both instantly frozen solid, saving the village from certain destruction.

The villagers were ecstatic to see this, but at the same time, they were looking at one another with bewildered expressions, wondering what had just happened.

Right at this moment, Han Li and Violet Spirit appeared in the sky, seemingly out of thin air.

"Those two are immortals! They're the ones who saved us!"

......

In the blink of an eye, Han Li had already been doing good deeds across the Soaring Wings Immortal Region for close to thirty years.

He had saved countless people during this time, and he had become so renowned across the immortal region that temples had been built in many places to worship him.

Furthermore, as more and more people witnessed Han Li, descriptions of his appearance became more and more concrete, and statues of him were erected in the temples in accordance with these descriptions.

Some of the immortal sects of the Soaring Wings Immortal Region gradually caught wind of this and sent out people to investigate this matter.

Han Li had no intention of becoming entangled with the immortal powers of the Soaring Wings Immortal Region, so he and Violet Spirit departed and set off for a nearby immortal region.

On this day, Han Li was seated on a flying boat as it raced over the primordial land outside the Soaring Wings Immortal Region.

His eyes were closed as if he were sensing something, and only after a long while were they reopened.

"Is everything going smoothly, Brother Han?" Violet Spirit asked.

"I've been making some progress. At the very least, I now have a vague sense of my kind corpse soul," Han Li replied, but there wasn't much elation in his voice.

Violet Spirit could sense that he wasn't in particularly high spirits, and she asked in a gentle voice, "Is there something wrong?"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he replied, "Over the years, I've been deriving less and less benefit from my acts of kindness. In particular, over the past year, there have been virtually no returns made."

"Why is that?" Violet Spirit asked in a concerned manner.

"I'm not sure. At the moment, I'm still very far from being able to sever my kind corpse soul, so I have to find a solution to this problem. Otherwise, my progress will stagnate again," Han Li replied in a grim voice.

After a brief silence, Han Li continued, "I'm wondering whether it's because I haven't saved enough people recently, so my acts of kindness are lacking in magnitude, and that's why my progress has stagnated."

"That is a possibility, but I feel like grasping at straws here. By the way, do you still recall which act of kindness you received the most reciprocation from?" Violet Spirit asked.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "That had to have been the first act of kindness, when I saved that storyteller and his granddaughter. Ever since then, the reciprocation has paled in comparison."

"On that occasion, you only saved two people, but there were many occasions after that where you saved far more than two people, so I don't think it's a matter of how many people you save," Violet Spirit analyzed.

"That's true. In that case, what sets that act of kindness apart from all of the others?" Han Li mused as he fell into deep thought, and Violet Spirit also fell into a contemplative silence.

"Just forget about it. I can't think of an answer anyway, so thinking excessively will only result in unnecessary stress. I've already made some good progress, so I'll just continue down the same path and try my luck," Han Li said after a lengthy period of deep thought, and Violet Spirit nodded in response.

From there, Han Li cast an incantation seal into the flying boat and the spirit patterns on its surface instantly became ten times brighter, and it also accelerated drastically, threatening to tear through the nearby space.

After flying for around half a month, the two of them finally arrived in a new immortal region.

This immortal region was very lacking in spiritual qi. In this regard, it was far inferior even to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and it was almost on par with the Spirit Realm.

"What a barren immortal region..." Han Li remarked with slightly furrowed brows.

This was also a very small immortal region, less than half the size of the Soaring Wings Immortal Region, so he was able to fully encompass it with his spiritual sense.

The immortal region was riddled with what appeared to have been defunct ore mines, leaving it scarred and ravaged like a well overused rag. All of the spirit veins underground had also been destroyed, so it was no wonder that the spiritual qi here was so severely lacking.

The immortal region had a very small population, most of which were gathered in a few set areas in which the spirit veins weren't too severely destroyed, so there was still some world's origin qi left for cultivators to harness.

"What is the name of this immortal region?" Han Li asked.

"This place is called the Crane Ridge Immortal Region. A very long time ago, it had been abundant with the world's origin qi and ore mines, but it's been reduced to its current state due to overexploitation from the Heavenly Court," Violet Spirit replied after consulting a jade slip.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"Are you going to keep helping people here, Brother Han? This immortal region has a very sparse population, so you might not be able to make much progress here," Violet Spirit said.

"I'll take a look and see first. Such a barren immortal region is quite rare in the True Immortal Realm," Han Li replied, then conjured up a golden lightning array, and the two of them instantly vanished from the spot.

In the northwestern area of the Crane Ridge Immortal Region was a giant basin that was thousands of kilometers in size.

There was a huge city inside that filled almost the entire basin, and it was inhabited by both cultivators and mortals alike.

The city wasn't small, but it wasn't thriving at all. Many places had already fallen into disuse, and there was a faint smell or rust in the air. There weren't many people on the streets, even in the center of the city, and the shops also barely had any patrons, while most of the city's residents seemed to have been staying at home.

The entire city resembled an elderly man on his deathbed, awaiting the embrace of death.

Han Li appeared outside the city amid a flash of lightning, but no one noticed the lightning due to the gray mist in the sky.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he looked down at the city below.

"Let's go and take a look," he said, and the two of them descended onto a street in the city.

It was close to nighttime, and most of the city had already fallen into darkness, with only some sparse specks of light indicating that the city was inhabited.

Some of the shops that lined the streets were also lit, illuminating a small area around them.

Han Li strolled along the street in an aimless manner with his eyes closed, seemingly sensing something.

Violet Spirit was rather perplexed to see this, but she didn't ask any questions as she walked along beside him in silence.

Chapter 1317: Hiding Away

A long time passed by, and Han Li continued to walk through the city with his eyes closed.

Finally, Violet Spirit was unable to resist the urge to ask, "Why have we come here, Brother Han?"

It didn't appear as if he was going to be helping anyone here.

"The True Immortal Realm is very abundant with spiritual qi, so most of the immortal regions are very prosperous places. It's very rare to see a place as barren and decrepit as this, so I want to bask in the special environment here," Han Li replied.

"What's there to bask in in such a rundown city?" Violet Spirit asked with slightly furrowed brows.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, but ultimately merely shook his head in response.

One of the reasons why he had come here was actually to further his cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

In contrast with the previous six levels, cultivation of the seventh level was far more complex, and it wasn't something that could simply be mastered through aptitude and willpower alone. In addition to that, one had to witness and understand people in all types of circumstances, those who were successful, downtrodden, wealthy, impoverished...

In doing so, he would be refining his own mental state to give his own soul an all-inclusive quality, and only then could he hope to master the seventh level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Hence, they had been traveling not just to satisfy Violet Spirit's wanderlust, but also for him to see people from all walks of life and see the world through their eyes.

Upon mastering the sixth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, Han Li had also become able to glean the thoughts of others through their soul fluctuations, just like Weeping Soul.

This entire city was filled with a decrepit aura, presenting a stark contrast with the other places that he had visited, and that was why he had been drawn here.

Violet Spirit didn't ask any further questions as she continued to trail along behind Han Li in silence.

Only after strolling through the city for an entire night did Han Li finally stop in his tracks and open his eyes.

"Done?" Violet Spirit asked.

"Sorry to keep you waiting," Han Li replied with a nod.

"It's fine. What are you planning to do from here? Continue to help people?" Violet Spirit asked.

Han Li smiled and offered no response as he released his spiritual sense, and it wasn't long before he found his next target.

A golden lightning array was quickly conjured up around the two, and they instantly vanished from the spot before reappearing in the sky above a small courtyard in the city.

There were seven or eight muscular men surrounding an elderly man, seemingly trying to rob something from him.

"Stop!" Han Li yelled as he flicked a finger through the air, sending a bolt of lightning crashing down onto the nearby ground.

A huge crater was blasted into the ground, and the robbers were sent flying by the resulting shockwaves.

Han Li didn't dare to take any lives for fear of losing touch with his kind corpse soul. In fact, over all these years, he hadn't even slain a single wild beast.

The color instantly drained from the robbers' faces at the sight of Han Li and Violet Spirit, and they frantically scrambled to their feet before scurrying away, while the elderly man was momentarily rooted to the spot in a daze before hurriedly rushing over to Han Li's duo to offer his gratitude.

However, to Han Li's dismay, even though he had just helped the elderly man, the latter's gratitude hadn't bestowed any further kind intent upon him.

With his brows slightly furrowed, he gave the elderly man a slight nod before teleporting to the next site of conflict.

After his first half a month or so in this barren city, Han Li had committed over a hundred acts of kindness, yet not a single one yielded any kind intent.

At this moment, the two of them were seated together in a relatively tidy tea shop in the city.

Placed on the table in front of Han Li was a cup of spirit tea that was giving off a fine fragrance, but he was in no mood to taste it.

Violet Spirit's tea was also untouched, and she was reading through a thick book.

This was a book concerning the concepts of good and evil that Han Li had purchased from the Reincarnation Palace trading interface, and Violet Spirit was trying to see if there was anything in the book that could help Han Li out of his current predicament.

Han Li and Violet Spirit were the only customers in the tea shop, so it was very peaceful.

Right at this moment, they were approached by a thin middle-aged man, who smiled and asked, "Is the tea not to your liking? Should I switch to another tea?"

This man was the shopkeeper of the tea shop, and he was a Grand Ascension cultivator, but for some reason, he had taken up residence here to run this tea shop.

Given that he was on the cusp of the True Immortal Stage, his cultivation base was already quite lofty as far as this area was concerned, but of course, Han Li was able to see through him right away.

"There's no need for that. The tea is just fine, it's just that we're not in much of a mood for tea right now," Han Li replied with a faint smile, then took a sip of the tea in his cup before giving the shopkeeper a slight nod.

As for Violet Spirit, she paid no heed to the shopkeeper at all as she continued to read her book.

"It sounds like the two of you are troubled by something. In that case, this tea is not quite right for you. I just so happen to have a tea here that can cleanse one's heart and calm one's mind. I'll bring it out for the two of you to try," the shopkeeper said, then departed before Han Li had a chance to respond.

Moments later, he emerged with two cups of green spirit tea, then set them down onto the table.

The tea was virtually completely devoid of aroma, but Han Li's eyes lit up with intrigue as he took a sip out of one of the cups, and a cool and refreshing sensation instantly flowed throughout his entire body as the tea entered his stomach.

As a result, much of the frustration that he was feeling instantly dissipated.

"You are truly exceptional at your craft, shopkeeper," Han Li praised.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist. I can see that both of you appear to be cultivators, is that right? On top of that, it seems like you're not from these parts," the shopkeeper said with a smile, and he seemed to have quite an outgoing personality.

"You're correct. We only came to this city around half a month ago. My name is Han Li, and this is Violet Spirit," Han Li replied.

"I see. It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance. My name is Li Hai," the shopkeeper said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Violet Spirit looked up from her book momentarily to give the shopkeeper a slight nod, then turned her attention back to her reading again.

"There's no one else in the shop at the moment, so why not have a seat and join us for a chat, Shopkeeper Li?" Han Li invited.

Li Huai duly obliged, sitting down at the table.

"How were you able to tell that we're not from this area, Shopkeeper Li?" Han Li asked.

"Both of you possess very exuberant auras like that of the rising sun, and that's far different from the dispositions of the people that I see here. Anyone who has resided here for an extended period of time inevitably takes on the aura of this place," Li Hai replied with a smile.

"You possess a keen eye, Shopkeeper Li. Are things this bad everywhere around these parts, Shopkeeper Li?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid so," Li Hai sighed. "All of the spirit veins on this continent have been completely overexploited as far back as tens of thousands of years ago, and everyone who's able to leave has already left. All those that are left are those who are unable to leave or are attached to their homeland, so over time, it's become a rather depressing place."

"This continent isn't the only place in this situation, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. It sounds like you've been to a lot of places, Fellow Daoist Han," the shopkeeper replied with a nod.

"You're not a local here, either, right, Shopkeeper Li? In fact, I daresay you're not even from this immortal region," Han Li said as he set down his teacup with a smile.

"Oh? What makes you say that?" the shopkeeper asked with a surprised expression.

"I'm not well versed in the art of tea, but I've heard that the neighboring Green Water Immortal Region excels in tea arts and the production of tea leaves. I've even heard that in order to improve their skills, many of the tea masters of the Green Water Immortal Region have even pursued special cultivation arts to help hone their craft, the most popular of which is the Green Water Brewing Mantra.

“I can see that the water-attribute cultivation art that you're using is very similar to the Green Water Brewing Mantra, and there are also some traces of the style of the Green Water Immortal Region that I can see in the construction of the tea shop, and it's this combination of clues that led me to my conclusion," Han Li explained with a smile.

"You possess a far sharper eye than my own, Fellow Daoist! Indeed, I am originally from the Green Water Immortal Region," Li Hai praised as a hint of admiration appeared in his eyes.

He was unable to glean Han Li and Violet Spirit's cultivation bases, and he had initially assumed that they had hidden their cultivation bases using some type of aura concealment secret technique. However, given that Han Li was able to freely traverse between immortal regions and see through his cultivation arts with ease, it was clear that he had to have been at least at the True Immortal Stage.

However, at the same time, he could tell that Han Li had no intention of revealing his cultivation base, so he wisely decided not to ask.

"You tea-brewing skills seem to be quite impressive, so why is it that you left the Green Water Immortal Region to come to a barren immortal region like this one?" Han Li asked.

"You think far too highly of me, Fellow Daoist. I didn't really have a future in the Green Water Immortal Region, given my paltry tea-brewing skills and my lowly cultivation base. I strove to reach greater heights in the past, but it didn't work out in the end. In any case, I'm just happy to be able to lead a peaceful life and no longer have to constantly worry about my future," Li Hai replied with a wry smile, and Han Li nodded in response.

"That's enough about me. I'm assuming the two of you came here to do something, right? My cultivation base may not be all that impressive, but I've been here for many years, and I'm quite familiar with this place, so perhaps I can help you out," Li Hai said.

"Thank you for your kind hospitality, but what I've come here to do is a little special, and no one can help me," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"In that case, I can only wish you all the best. If you need any help from me, feel free to ask," Li Hai said.

Han Li could sense that Li Hai was being very genuine here, and he cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "You have my thanks."

Right at this moment, the voice of a young boy rang out from outside the shop.

"Uncle Li, are you there?"

It was a mortal boy dressed in ragged clothes, and he was standing outside the tea shop in a timid manner.

"Please excuse me for a moment, fellow daoists," Li Hai said, then stood up and made his way out of the tea shop.

Han Li took a sip of tea as he casually cast his gaze out of the tea shop.

Chapter 1318: A Century in a Flash

"What do you need, Little Zhao?" Li Hai asked.

"The frost poison in my mother's body has relapsed, so I would like to buy some Crimson Sun Tea for her," the boy replied with his head lowered.

"Alright, I'll fetch some for you right now," Li Hai replied with a nod, then re-entered the tea shop.

The boy raised his head to say something, but ultimately remained silent as he lowered his head again.

Before long, Li Hai re-emerged from the tea shop with a red jade box in his hands.

He offered the jade box to the boy as he said, "This is enough for three batches of tea, and once she's finished, her frost poison will be suppressed."

"Thank you, Uncle Li, but over the years, we've spent all of our money on treating my mother's condition, and this is all that I have left..." the boy said he tipped out some small scraps of silver from a patchy cloth pouch.

Instead of taking the silver, Li Hai smiled and replied, "I'm aware of your family's financial circumstances. Just take the tea for your mother to drink for now, and feel free to come back for more if you need."

"Uncle Li..."

The boy bit down onto his own lower lip to fight back his tears, but they still began flowing from his eyes, nonetheless.

"Alright now, strong boys like yourself shouldn't cry. Go back to your mother, she's still waiting for you," Li Hai said as he patted the boy on the shoulder, then turned to make his way back into the tea shop.

The boy wiped the tears from his eyes, then fell to his knees and kowtowed twice before departing.

Inside the tea shop, an intrigued look had appeared on Han Li's face.

There was a wall between the young boy and where he and Violet Spirit were sitting, but of course, he was able to see through the wall with ease.

In his pursuit of severing his kind corpse soul, he had become quite sensitive to kind intent, and he had noticed a burst of kind intent appear around Li Hai as the boy had kowtowed to him in gratitude.

It was a considerably large burst of kind intent, far more than what Han Li had received from his past acts of kindness.

Why is that? Why has Li Hai received so much more kind intent from his act of kindness? What is the difference between me and him?

His breathing began to accelerate as he stared intently at the cup in his hand, and he felt as if he were on the verge of reaching an important epiphany.

Right at this moment, Violet Spirit suddenly reacted as if she had just read something of interest.

"What is it?" Han Li asked.

"This Pear Orchard Journal was written by a very respected Confucian scholar, and I just read something in here that I think relates to you," Violet Spirit replied as she offered the book to Han Li while pointing out the passage of text that had caught her interest.

The text read: "Acts of kindness are inherently good, but the goodness of such acts will be tarnished if one's motives are impure."

Han Li was instantly struck by a profound sense of enlightenment upon reading this line.

"I understand it now! Doing kind deeds for one's own benefit is only a form of false kindness. No matter how many such deeds are committed, they remain fundamentally flawed. Only acts of kindness committed for no ulterior motive or desire for compensation is true kindness," Han Li exclaimed.

Even though Li Hai was a Grand Ascension cultivator, he had made peace with himself and was no longer pursuing greater heights in his cultivation. Instead, he had chosen to settle in this desolate immortal region, and he had helped that boy just now with very pure motives, which was why he had been rewarded with so much kind intent.

Similarly, Han Li had helped that storyteller and his granddaughter on a whim, so it had been an act of kindness that had been similar in nature.

"I see. Even though you've committed more acts of kindness of an objectively greater magnitude than Li Hai, your fixations and impure intentions have worked to your detriment," Violet Spirit said as her eyes lit up in understanding.

"Now that I know the reason, I'll be able to remedy my actions accordingly," Han Li said with an excited smile.

Seven years later.

A shop in a peaceful and secluded area had changed owners. It had been purchased by a young couple, and what had once been a variety store had been turned into a clinic where patients were treated and medicines were sold.

Even though the couple was quite young, they were exceptional at what they did, able to cure many strange and complex ailments to great effect, in addition to the more commonly seen injuries and illnesses.

On top of that, the prices that they charged were extremely low, and it didn't take long before their clinic became vastly renowned far and wide.

As a result, business was booming despite the clinic's secluded location.

The couple was naturally none other than Han Li and Violet Spirit, and at their current cultivation bases, curing mortals of their ailments couldn't have been an easier task.

Prior to this, Han Li spent a whole seven years transforming himself into a mortal resident of the city, forgetting his fixations and even his status as a cultivator.

He had earned some silver over the years, using which he had purchased this shop to open this clinic, and he was doing his best to genuinely help others for no compensation.

However, this selfless mindset wasn't something that could be achieved on a whim, and his impure intentions still often got in the way.

At the very most, he could only treat one or two out of a hundred patients with a truly pure and selfless heart.

However, he didn't grow disheartened or frustrated, and he continued to run the clinic while pondering the true meaning of kindness.

Before long, the clinic had already been operating for ten years, and the young couple had become a middle-aged one.

Thirty more years passed by, and the couple had entered their autumn years.

Over time, Han Li's heart had become purer and purer, and as a result, he was receiving more and more kind intent from his treatments.

Over a hundred years flew by in a flash.

At this point, the clinic had become a time-honored brand that was renowned far and wide, and there had supposedly been many generations of shopkeepers.

Inside the clinic's inner chamber, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed, and there was a bright glow emanating from his facial features, while Violet Spirit was standing nearby, observing him in silence.

There was also a faint sheen over her face, and her aura had become more gentle and refined.

Over the years, she had also committed many kind deeds and accumulated a great deal of kind intent. Her cultivation base hadn't advanced much over the years, but her soul had become far more supple and refined than before.

Some time later, Han Li opened his eyes, and it was as if two arcs of lightning had flashed through the inner chamber.

"Is everything ready, Brother?" Violet Spirit asked.

"I am now fully able to sense my kind corpse soul, and I've also fully grasped the true meaning of kindness. By my estimates, my chances of successfully severing my kind corpse soul using my Avatar Corpse Soul Severance Technique are around 80%," Han Li replied.

"That's good to hear," Violet Spirit said in a relieved manner.

Looking at the clinic where they had stayed for over a century, Han Li was a little reluctant to leave, but he knew that it was time.

"Let's go," he said, and the two of them departed.

It was still very early in the morning, and there were no patients waiting outside.

Right at this moment, Shopkeeper Li Hai's voice rang out from nearby.

"Are you leaving, fellow daoists?"

"Thank you for looking after us all these years, Fellow Daoist Li," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute, and this was a very genuine and earnest salute.

If it hadn't been for Li Hai, he wouldn't have been able to identify the flaws in his ways.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Han," Li Hai replied as he hurriedly returned the salute. "I haven't helped you at all over the years. In contrast, I've received much guidance from you, and for that, you have my undying gratitude."

Over the past century or so, Han Li would often visit Li Hai's tea shop to drink and chat.

Even though Li Hai had previously already come to terms with the fact that his cultivation journy was behind him, Han Li's guidance had reignited a spark of hope in his heart, and it seemed like Han Li always knew just the right thing to say to guide him in the right direction.

"I knew from the first time that I saw you that you were far beyond me, and what you've done here is beyond the realm of my comprehension, but in any case, I wish you both the best of luck in your future endeavors," Li Hai said as a look of mixed emotions surfaced in his eyes.

"Likewise, Fellow Daoist Li. I'll be sure to come back to visit your tea shop if the opportunity arises," Han Li said with a smile.

"Please do!" Li Hai replied in an ecstatic manner.

In the next instant, Han Li and Violet Spirit were already nowhere to be seen.

Li Hai stared at the empty street as a sense of sorrow welled up in his heart, and only after standing outside in a daze for a long while did he return to the tea shop.

However, his sorrow then gradually faded away as he looked at his peaceful tea shop.

The world that Han Li and Violet Spirit were in was undoubtedly far more spectacular than this city, but the peaceful life that he led here was a form of bliss in itself.

With that in mind, a satisfied look appeared on Li Hai's face as began preparing the spirit tea for the day.

......

In a nameless mountain range in the Crane Ridge Immortal Region, Han Li and Violet Spirit appeared amid a flash of lightning.

"This looks like a good place," Han Li said as he pointed a finger at a tall mountain up ahead, releasing a streak of golden sword qi that pierced into the mountain face with ease.

The streak of sword qi raced through the mountain like a living creature, digging out a cave abode in the blink of an eye.

"Won't the sparse world's origin qi in the Crane Ridge Immortal Region be detrimental to your corpse soul severance?" Violet Spirit asked as her brows furrowed slightly.

"It's fine. At my cultivation base, I'm able to absorb the world's origin qi from many spaces, so that's not a concern. This is the place where I've gleaned the true meaning of kindness, so my soul is very compatible with this immortal region. Hence, my chances of a successful corpse soul severance will be higher here," Han Li replied.

"I see," Violet Spirit mused with an enlightened expression.

The two of them entered the cave abode, and Han Li set up several layers of restrictions around it before turning to make his way toward the innermost secret chamber.

"Brother Han!" Violet Spirit suddenly called out after him with a concerned expression.

Each corpse soul severance was a very stern test, and failure could result in catastrophic circumstances.

"There's no need to worry. With all of the extensive preparations that we've made, I'm certain that I'll succeed," Han Li said with a confident smile as he gave Violet Spirit's hand a reassuring squeeze.

His confidence instilled within Violet Spirit a great deal of reassurance, and she gave a firm nod in response.

Han Li released her hand and made his way into the secret chamber.

The door of the secret chamber swung shut, and a layer of golden light appeared over its surface, completely isolating it from the outside world.

Chapter 1319: A Discussion of Good and Evil

Inside the secret chamber.

Han Li was busy engraving an array onto the ground, the same one that he had used for his wicked corpse soul severance.

After the array was complete, he pulled out a stack of array tools and began setting them down as well.

This array was extremely complex, and even with his prior experience, it took him an entire day to complete it.

At this moment, countless tiny runes were dancing over the yin yang symbol on the ground, which was giving off bursts of translucent light that illuminated the entire secret chamber.

Han Li gave a pleased nod as he swept a sleeve through the air to summon an Earthly Deity Avatar puppet, which he set down in the yin half, while he sat down in the yang half.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he activated the array, and a hemispherical light barrier appeared, encompassing both him and the puppet within it.

Immediately thereafter, chains formed by flames, glacial qi, lightning, and other various other things shot out of the light barrier before piercing into the puppet's body.

After that, Han Li closed his eyes and entered his own consciousness.

In contrast with during his wicked corpse soul severance, his consciousness was currently extremely peaceful, with only a white-robed Han Li seated inside with his legs crossed and his eyes closed in meditation.

"Welcome," the white-robed Han Li said as he opened his eyes, and there wasn't any animosity or confrontation within them.

"Were you waiting for me?" Han Li asked while secretly preparing for battle.

"There's no need to be so tense. I'm not your wicked corpse soul, I have no intention of fighting you. Please, take a seat," the white-robed Han Li said with a faint smile, and a cushion, a tea table, a teapot, and two teacups appeared out of thin air at his behest.

These things had all been formed by spiritual sense, yet they appeared no different from actual objects.

Even Han Li was unable to accomplish such a feat with his spiritual sense, yet his kind corpse soul had been able to do so with ease.

"What is the meaning of this?" Han Li asked as he sat down across from his kind corpse soul.

"It's in the nature of one's three corpse souls to try and seize the body of their host, but that doesn't necessarily have to come down to a battle," the white-robed Han Li said as he took a sip of tea while pushing the other cup toward Han Li.

"How are we going to reach an outcome without a battle?" Han Li asked.

"It's very simple, all we need to do is have a discussion," the white-robed Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"A discussion?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"That's right. I want to discuss with you the concepts of good and evil. If your answers are satisfactory, I will voluntarily banish myself from this body. Of course, if your answers prove to be unsatisfactory, then I'll have to turn to more forceful measures," the white-robed Han Li replied.

"You can certainly give that a try," Han Li harrumphed coldly as a burst of tremendous spiritual sense erupted out of his body, causing his nearby consciousness to rumble violently.

The teacup in the white-robed Han Li's hands instantly shattered before dissipating into nothingness.

However, he remained unfazed as he conjured up a new cup with a faint smile on his face.

The unrest in Han Li's consciousness subsided at his behest, and he said, "If you want to have a discussion, then I'm happy to humor you. What questions do you want to ask me?"

"Alright, my first question is: why are there both good and evil people?" the kind corpse soul asked.

"No one is inherently good or bad. Instead, good and evil are rooted in one's heart," Han Li replied.

"It's said that karma will give unto people what they deserve, but that's not actually the case. There are many kind and virtuous people who lead miserable lives, just as there are many evil-doers who seem to have everything going in their favor. Why is that?" the kind corpse soul asked.

"This is a very superficial way of looking at things. What is good, and what is evil? These questions cannot be answered through mere surface-level observations. As long as one is benefiting others and the world around them, even if they beat or abuse someone, that could be considered an act of good.

“In contrast, if one is solely self-serving, then even if they display respect and reverence to others, it will only be a sycophantic gesture that's evil in nature. If someone commits kind deeds and accumulates good karma, even if they lead impoverished and miserable lives, it's often the case that their descendants will benefit from their actions and lead better lives than they do.

“In contrast, even if an evil-doer is able to revel in riches for a time, a far worse will await them down the line," Han Li replied.

The kind corpse soul raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, then asked, "In that case, what is good, and what is evil?"

"Actions that benefit both oneself and others can be referred to as good, while actions that benefit others at the expense of oneself can be said to serve the greater good. Actions that are detrimental to both oneself and others are evil, while actions that benefit oneself at the expense of others are an even greater evil," Han Li replied.

"So all acts that benefit others can be referred to as good?" the kind corpse soul asked.

"No, it also depends on one's intentions. Those who commit kind deeds for ulterior motives are not truly good and virtuous. Only those who do good purely out of the kindness of their hearts without seeking compensation are truly good," Han Li replied.

A pleased look flashed through the kind corpse soul's eyes, and he continued, "Consider this then: an old man who is unable to swim has fallen into the water. A young merchant that's passing through saves the old man, and the latter compensates the young man with a silver ingot, which is gleefully accepted. Is that an act of good?"

"It is," Han Li replied.

"But you just said that only acts of kindness committed without the desire for compensation can be considered good. The merchant has taken the old man's money as compensation, so aren't his intentions impure?" the kind corpse soul asked.

"Regardless of whether that merchant expected to be compensated prior to saving the old man, word of his feat will be sure to encourage others to do good, and as long as a certain action can benefit the masses, it can be referred to as good," Han Li replied.

"It's often said that all lay load on the willing horse. How do you interpret that?" the kind corpse soul asked.

"This is indeed something that happens, but it's a rare occurrence and far from the norm. Only by accepting the minor injustices of the world with an open heart and mind can we continue to do good with an untarnished heart. Otherwise, we will be overcome with pettiness and resentment and lose our way," Han Li replied.

The kind corpse soul was silent for a moment, then said in an earnest and heartfelt manner, "I am truly impressed. I have one final question for you to answer."

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted with a smile.

"There are many people in this world who speak of goodness and righteousness, but when it comes time to put such concepts into practice, their actions are often lacking. I can see that you have a very deep understanding of the true meaning of kindness, but how is one supposed to actually put this into practice?" the kind corpse soul asked.

"Do not seek to give or take, do not develop fixations, and do not waver from your conviction. Do what brings the greatest good to the most people, and kindness will naturally be achieved," Han Li replied.

"Fantastic! Your answers have proven more than satisfactory!" the kind corpse soul exclaimed as he clapped his hands together in a pleased manner, then flew away as a ball of white light, seemingly trying to leave Han Li's consciousness.

However, it seemed to have been stopped in its tracks by an invisible barrier.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he immediately raised a hand before bringing it down in a forceful severing motion.

A peerlessly sharp sword projection appeared in his consciousness, and the connection between his kind corpse soul and his consciousness was instantly severed, allowing it to leave as it pleased.

Inside the secret chamber, Han Li opened his eyes as a ball of white light flew out of his body, and along with it went close to half of his immortal spiritual power and time law threads.

The ball of white light vanished into the puppet in the array in a flash, while Han Li shuddered violently as blood came spurting out of all of his orifices.

Even though the ball of white light had taken close to half of his immortal spiritual power and law powers, his 1,320th immortal acupoint had opened up, elevating him to the late-Great Encompassment Stage.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of invisible force descended upon him, and the space around became twisted and warped, as if to separate him from the rest of the world.

All of a sudden, the space above him parted to reveal a boundless sea of golden light, and a burst of almighty law powers descended from the golden sea to envelop him.

Han Li could sense the aura of the vast and unfathomable aura of the Heavenly Dao within the sea of golden light.

At this point, he was already very close to the pinnacle of cultivation, but in the face of this unfathomable power, he was still made to feel as powerless and vulnerable as an ant.

Even the almighty auras of Bone Emperor, the Reincarnation Palace Master, and all of the other Dao Ancestors that Han Li had encountered in the past were completely dwarfed by the aura of this golden sea.

Could this be the laws of time within the Heavenly Dao?

Right at this moment, the sea of golden light suddenly began to churn violently, and a beam of golden light descended from within before surging into his body.

The golden light was imbued with incredibly formidable time law powers, and within the span of just a few breaths, all of the time law powers that he had lost had been replenished, while the number of time law threads in his possession quickly returned to one thousand eight hundred.

At the same time, the nearby space churned violently as bursts of world's origin qi converged from all directions before surging into his body, and in the blink of an eye, his immortal spiritual power reserves were fully replenished as well.

Inside another room in the cave abode, Violet Spirit's eyes abruptly sprang open as she cast a stunned gaze toward the secret chamber where Han Li was cultivating in seclusion.

Chapter 1320: Destiny

Heavenly Court, Celestial Time Peak.

The mountain was surrounded by layers upon layers of golden divine clouds, above which stood an enormous stone plaque that was over a hundred thousand feet tall and giving off dazzling, golden radiance.

The plaque was riddled with golden characters that appeared to have been names that varied in size, and the golden names were laid out from top to bottom in order of largest to smallest.

The third name on the plaque was none other than Han Li, and right at this moment, it suddenly swelled drastically in size before leapfrogging the two names above it to reach the top of the list.

Immediately thereafter, a white-robed man in a wheelchair appeared in front of the stone plaque amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

Standing beside him was a young man with a golden complexion that was matched by his golden robe, giving him a regal appearance.

His eyes were shimmering with a dreamy golden light that made it impossible for one to look directly into them, and they seemed to have transcended some laws of heaven and earth.

"Impossible! How could he have reached the late-Great Encompassment Stage so quickly?" the golden-robed young man exclaimed in an incredulous manner.

"Indeed, he managed to get there before you," the wheelchair-bound man remarked wti ha faint smile.

"Please forgive my incompetence!" the golden-robed young man said as he immediately fell to his knees.

"Han Li has received Miro's inheritance, so it's no surprise that he's progressing faster in his cultivation than you. However, I have high hopes for you, so don't disappoint me," the wheelchair-bound man said, then vanished in a flash.

Only after the wheelchair-bound man's aura had completely faded did the golden-robed young man dare to rise to his feet, and he took a resentful glance at Han Li's name on the stone plaque before vanishing from the spot as well.

......

Inside the secret chamber in the nameless mountain range, more and more time law powers continued to surge into Han Li's body from the golden sea.

All of his profound and immortal acupoints were flashing incessantly, and it was as if his body had become an insatiable black hole, absorbing vast volumes of time law powers and the world's origin qi with each passing second.

His immortal spiritual power and time law powers were rapidly elevating, and even though he didn't gain any further time law threads, all of his existing law threads were becoming thicker and more radiant.

At the same time, his aura was also elevating rapidly, causing the secret chamber around him to tremble violently.

Widening cracks began to appear over the walls, yet right as the secret chamber was about to collapse, a burst of golden light surged out of Han Li's body before sweeping over the surrounding walls, and the cracks quickly shrank before fading away altogether.

Before long, they were brought to the verge of collapse again by Han Li's formidable aura, only to be repaired a second time by the golden light.

The cycle continued to repeat itself as a day and a night quickly passed by, and at this point, the golden light around Han Li had become so blinding that he was barely visible within it.

At the same time, his body had taken on a semi-transparent appearance, and all of his time law threads were clearly visible within.

These law threads had become over ten times thicker than before, and they were wound around all parts of his body like indestructible chains.

At the same time, his aura had become so vast that it wasn't inferior in the slightest to that of Bone Emperor, but it was still somewhat lacking compared with the unfathomable Reincarnation Palace Master.

Right at this moment, the golden sea above him suddenly began to ripple before quickly fading away, and the split space was also sealed back up again as everything returned to normal in the secret chamber.

The golden light around Han Li quickly dissipated, and all of a sudden, his aura completely faded away, making it appear as if he were a mortal that had never cultivated before.

The array in the secret chamber had already been destroyed at this point, while the kind corpse soul was standing completely still in a corner, having already acclimated himself to his new body.

All of a sudden, a hint of fear flashed through his eyes as he sized up Han Li.

No more than a day and a night ago, he had been able to stand toe to toe against Han Li to have a discussion as equals, but right now, Han Li was like a boundless ocean to him.

Despite his best efforts, he was unable to glean the depths of Han Li's true power, and as he delved deeper, he felt as if he were about to be sucked in, prompting him to hurriedly withdraw his spiritual sense.

"Congratulations on your breakthrough, Fellow Daoist," he said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"It was all thanks to you," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"Given your powers, even if I had refused to vacate your body, I would've been severed by force anyway, so you have nothing to thank me for," the kind corpse soul said with a shake of his head.

"I refined this Earthly Deity Avatar precisely for this purpose. I'm hoping it's at least decently compatible with you," Han Li said.

"It's perfect. Thank you for creating such a fine vessel for me," the kind corpse soul replied with a pleased smile.

He then cupped his fist in a salute as he continued, "While my decision to leave voluntarily wouldn't have made much of a difference in the grand scheme of things, it's at least spared you a bit of trouble, so in exchange, I would like to raise a request."

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted.

"Now that you've reached the late-Great Encompassment Stage, I presume you're planning to travel to the Reincarnation Palace. With your current powers, you naturally have nothing to fear, but I do not wish to get swept up in this conflict," the kind corpse soul said.

"So you want to leave?" Han Li asked.

"Rest assured, I won't turn to the Reincarnation Palace or the Heavenly Court to oppose you. Instead, I've found my calling in seeing you travel from place to place while helping others, and I want to continue in your footsteps to pursue the greatest good," the kind corpse soul said with a pure and earnest look in his eyes.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then said, "I'm happy to support this wish of yours."

"In that case, I'll be taking my leave. Look after yourself, Fellow Daoist," the kind corpse soul said in an ecstatic manner as he cupped his fist in a parting salute, then vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden light.

Han Li remained still on the spot, making no effort to prevent the kind corpse soul's departure.

With the kind corpse soul gone, he wouldn't have to constantly be on his guard, so this was a good thing for him as well.

After taking a moment to assess his internal condition, a look of elation slowly began to appear on his face.

He had already anticipated that a breakthrough to the late-Great Encompassment Stage would result in a significant evolution, but only now did he come to realize that he had underestimated just how drastic the change would be.

He felt as if he had stepped in a brand new world, and everything was different from before.

He reached out to stroke the space beside him without drawing upon any of his immortal spiritual power, time law powers, or his physical strength, and a spatial hole that was over a hundred feet in diameter instantly appeared within the secret chamber.

Shards of fragmented space shot out of the hole before flying toward the walls of the secret chamber, but they were instantly stopped in their tracks at Han Li's behest, as if they had been halted by some type of invisible force.

Han Li looked down at his own hand with an amazed expression.

At this moment, he felt as if some type of profound power had entered his body, granting him a level of unprecedented control over the surrounding world, as if he had become an omnipotent being.

Han Li used this newfound power to inspect his surroundings, and the entirety of the Crane Ridge Immortal Region was instantly revealed to him with no blind spots, and everything was ten times clearer than before.

At this moment, his kind corpse soul was observing a certain city, while in the previous city that Han Li had been in, Li Hai was serving tea to some customers.

On top of that, he was able to see some nearby immortal regions and even some lower realms with incredible ease and clarity.

Could this be the power of the Heavenly Dao?

He had seen in a scripture in the past that once one cultivated a type of law powers to the very pinnacle, they would be able to communicate with the Great Dao of heaven and earth and attain near-omnipotent power.

However, this was something that should've only applied to Dao Ancestors, so how was he able to do this at only the late-Great Encompassment Stage?

Intrigued by this change, Han Li thrust a palm upward, and a gargantuan, golden hand appeared in the Extraheavensphere above his head, encompassing a boundless expanse of space beneath it.

A burst of terrifying energy fluctuations erupted out of the golden hand, and all of the asteroids and energy storms beneath it were instantly reduced to nothingness.

The space in the Extraheavensphere collapsed violently, creating a black hole that rivaled the size of some of the smaller immortal regions, and it began devouring everything around it in a frenzy.

However, immediately thereafter, the golden hand gently smoothed over the black hole, and it instantly vanished without a trace.

The golden hand itself then also faded away, while Han Li looked down in amazement at his own hand for a second time.

At this point, it was already confirmed to him that he was indeed able to draw upon the power of the Heavenly Dao. As for why this was the case, perhaps it was because he was cultivating one of the three paramount laws.

With his current powers, he wouldn't have to fear even Dao Ancestors.

With that in mind, it was no wonder that the Reincarnation Palace Master and the Devilish Monarch were both so fearsome, even though they were only at the Great Encompassment Stage.

However, he still had to keep making strides in his cultivation, and once he reached the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage, he would theoretically be able to stand toe to toe against the Reincarnation Palace Master and the Devilish Monarch.

Finally, he had reached the true pinnacle of cultivation, a determined look appeared in his eyes as he internally vowed to rescue Nangong Wan and bring her back to his side.

After that, he took a deep breath to suppress the elation in his heart, then sat back down with his legs crossed.

Even though he had reached the late-Great Encompassment Stage, his cultivation base still required consolidation.

He released his spirit domain, then activated the Celestial Time Array, and the flow of time within the spirit domain was instantly accelerated by a hundred thousandfold.

In the wake of his breakthrough, the space of accelerated time had become even more potent.

On top of that, his control over the world's origin qi had also improved by an unfathomable extent, and he was able to draw in the world's origin qi to support the Celestial Time Array, significantly slowing down the rate at which the array consumed Immortal Origin Stones.

After that, he sat down with his legs crossed, and countless rays of golden light appeared around him.

Chapter 1321: Brewing Unrest

In the southern region of the Middle Earth Immortal Region was a continent called the Southern Gaze Continent, stretching along the southern coastline of which was a mountain range that was hundreds of thousands of kilometers in length, and in the mountain range were ninety-eight volcanos, all of which were active.

Every century or so, one or two of these volcanoes would erupt, and on each occasion, countless vagrant cultivators and cultivators from the immortal sects on the Southern Gaze Continent would arrive to marvel at the spectacle.

Of course, they didn't come here purely for sightseeing purposes. Instead, they came to try their luck to see if they could find a spirit material called Fire Refinement Stone from the magma that erupted out of the volcanoes.

In the past, the Heavenly Court had always turned a blind eye to this, allowing the cultivators to try their luck to secure what they could, but things were different this year.

It had been predicted that seventeen volcanoes would erupt at once this year, but right as they were about to erupt, the immortal envoys of the Heaven Guard Pavilion had intervened, guiding the fire veins into the western sea to prevent the eruptions.

None of the cultivators on the continent raised any complaints about this as they knew that this had been done in preparation for the Bodhi Banquet.

In this mountain range was a structure known as the Heaven Answer Gate, which was a very important structure to the Heavenly Court.

The Heaven Answer Gate was the southern gate through which cultivators of other immortal regions entered the Middle Earth Immortal Region, so it was often also referred to as the Southern Heavenly Gate.

To put it more accurately, it was actually a giant teleportation array with tens of thousands of teleportation arrays of different sizes constructed within it, connected to thirty-five other large immortal regions and capable of teleporting hundreds of thousands of people at a time.

With the gate opened, a spatial passageway leading to the other thirty-five large immortal regions could be established, allowing cultivators through from both sides, and there were three more Heaven Answer Gates just like this one.

As the core of the True Immortal Realm, the Middle Earth Immortal Region had a total of nine continents and four seas, all of which were incredibly vast.

The Heavenly Palace Continent was situated at the center of the nine continents and four seas, and it was the basis of the Heavenly Court. There were also the Eastern Victory Continent, the Western Adulation Continent, the Southern Gaze Continent, and the Northern Complete Continent, which were situated respectively in the eastern, western, southern, and northern seas.

Each of these continents had its own Heaven Guard Pavilion and Heaven Answer Gate.

All of the Heaven Answer Gates were connected to the other large immortal regions and were guarded by divine generals. Additionally, all of the Heaven Guard Pavilions were also very important structures, and Dao Ancestors were stationed there all year round.

With the Bodhi Banquet fast approaching, many cultivators from all over the True Immortal Realm had already begun to gather in the Middle Earth Immortal Region. In addition to those who had received Bodhi Tokens, there were also cultivators who had come purely to spectate this grand event.

Even though the Bodhi Banquet was going to be held on the Heavenly Palace Continent, all types of smaller festive events were going to be held on the other continents as well, and countless precious and exotic treasures from all over the True Immortal Realm were going to appear on the Middle Earth Immortal Region, thereby giving rise to all types of auctions and exchange events, all of which were very alluring.

However, in order to hold such a prestigious event, the Heavenly Court was also going to be under an immense amount of pressure. During the course of the event, it was estimated that the cultivator population of the Middle Earth Immortal Region was going to increase by in excess of tenfold, so regardless of what security measures were adopted, there were inevitably going to be some unsavory figures that managed to slip through the cracks.

......

In the Reverse Bark Immortal Region.

There was a snowfield that stretched for close to a hundred thousand kilometers, and at this moment, it was riddled with crimson flames that resembled radiant, red lotus flowers, leaving the ground charred and blackened.

The entire snowfield was encompassed within an enormous, crimson spirit domain, and all of the snow that fell upon the spirit domain from above were instantly evaporated.

At the center of the snowfield was a giant crater that was over ten thousand feet in size, lying within which was the body of an armorclad, demonic cultivator that was missing half of its head. The golden blood that was pouring out of their body clearly indicated that they had reached a very lofty cultivation base prior to meeting their demise.

Judging from the remaining half of their head, it was possible to tell that they had been some type of wolf demon.

This man was the patriarch of the largest demonic sect in the Reverse Bark Immortal Region, the Myriad Demon Grotto, and he was a late-Great Encompassment cultivator.

He was on his way to the Middle Earth Immortal Region to attend the Bodhi Banquet with his direct disciples, but he had been ambushed here en route to the teleportation array.

At the very least, his body remained mostly intact, while his disciples had already been completely wiped out of existence.

A dull thump rang out as a tall and imposing man jumped down from the edge of the crater to land beside the body.

The man had a head of curly, red hair that draped down behind him in a casual manner, and his facial features were completely devoid of emotions. His skin was riddled with red patterns that resembled fiery clouds, and they were flashing incessantly, giving off a scorching aura that caused the surrounding space to shimmer and warp.

He bent down to pick up a Bodhi Token from beside the body, then wiped the blood from it before casually tossing it out of the crater behind him.

Standing at the edge of the crater was a woman in a black dress, and she caught the token, then inspected it momentarily before stowing it away.

The woman had an alluring figure coupled with skin that was as fair and delicate as mutton fat jade, and her facial features were also stunningly gorgeous. However, half of her face was concealed behind the hair that trailed down from her forehead, and the tiny section of the concealed half of her face that had been left exposed was riddled with fish-scale-like scars.

"It's time to go, Yan Zhuo. According to the palace master's instructions, whether we killed Rong Quan or not is hardly of consequence, whereas Daoist Master Tong Qiu is someone that we have to kill," the woman said.

"I know," the red-haired man by the name of Yan Zhuo replied, then removed the storage bracelet from Rong Quan's wrist before jumping out of the crater.

"You know, you can be really stubborn sometimes. Why did you insist on coming here?" the woman sighed.

"Killing Rong Quan serves as a warning shot to Tong Qiu, so he'll most likely put his plans of traveling to the Middle Earth Immortal Region on hold. I suppose that's a good thing, seeing as we won't have to find a place to intercept him. Instead, we can just go kill him in his sect. You remember our agreement, right, Xuan Yu? I don't care what happens to the disciples of his sect, but the ancestral hall must be demolished," Yan Zhuo said.

"I'm only responsible for claiming Tong Qiu's head, you can do with the others as you please. This is the first time that all eight of us Reincarnation Envoys have been deployed together, and the palace master has encouraged us to cause as much pandemonium as possible," Xuan Yu replied.

With that, the two of them sprang up into the air and quickly vanished out of sight, while the spirit domain faded away, and before long, all signs of the battle that had just taken place had been buried under a blanket of fresh snow.

There were many more similar ambushes and assassinations taking place in other immortal regions to varying degrees of success, but most of them resulted in the targets' demise.

The deaths of such almighty cultivators would've normally created massive stirs throughout their native immortal regions, but for some reason, news of these events had been completely stifled.

Most of the immortal regions were still eagerly awaiting the commencement of the Bodhi Banquet, completely oblivious to the storm that was brewing on the horizon.

......

In a certain, unknown immortal region, there was a huge, gourd-shaped canyon that was filled with miasma and littered with bodies.

The entire canyon was filled with all types of remains, including those that belonged to ordinary wild beasts, as well as the remains of powerful demon beasts and human cultivators, some of which were still giving off fearsome auras.

The miasma was even thicker deep in the canyon, and at this moment, there was a knocking sound ringing out incessantly from within.

Through the dense miasma, one could see a gorgeous young woman in a yellow dress seated with her legs crossed atop a giant rock.

The young woman was none other than Jin Tong, and at this moment, she was knocking on the huge rock beneath her with a demon beast bone in her hand.

"You can't just keep hiding like this. You're the only other Great Encompassment Stage Gold Devouring Immortal aside from me. Once I've devoured you, it'll only be a matter of time before my powers as a Dao Ancestor are restored. Don't you want revenge? Are you going to hide here your entire life? You've eaten so much trash over the years, have you still not had enough?" Jin Tong asked.

She continued to knock on the giant rock, but received no response.

A cold look flashed through her eyes as she harrumphed, "Fine. If you're not going to come out, then I'll just have to make you!"

As soon as her voice trailed off, she sprang up into the air, then hurled the bone in her hand downward like a javelin, sending it crashing down onto the huge rock below with incredible force.

A resounding boom rang out as the massive rock exploded into countless pieces, and a giant, golden beetle flew out from underneath before racing away as a streak of golden light.

"Get back here!"

Jin Tong immediately adopted her Gold Devouring Immortal form as well, and a fierce battle commenced between the two.

The surrounding space trembled violently as golden light and black spatial rifts intertwined with one another, and the entire area in a radius of hundreds of thousands of kilometers was instantly transformed into an inhospitable death zone.

Chapter 1322: Extortion

In the Crane Ridge Immortal Region.

The cave abode hidden in that nameless mountain range had already been sealed for several hundred years.

Violet Spirit was seated with her legs crossed in meditation on a stone bed in one of the rooms of the cave abode.

Right at this moment, her eyes sprang open, and she cast her gaze forward with an elated look on her face.

Immediately thereafter, the door of the secret chamber across from her room was opened, and Han Li emerged from within before giving her a warm smile.

Violet Spirit stood up from her bed, and a hint of incredulity flashed through her eyes at the sight of Han Li.

"Your aura..." she exclaimed.

"I've only just come out of seclusion, so my aura fluctuations are still a little unstable, but everything will be back to normal after a few days," Han Li reassured with a smile.

"I'm referring to your cultivation base," Violet Spirit said with a concerned look in her eyes.

"You're not mistaken, I have indeed reached the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage. However, I can assure you that I haven't taken any extreme measures to get here. It's just that my cultivation arts are rather special, and that has allowed me to make rapid progress without compromising on the stability of my cultivation foundation," Han Li said.

"That's good to hear," Violet Spirit replied with a nod, following which a hint of dejection appeared on her face.

Now that Han Li had reached the pinnacle of the Great Encompassment Stage, he was most likely going to return to the underworld soon.

Right at this moment, Han Li's expression suddenly changed slightly as he flipped a hand over to produce his black Reincarnation Palace mask.

After putting on the mask, he tapped a finger against his own glabella, and a beam of light instantly shot out of the mask to form a projection of a male figure.

It was the Reincarnation Palace Master, and Han Li immediately knew that something had to have gone wrong for the Reincarnation Palace Master to have contacted him.

"What happened?"

"Rushuang was abducted by the Heavenly Court," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied after a brief hesitation.

"What did you just say?" Han Li exclaimed, and Violet Spirit's expression also changed drastically upon hearing this.

At some point, Han Li had chosen to reveal the truth to her, so she was aware of the Reincarnation Palace Master's identity, as well as the fact that Gan Rushuang and Nangong Wan were one and the same.

"Rushuang woke up not long after you left the underworld, and in the end, she decided that she wanted to return to being Nangong Wan as opposed to being my wife," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

"How was she abducted by the Heavenly Court? Didn't you tell me that you could keep her safe?" Han Li snapped in a furious manner.

"After she chose you, she wanted to immediately leave to find you, but she was worried about becoming a burden to you, and I was also worried for her safety, so I never let her leave. However, after that, it was as if you had disappeared off the face of the Immortal Realm, and I wasn't even able to contact you through your mask.

“Not long ago, she left the underworld on her own to search for you while I was in seclusion, and the Heavenly Court pounced on the opportunity to capture her," the Reincarnation Palace Master revealed.

"Have you managed to find out where she is?" Han Li asked.

"No. The Heavenly Court has taken extensive measures to ensure that she remains hidden. However, not long after she was abducted, I received a message from Gu Huojin, demanding that I go to the Middle Earth Immortal Region. He has promised me that they won't hurt her as long as I do as he says, and that they'll immediately release her once I've reached the Middle Earth Immortal Region," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

Han Li fell silent upon hearing this.

Given how sorely the Heavenly Court resented the Reincarnation Palace Master, it didn't exactly take a genius to predict what would become of him if he were to fall into their grasp.

"I've already agreed to travel to the Middle Earth Immortal Region," the Reincarnation Palace Master declared.

"When will you be setting off?" Han Li asked.

"I still have to make some preparations. Otherwise, not only will I not be able to save Rushuang, all of my other plans will also be thrown into disarray," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"I'm going with you," Han Li said without any hesitation.

The Reincarnation Palace Master hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then replied, "I suppose that would be for the best. That way, you can take Rushuang to safety while I confront Gu Huojin."

"The person that I'll be taking with me is Nangong Wan, not Gan Rushuang. I also have some matters to attend to, and I'll meet up with you in the underworld once I'm ready," Han Li said.

"Alright, I'll be waiting," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"Also, the Heavenly Court is not to be trusted, so it would be best if you could find out where Wan'er is being kept in case they go back on their word and refuse to release her," Heavenly Court continued.

"I'll notify you if I find out anything," the Reincarnation Palace Master promised.

With that, the projection from Han Li's Reincarnation Palace mask faded away, while Violet Spirit turned to him with a concerned gaze.

Before Han Li had a chance to say anything, Violet Spirit beat him to the punch.

"Go and save her."

"Let's go back for now," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Go back where?" Violet Spirit asked.

"The Northern Glacial Immortal Region," Han Li replied.

......

Meanwhile, in a palace in the underworld.

The Reincarnation Palace Master had just finished his communication with Han Li, and he made his way down from a raised platform.

Right at this moment, a black-robed figure hurriedly made their way into the palace. Their neck and face were covered in a thick layer of bandages, upon which were inscribed a series of golden runes, presenting a peculiar sight to behold.

"Palace Master, I've just conducted some divination to track down Immortal Lord Huang Lu of the Sky Mound Immortal Region, and he'll be arriving on the Kind Sun Continent soon," the black-robed figure reported in a hoarse voice.

"The Sky Mound Immortal Region has no teleportation array that leads directly to the Middle Earth Immortal Region, so he most likely intends to travel to the Dark Heavens Immortal Region from the Kind Sun Continent so that he can get to the Middle Earth Immortal Region from there. Send a message to Fang Hui and Wu Jiang, instruct them to intercept him on the Kind Sun Continent and kill him and his entourage," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

The black-robed man gave an affirmative response before preparing to depart, only for the Reincarnation Palace Master to suddenly ask, "How long have you been with me, Yuan Chunfeng?"

The black-robed man stopped in his tracks, then pondered the question for a moment before replying, "It's been too long, so I can't clearly recall, but it has to have been a few million years at this point."

"Conduct a heavenly divination to see what my chances of victory are if I go to the Heavenly Court early," the Reincarnation Palace Master requested.

"Are you sure, Palace Master? If I conduct one more heavenly divination, I'll be reduced to a disabled man by divine punishment. On top of that, this matter concerns the Time Dao Ancestor, so I may not be able to glean an outcome even if I tried," Yuan Chunfeng said.

"In that case, forget about it. I still have to rely on you to predict the routes that all of the Great Encompassment cultivators are going to take to reach the Bodhi Banquet. Otherwise, it'll become next to impossible to intercept them," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

Yuan Chunfeng didn't say anything further before preparing to depart again, but once again, he was stopped by a sudden remark from the Reincarnation Palace Master.

"I must say, it's quite smart of your Heavenmend Sect to have hedged your bets on both the Heavenly Court and my Reincarnation Palace."

"I'm afraid that's more borne out of necessity than anything else. Both you and the Time Dao Ancestor stand at the very pinnacle of the True Immortal Realm, and the conflict between you two has completely stirred up even the Heavenly Dao. As a result, our Heavenmend Sect is unable to predict the outcome, so we had no choice but to split our eggs and put them in both baskets," Yuan Chunfeng said.

"Patriarch Chen Tuan has chosen to place his bets on Gu Huojin, yet as his first-ever disciple, you've chosen to side with me. In light of that, it looks like your Heavenmend Sect still likes the Heavenly Court's chances better than ours. Regardless of the outcome, you'll be able to ensure that your sect survives to tell the tale," the Reincarnation Palace Master remarked.

"That may be the case, but if the Heavenly Court wins, then I will meet my demise with the Reincarnation Palace, so please do come out on top, both for your sake and mine," Yuan Chunfeng said.

The Reincarnation Palace Master nodded in response as he gestured for Yuan Chunfeng to leave, and before long, he was the only one left standing in the empty palace.

......

Over two years flew by in a flash.

A streak of light descended out of the heavens outside a border city on the Ancient Cloud Continent of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

Within the streak of light were none other than Han Li and Violet Spirit, and the two of them had arrived beside a dilapidated stone pergola outside the city.

The layer of faint, golden light around them kept out the surrounding, gray mist, and a hint of reminiscence appeared in Han Li's eyes as he mused, "I stayed in this city for a short time on my way to the Blaze Dragon Dao. It certainly has changed quite a bit since then."

"The Northern Glacial Immortal Region and all of the nearby immortal regions have already been taken over by the Gray Realm, so of course things have changed drastically," Violet Spirit replied.

"Most of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region has already been modified by the Gray Realm, forcing the native cultivators to cower in the cities. I don't think it'll be long before this city falls as well," Han Li sighed.

"There's not much that can be done. Not only has the Heavenly Court not sent any reinforcements, they've done everything in their power to keep this matter a secret, so there aren't many people that are even aware of the Gray Realm invasion. Thankfully, the Gray Realm hasn't been too aggressive with its expansion. Otherwise, even the Heavenly Court may not be able to keep everything under wraps," Violet Spirit said.

"It appears that there's some type of unspoken agreement between the Heavenly Court and the Gray Realm. As long as one doesn't overpress, the other won't retaliate," Han Li said with a cold smile.

"Why is that?" Violet Spirit asked.

Chapter 1323: Revisiting the Giant Eye

"The Gray Realm wants to take a steady approach and establish a foundation in preparation for future expansion. As for the Heavenly Court, on one hand, it wants to keep up appearances to ensure that the Bodhi Banquet is held smoothly, and on the other hand, it wants to focus most of its power on dealing with the Reincarnation Palace," Han Li explained.

"It's always those at the bottom of the pecking order who suffer the most," Violet Spirit sighed.

"Let's go, we don't have much time," Han Li said, and the two of them departed from the Ancient Cloud Continent to travel to the Primordial Wave Continent.

As the two of them traveled over the sea, the seawater gradually became darker and darker in color, gradually turning from the initial bright blue to a blackish-purple color.

At the same time, blankets of dark clouds had begun to appear in the sky at extremely low altitudes, hanging at only no more than six hundred to seven hundred feet above the surface of the sea.

At this moment, gusts of howling wind were blowing over the sea, raising giant waves that rose up to meet the dark clouds above.

Bursts of thunderous rumbling rang out as incredibly thick bolts of lightning flashed within the dense clouds, with the occasional one crashing down onto the sea below to momentarily illuminate the darkness.

Even before entering the lightning sea, Han Li was already able to feel the destructive aura of the lightning up ahead, and even the gray mist released by the Gray Realm didn't dare to encroach upon this area.

"It's going to get a little dangerous from here, so wait for me in the Flower Branch domain," Han Li said to Violet Spirit, and the latter duly obliged.

After Violet Spirit entered the Flower Branch domain, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to summon his seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, then jumped onto one of them, using it as a vessel to carry him through the air.

The other seventy-one Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords circled around him incessantly, forming a protective sword array.

As soon as Han Li flew into the lightning sea, a giant bolt of purple lightning came crashing down upon him, only to be intercepted by an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

A metallic ringing sound rang out as the lightning struck the flying sword, as if the latter were crying out in pain, and arcs of purple lightning erupted in all directions.

As opposed to accelerating after that initial lightning strike, Han Li slowed down significantly, and a bolt of purple lightning came crashing down upon him around once every one thousand feet.

His Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords took turns shielding him from the purple lightning, and as time passed, a series of fine lightning patterns began to appear over the swords from the repeated lightning strikes.

This was a very encouraging sight for Han Li, and as he advanced deeper, the lightning strikes became more powerful and frequent, as azure, purple, golden, and silver lightning came crashing down upon him in a haphazard fashion.

As opposing to withstanding the lightning strikes one by one, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had surrounded Han Li to form a protective barrier that kept the ferocious barrage of lightning at bay.

Close to a month flew by in a flash, and during this time, Han Li was swept up in several extremely fearsome lightning storms, but he was able to make it through unscathed without much trouble each time.

In the process, his seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were also becoming more and more powerful.

Right at this moment, several hundred bolts of golden lightning came crashing down in unison, forming a golden lightning waterfall.

All of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew forward before connecting with one another end to end to form an arched bridge directly above Han Li.

The golden lightning waterfall crashed down onto the arched bridge with an almighty boom, and countless arcs of golden lightning erupted forth in all directions.

All of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were riddled with lightning patterns that resembled cracks, and the lightning law powers within were becoming more and more vast and natural, to the point that they were beginning to resemble Essential Immortal Treasures like the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword rather than Acquired Immortal Treasures.

Han Li was standing beneath the sword bridge, looking calmly ahead through the spraying electricity.

All of a sudden, a massive, black hole appeared up ahead without any warning, and within it was an indistinct shadow.

Despites its murky appearance, Han Li knew exactly what it was.

With a sweep of his sleeve, all of the flashing lightning up ahead was wiped away like dust, revealing a gargantuan eye within th black hole.

A sense of apprehension welled up in Han Li's heart as he recalled what had happened the first time he had caught sight of this eye.

According to his recollection, the eye was several thousand feet in size and orange in color, with a long and thin pupil down the center that gave off a cold gleam.

At the time, all it had taken was a single glance at the eye for him to suffer severe spiritual sense backlash.

With his spiritual sense back then, it had been impossible for him to glean what laid behind the eye, and he had once speculated extensively on what type of massive beast the eye could've belonged to.

Since then, he had become countless times more powerful than he had been back then, but he still couldn't help but be struck by a sense of awe at the sight of the giant eye.

He had speculated that the eye had been attached to a body, but as it turned out, there was nothing in the black hole aside from a lone eye.

As his gaze fell upon the eye, it also turned slightly to look at him, and he felt as if an explosive thunderclap had suddenly erupted within his spiritual sense.

An enormous gash was instantly torn into the sky above his consciousness, and the resulting headache was so severe that he was barely able to remain in control of himself.

However, in the next instant, a burst of translucent light swept through his consciousness, and the gash was immediately sealed, while the unrest in his consciousness was also quelled.

At this point, he had already mastered all seven levels of the Spirit Refinement Technique, elevating his spiritual sense to unfathomable heights.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and a full moon rose up into the sky before revealing itself to be the Mantra Treasured Axis.

At the center of the hole in the Mantra Treasured Axis was a large, golden eye that was currently closed, and Han Li was staring intently at the orange eye as he thought to himself, Let me see exactly what you are!

All of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis quickly lit up at his behest, and the Eye of Truth sprang open to reveal a golden eyeball.

As soon as the Eye of Truth sprang open, the circle of runes around the pupils instantly began to rapidly revolve, while a burst of faint golden light was projected out of the pupil, and Han Li began viewing the giant eye through the Eye of Truth, as opposed to his physical eyes.

Thin, golden threads began to emerge from the giant eye, then intertwined and connected with one another to gradually form a gargantuan body, one that possessed an ox-like body, but had dragon horns on its head.

Its round belly was riddled with ancient runes, but it only had a single leg, making it somewhat resemble a huge, black hammer. On top of that, there was a long, whip-like tail trailing along behind it.

"Isn't that a Lightning Kui?" Han Li exclaimed to himself.

Han Li wasn't unfamiliar with the Lightning Kui. In fact, he had even previously referenced the patterns on its body in the process of making inscriptions on his Dao Warriors. Never had he imagined that the giant eye here would've been left behind by a Lightning Kui.

However, upon closer inspection, Han Li quickly discovered that this was no ordinary Lightning Kui. Instead, the patterns on its body were imbued with the true meaning of lightning, and they were far more profound than the patterns found on a normal Lightning Kui's body.

With that in mind, Han Li injected more of his time law powers into the Eye of Truth, and the golden light pouring out of it instantly became brighter and denser than before.

The flow of time in the entire lightning sea seemed to have been severed, and everything was brought to an abrupt halt, yet the Lightning Kui had begun to move.

Giant pillars of lightning came crashing down upon its body from the heavens, and its near-indestructible body disintegrated bit by bit, dissipating into spectacular streaks of light that surged up into the heavens.

Unwilling to accept its fate, the Lightning Kui split its own body into two in a final act of desperation, and one half of its body was devoured by the heavens, while the other half surged toward its own left eye in a frenzy.

Before long, its entire body had been reduced to nothingness, leaving only this lone, orange eye hovering in the sky.

Chapter 1324: Sword Refinement

Han Li was stunned beyond belief as he witnessed the scenes unfolding before him, and only after a long while did he return to his senses, upon which he exclaimed to himself, "This eye was left behind by a Dao Ancestor!"

Even after he withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis, Han Li was still reeling from the astonishing sight that he had just witnessed.

He hadn't heard of any Lightning Dao Ancestor before, and this Lightning Kui had most likely been the previous one. With its innate lightning physique, it was able to reign supreme over all of the lightning under the heavens, but as its powers grew, it was ultimately unable to escape the fate of being devoured by the Heavenly Dao.

This lightning eye was the last thing that the Lightning Kui had forcibly left behind in the True Immortal Realm before it was devoured by the Heavenly Dao.

Han Li channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to inspect the lightning eye, and he discovered that the power that it contained was even more immense than he had imagined, but all of it had been converted into pure lightning energy, and not a trace of the Lightning Kui's will was left behind.

This made sense, considering that if the Lightning Kui had managed to preserve some of its will, then it would've begun cultivating again and left this place long ago. On top of that, there was no way that the Heavenly Dao would've left its spiritual sense behind.

After staring at the giant eye for a moment, he suddenly snapped his fingers, releasing a golden light barrier that proliferated outward rapidly to encompass the entire lightning sea.

At the same time, Han Li channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and his five time law treasure manifestations emerged to surround the lightning sea.

As soon as his Oneness Tier spirit domain was summoned, the lightning sea immediately began to resist with all its might, while the orange eye turned to glower intently at Han Li.

The entire lightning sea had become more violent than ever, and countless pillars of lightning came crashing down from above like an endless waterfall to challenge Han Li's spirit domain.

However, Han Li remained completely unfazed, and time in the surrounding space fell completely still at his behest, while the descending pillars of lightning were also instantly immobilized.

Within his spirit domain, he was the only one able to move freely.

As he strode through the air, his seventy-Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords appeared behind him before following along.

He walked a lap around the eye of the Lightning Kui, stopping once every few steps to plant an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in mid-air.

The lap around the giant eye took precisely three hundred and sixty steps, and by then, all of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had already taken up their positions around the eye.

Han Li carefully examined the positioning of the swords to ensure that they were in the right places, then flipped a hand over to produce a pristine white, octagonal jade plate.

The jade plate was none other than the diagram for the Almighty Sword Array.

During these past years of seclusion, Han Li had studied the array diagram extensively, and as his cultivation base progressed, he was finally able to unravel all of its secrets.

He had originally thought that the array diagram had to have been refined by the founding father of the Almighty Sword Sect, but since then, he had discovered that the diagram was far too profound to have possibly been a man-made artifact. Instead, it was a Profound Heavenly Item manifested by the laws of swords.

The sword array possessed no attributes, yet could take on any attribute depending on the flying swords used, and that was because it harbored the laws of swords, thereby allowing it to harness the power of other attributes.

At this moment, all of Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had been used to set up an extremely powerful refinement sword array in the Almighty Sword Array, and Han Li was planning to use the array diagram to refine this eye.

After all of the preparations were complete, Han Li made a hand seal as he began chanting an incantation, and a faint buzzing sound rang out as the patterns on the octagonal jade plate began to glow radiantly, forming a giant projection of an octagonal plate above the eye of the Lightning Kui.

Han Li rose up into the air before sitting down with his legs crossed at the center of the plate projection, and countless sword projections shot out of it at his behest before raining down upon the giant eye below.

At the same time, all seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords began radiating dazzling golden light, which came together to form an enormous cauldron projection, with the eye of Lightning Kui encompassed within.

The octagonal plate projection formed by the array plate served as a lid to seal the cauldron, and bursts of thunderous rumbling rang out as a layer of golden light surfaced over the eye of the Lightning Kui, while all of the lightning churning within the clouds outside the cauldron suddenly subsided.

In the next instant, a series of Lightning Kui projections emerged from the eye, and arcs of incredibly pure, golden lightning were flashing around them as they crashed against the inner wall of the cauldron projection.

With each collision came a deafening boom, while a violent shudder would run through the entire lightning sea.

Seated on the octagonal plate projection, Han Li was also trembling violently from the repeated impacts of the Lightning Kui projections, and he was also being struck by tiny arcs of lightning that were bursting out of the cauldron, but he couldn't allow himself even the slightest lapse in concentration.

Otherwise, if the Lightning Kui were to burst out, not only would the entire cauldron be destroyed, the lightning sea and the two nearby continents would also be ravaged by an unprecedented lightning storm that would erase them from the face of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

All of a sudden, Han Li let loose a thunderous roar, and countless sword projections erupted out of his seventy-two flying swords and sword array diagram before surging into the cauldron.

......

Meanwhile, on the edge of the Primordial Wave Continent.

Countless Gray Realm beings were gathered together on the coastline like a swarm of locusts, looking out at the lighting sea in the distance.

Standing at the forefront of the Gray Realm beings were several hundred Gray Realm cultivators, led by a tall man clad in a suit of rusty, copper armor.

Standing behind him was a short and thin black-robed elderly man, who asked in a hoarse voice, "Should we go and see what's happening, Master Mo Shi?"

"There's no need for that. Whatever it is that's out there, it's not something that we can deal with, so as long as it doesn't come after us, it would be best for us to leave it alone," the tall man by the name of Mo Shi replied with a shake of his head, and the black-robed elderly man gave an affirmative response.

"Make sure to keep everyone in check so that they don't go looking for trouble. Are there any cities on the Primordial Wave Continent that are still yet to be conquered? We're going to have to pick up the pace," Mo Shi instructed.

......

Several months flew by in a flash.

At this point, the lightning sea had undergone a massive transformation, having been reduced to no more than several dozen kilometers in size.

Within what little remained of the lightning clouds, Han Li was walking around the cauldron that contained the eye of the Lightning Kui with a rather frustrated look on his face.

The refinement is already complete, so why can't I break it open?

Inside the cauldron, the orange eye had been reduced to a size of a longan, and there were arcs of golden lightning flashing incessantly over it.

The eye was surrounded by Han Li's seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, all of which had shrunk down by around half, and they were all connected by arcs of lightning, making it appear as if they were a single, unified entity.

By Han Li's estimates, his seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords would all evolve into fourth tier immortal treasures after having the power of the Lightning Kui eye refined into them by his refinement sword array, but for some reason, even though the refinement process was complete, the eye of the Lightning Kui refused to break down.

As a result, Han Li was unable to infuse its power into his swords.

What is the problem? What am I missing?

Right at this moment, a thought suddenly occurred to him, and an ecstatic look appeared on his face as he flipped a hand over to summon his Profound Heavenly Gourd.

Having absorbed the residual law powers of the Profound Heavenly Spiritslash Sword, the gourd currently contained the laws of destruction, which were perfect to help him break open this Lightning Kui eye.

However, a hesitant look then appeared on Han Li's face. Even though the eye had already been refined, it was still something that had been left behind by a Dao Ancestor, so it contained immense lightning power, perhaps too much for the Profound Heavenly Gourd to bear,

However, after some further contemplation, he couldn't think of a better course of action other than to also send his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords into the gourd to help suppress the Lightning Kui eye.

With that in mind, he didn't hesitate any longer, and the cauldron dissipated into nothingness at his behest to expose the eye and his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

All of the residual lightning clouds in the area instantly began to churn violently as a cacophony of deafening thunderclaps rang out.

In response, Han Li hurriedly raised his Profound Heavenly Gourd, then thrust a palm into its underside, and a cloud of green mist instantly emerged from its opening to form a misty vortex.

A burst of tremendous suction force erupted out of the vortex, and the Lightning Kui eye and Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were sucked in in a flash, upon which the lightning and thunder in the surrounding lightning clouds instantly began to subside.

Chapter 1325: Profound Heavenly Sword Spirits

After the Lightning Kui eye and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were sucked into the Profound Heavenly Gourd, Han Li instantly sealed its opening, then began to gently shake it from side to side.

A dull thunderclap instantly rang out from within the gourd, while countless arcs of golden lightning sprang out of its surface, only to be instantly quelled by Han Li.

It was also in the same instant that a loud crack rang out, and a tiny crack appeared on the gourd's surface.

Immediately thereafter, countless more cracks emerged over the entire gourd, and Han Li immediately tossed it up into the air without any hesitation.

He then reached out toward the gourd with both hands, releasing thin, golden threads formed by his time law powers to bind the gourd, and it was as if a radiant, golden outer garment had been conjured up around it.

With the fortification of Han Li's time law powers, the severely cracked Profound Heavenly Gourd was somehow able to hold itself intact, but the runes on its surface were glowing brighter and brighter.

Han Li peered into the gourd with his Infernal Devilish Eyes to discover that his seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were all pressed tightly against the inner wall of the gourd, still maintaining the refinement sword array, while the Lightning Kui eye was enveloped in a ball of dark green light while hovering at the center of the gourd.

The dark green light and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were doing everything in their power to contain the Lightning Kui eye's overwhelming might, and neither side was willing to back down.

In terms of overall power, the Lightning Kui eye naturally held the upper hand. The arcs of lightning that were constantly springing out of it had already completely destroyed the gourd, which would've fallen apart long ago without the support of Han Li's time law powers.

However, the dark green light coupled with the sword array were just barely able to keep its power contained, resulting in an impasse.

After several hours of this, the Profound Heavenly Gourd was finally unable to bear the pressure any longer, and it exploded violently with a deafening boom.

A burst of dark green light erupted out of the gourd, then transformed into a streak of dark green swordlight that parted the sea and the heavens, creating a vast spatial rift that was giving off astonishingly formidable spatial fluctuations.

As for the eye of the Lightning Kui, it had disintegrated into a vast expanse of dazzling, golden radiance during the explosion, and there were countless Lightning Kui projections running rampant within the golden light.

The Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that had been scattered throughout the surrounding area instantly plunged headfirst into the ball of golden light, causing it to become so bright that even Han Li was unable to see what was happening inside.

However, he could sense some type of peculiar energy fluctuations within the golden radiance, and all of a sudden, streaks of swordlight came erupting out of it in all directions.

One of the streaks of swordlight had flown straight into the closing spatial rift, and an alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face as he hurriedly reached into the gaping rift before pulling his arm back in a forceful motion.

His right sleeve was instantly torn to shreds, but his arm remained completely unscathed, and to his surprise, he was holding onto a tiny, green hand, rather than an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

Immediately thereafter, all of the surrounding streaks of swordlight shot back to his side, and all of them landed on his body before transforming into tiny, green figures that were each around a foot in height.

Several of them were standing on his shoulders, several more had climbed onto his head. There were also quite a few swinging back and forth while hanging from his arms, and there was even one that was standing on his nose, staring into his eyes with a pair of tiny eyes of its own.

These tiny figures were all entirely green in color, with only their hair and eyes taking on a golden coloration, and around each of their ankles and wrists was a golden band with fine, golden lightning patterns etched upon them.

Han Li counted them one by one to discover that there were precisely seventy-two of them, and an intrigued look appeared on his face at this discovery.

Could it be that my Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords have given rise to sword spirits after absorbing the power of the Lightning Kui eye?

As if the tiny, green figures were able to read his mind, as soon as this question occurred to him, all of them rose up into the air to form seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

However, in contrast with the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords of old, all of these flying swords were riddled with golden lightning patterns, and their auras indicated that they had become third tier immortal treasures, an entire tier above what Han Li had anticipated!

While it was only a single tier of difference, there was an unfathomable gulf in power between third and fourth tier immortal treasures, not to mention that there were seventy-two of them!

Furthermore, the seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were now so in sync with him that it was as if they had become extensions of his body, and they instantly rose up into the air to form an incredibly powerful sword array even without the need for any explicit mental instructions.

A rumbling thunderclap rang out as a gargantuan heavenly gate appeared in the sky, and even though the gates were tightly shut, there was an irrepressible lightning aura seeping out of it, one that even Han Li felt rather wary of.

All of a sudden, the giant, golden gate began rumbling violently, and there was a golden sea inside, within which were countless lightning wyrms of all types of different colors, ready to burst out of the gate as soon as they were called upon.

The space around the heavenly gate was trembling from its awesome might, and large rifts were beginning to appear.

A pleased smile appeared on Han Li's face, and the golden heavenly gate slowly swung shut at his behest before fading away.

The seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords reverted back into miniature, green children before descending toward him, and Han Li whisked them away with a sweep of his sleeve.

After that, Han Li opened the Flower Branch domain, in which Violet Spirit was waiting for him in the bamboo pavilion.

"How did it go?"

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face as he replied, "Everything went smoothly. I..."

"Go do what you need to do," Violet Spirit said with a warm smile. "If possible, I'd like to accompany you."

"It's too dangerous, I can't take you to the Heavenly Court with me," Han Li said with a shake of his head.

Violet Spirit seemed to have already anticipated this answer, and she replied, "I understand. I'll wait for you to come back."

"In any case, I'll take you to the underworld first. Once there, you can choose to stay there or travel to Devil Realm, and I'll come find you once I'm done," Han Li said.

"Alright," Violet Spirit replied with a nod.

After the two of them left the Flower Branch domain, Han Li conjured up a lightning teleportation array around them, and they departed from the lightning sea.

......

One month later.

In the underworld, a black-robed woman was pacing back and forth in an agitated manner in front of the stone palace on the island at the center of the Yellow Springs.

The two ghostly generals stationed in front of the palace's entrance exchanged a glance with one another, then returned to standing in a stationary manner.

Wyrm 3 had already been pacing in front of the stone palace non-stop for around half a month, and it seemed that she was waiting for someone.

The two of them had tried to convince her to take a rest on multiple occasions, but to no avail, and they eventually stopped trying.

Right at this moment, a streak of golden light suddenly appeared in the distance, and it was racing toward the island, completely unaffected by the Six Paths Gale winds.

Wyrm 3 was ecstatic to see this, and in the next instant, Han Li and Violet Spirit were already standing before her.

"Where's the palace master?" Han Li asked.

"Let's go in first," Wyrm 3 replied with a hesitant expression.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, then entered the palace with Violet Spirit.

After the palace gates swung shut, Wyrm 3 wasted no time as she revealed, "Father has already set off for the Middle Earth Immortal Region."

"What? Why?" Han Li asked.

"Father has been feeling very guilty for what happened to Mother, and on top of that, there were some other factors that contributed to his decision to make a move earlier than initially planned. From now on, the entire True Immortal Realm is only going to become more and more chaotic.

“Father said that even though the Heavenly Court has promised to release my mother as soon as he arrives in the Middle Earth Immortal Region, things definitely won't be so simple. He's gone to great lengths to try and find out where my mother is being held captive, but to no avail. However, in the process, he managed to find out who it was that captured my mother," Wyrm 3 replied.

"Who is it?" Han Li asked.

"Feng Qingshui. I'm sure you're aware of him," Wyrm 3 replied.

A thoughtful look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

Han Li had encountered Feng Qingshui once back in the Gray Realm, and he knew that the latter was the Water Dao Ancestor.

"I want all of the information that you have on him, including his background, the location of his immortal manor, where he is right now, and records of his past battles," Han Li demanded.

"Are you going to go after him?" Wyrm 3 asked as she raised an eyebrow.

"Your father told you to tell me that it was Feng Qingshui who captured Wan'er precisely so that I would go after him, did he not?" Han Li asked.

Chapter 1326: Separation

"Father didn't say anything about that. The problem is that Feng Qingshui is a Dao Ancestor, while you..."

Han Li wasted no time with words as he revealed his cultivation base to Wyrm 3, and in that instant, it was as if the entire sky had fallen upon the island.

However, he made sure to restrict his aura to only within a radius of thousand feet around him, and in that area, he was like an omnipotent deity, able to control everything on a whim.

Wyrm 3 stumbled back involuntarily in the face of Han Li's almighty aura, and she was momentarily stunned into silence.

After taking a deep breath to compose herself, she said, "It's incredible that you were able to make such significant strides in such a short time. No wonder Father..."

Her voice trailed off there, as if she had decided against saying what she was about to say.

"With him drawing most of the Heavenly Court's attention, this will be the perfect time for me to go after Feng Qingshui. I just hope that he's not at the Heavenly Court right now," Han Li said as he suppressed his own aura again.

"Fortunately for you, he's currently in the Dragon Abyss Immortal Region, where he's been cultivating in seclusion for some time in the Mist Dragon Sect that he founded," Wyrm 3 revealed.

"That's perfect. I'll set off tomorrow," Han Li said.

"Alright, I'll come with you," Wyrm 3 said.

"No, you're not," Han Li rejected flatly.

"Why can't I go? My mother..."

"She chose to be Nangong Wan, so she's not your mother, and I'm sure she also wouldn't want you to come with me," Han Li interjected.

"I don't care how you see it. In my eyes, she is my mother, so I have to go," Wyrm 3 insisted.

"You won't be able to help me at your current cultivation base, and I also need you to escort Violet Spirit to the Devil Realm for me," Han Li said in a frank and straightforward manner, making no effort to spare Wyrm 3's feelings, and sure enough, her face fell slightly upon hearing this.

"You're right, I'll only be a hindrance if I go with you, but why is Violet Spirit going to the Devil Realm?" she asked in a perplexed manner.

"Has something happened?" Han Li asked.

"Are you not aware of what's happened in the Devil Realm? If Violet Spirit intends to go and find Shi Chuankong, then I suggest she change her plans," Wyrm 3 said.

Violet Spirit's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and a sense of foreboding welled up in her heart.

"What happened?" Han Li asked.

"A civil war has been raging in the Devil Realm for over a thousand years at this point, and it's been particularly brutal the past century or so. Everything came to a head seven years ago, during a battle in which the entirety of Night Sun City was destroyed, while the Scalptia Spatial Domain was also completely erased from existence. Shi Chuankong and Shi Kongjie were subjected to a heavy defeat," Wyrm 3 explained.

"Are they still alive?" Han Li asked.

"The Devil Realm is currently completely sealed off to the outside world, so it's very difficult to find out any information. However, according to our sources, Shi Kongjie was killed in battle against the Devilish Monarch, while Shi Chuankong has gone missing, and it's unclear whether he's dead or alive," Wyrm 3 replied.

Han Li fell silent at this piece of grim news.

"Has there still been no news even seven years after the battle?" Violet Spirit asked.

"The Devilish Monarch personally issued an order to seal off the Devil Realm, and he hasn't specified when it'll open to the outside world again, so no new information has come out," Wyrm 3 replied with a shake of her head.

"I'll go to the Devil Realm to find out what's happened once I'm back from the Heavenly Court," Han Li said with a grim expression, and Wyrm 3 nodded in response.

"Seeing as the Devil Realm is no longer safe or accessible, you can wait for me in the underworld instead," Han Li said to Violet Spirit, who gave a concerned nod.

"By the way, do you know where Weeping Soul is right now?" Han Li asked.

"She went to the Soulfall Abyss," Wyrm 3 replied.

"Where's that?" Han Li asked.

"It's one of the perilous places in the underworld, somewhere that even my father has never set foot in. She says that the Great Dao that she's searching for is there, and I warned her about how dangerous a place it is, but she still insisted on going, nevertheless," Wyrm 3 replied.

"How long has it been since she went there?" Han Li asked.

"She set off over a century ago, and she's still yet to return," Wyrm 3 replied.

Han Li closed his eyes upon hearing this, and a speck of white light emerged over his glabella momentarily, following which he reopened his eyes.

"Is she alright?" Violet Spirit asked.

"I don't know. Our spiritual connection has been severed," Han Li replied.

"It's said that the Soulfall Abyss is a place in which all spiritual connections are rendered null. Even if you were standing in the abyss right next to her, you wouldn't be able to sense her," Wyrm 3 said.

"This is the path that Weeping Soul chose, so you should trust her," Violet Spirit said as she latched onto Han Li's hand, and he could only give a resigned nod.

Weeping Soul and Jin Tong each had their own paths to walk, just as he was on a path that would bring him in direct opposition to the Heavenly Court.

"I'll set off for the Dragon Abyss Immortal Region tomorrow. Make sure to have all of the information on Feng Qingshui ready by then," Han Li said to Wyrm 3.

......

That night.

Han Li and Violet Spirit were laying together on the rooftop of the stone palace on the island, gazing up at the stars.

Unfortunately, it was a rather cloudy night, so there were very few visible stars, and even the moon had been concealed.

Han Li turned his gaze to Violet Spirit, and her heartbreakingly beautiful features were gently illuminated by the hazy moonlight, further accentuating her allure.

Han Li had always harbored some guilt in his heart when it came to Violet Spirit. To him, she was every bit as important as Nangong Wan, but fate always seemed to have a way of keeping them apart.

With that in mind, he couldn't help but reach out to stroke her cheek as he began, "Violet Spirit, I..."

"There's no need to say anything," Violet Spirit interjected as she continued to look up at the sky. "I'm already content just staying with you in peace like this."

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Moments later, Violet Spirit grabbed onto one of Han Li's arms, then tucked it behind her own head as a pillow.

"Make sure to be careful and bring back Big Sister Wan'er safe and sound. I'll be here awaiting your return," Violet Spirit said.

Han Li looked down at Violet Spirit, who had buried her face against his chest, and it felt a little strange. In his mind, she had always been a very independent and strong-willed woman, and she very rarely displayed such a delicate side to herself.

"Do you want to know what I saw in my previous life through the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate?" Violet Spirit asked.

"What did you see?" Han Li asked.

He had always wanted to ask the question, but he didn't want to pressure Violet Spirit into sharing what she had seen.

"My previous life was very uneventful. I was a mortal woman in a mortal realm with no spirit roots, and I only lived for about a century. I waited for someone my entire life, from my prime years all the way until my grave, but that person never appeared," Violet Spirit recounted.

Her voice trailed off there as she looked straight into Han Li's eyes.

Entranced by her beauty, he gently wound an arm around her as he stroked her long and silky hair.

Violet Spirit continued to rest against his chest as she murmured, "That's why I already feel very fulfilled in this lifetime. I've managed to meet the person that I waited an entire lifetime for, so what regrets could I possibly have?"

Han Li looked into her eyes, and they were more beautiful than any of the stars in the sky, a breathtaking sight that he felt like he would never grow weary of.

Right at this moment, a gust of wind suddenly swept past, pushing a dark cloud along to conceal the final glimmer of moonlight.

The entire island was plunged into darkness, and shortly thereafter, it began to rain.

The rain of the underworld was different from that of the True Immortal Realm in that it was tinged with the ghostly qi that was pervasive in this environment.

It wasn't necessarily harmful, but it was certainly not pleasant, either.

Han Li didn't want this rare moment of peace to be interrupted, so he raised a hand as he prepared to sweep the dark clouds away, only for Violet Spirit to latch onto his arm as she said in a barely audible voice, "Let's go back."

"You don't want to stay a little long..."

Han Li's voice abruptly cut off as he noticed that Violet Spirit had turned as red as a beetroot, and he instantly understood her intentions.

He reached one arm around her back while supporting the crook of her knees with the others, gently lifting her up from the rooftop before carrying her into the stone palace.

The storm over the island gradually picked up in ferocity as the night deepened.

......

It rained the entire night, fluctuating between a light sprinkle and a heavy downpour.

A storm had also been raging in the palace the entire night, albeit one of a much more romantic nature.

The rain finally subsided in the morning, and Han Li awakened form his slumber to stare at the still sound asleep Violet Spirit.

His gaze lingered on her for a very long time, and he opened his mouth to say something on multiple occasions, but couldn't find the words.

In the end, he could only heave a faint sigh.

He got out of bed and put on a new fresh azure robe, then stood beside the bed in silence before finally turning to depart.

On the bed, Violet Spirit's eyelashes fluttered ever so slightly as a tear slid down a cheek, leaving behind a barely visible trail.

Upon reaching the door, Han Li took one final glance back at Violet Spirit, then left the room before gently closing the door behind him.

The flame of the candle in the room flickered momentarily before falling still again.

By the time he reached the entrance of the palace, Gan Jiuzhen was already waiting for him.

"Is everything ready?" Han Li asked.

"Where's Violet Spirit? Is she not going to see you off?" Gan Jiuzhen asked.

"We already said our farewells last night," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

Gan Jiuzhen didn't pry any further as she flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized token and a black jade slip, both of which she handed to Han Li.

"Why are you giving me this Bodhi Token?" Han Li asked.

"The Dragon Abyss Immortal Region is one of the thirty-six large immortal regions, and you can travel directly to the Middle Earth Immortal Region from there. With this Bodhi Token, you can say that you're traveling to the Middle Earth Immortal Region to take part in the Bodhi Banquet, and that'll be more effective than any passport," Gan Jiuzhen explained.

"That's very thoughtful of you," Han Li replied with a nod.

"This was all planned out by my father in advance. The jade slip lays out how you can travel to the Dragon Abyss Immortal Region, as well as some information on Feng Qingshui. I hope it can be of help to you," Gan Jiuzhen said.

She then paused momentarily before requesting in a solemn manner, "Please make sure to rescue my mother."

"I will," Han Li replied with a nod, then vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning, leaving Gan Jiuzhen to stare into space with a concerned look on her face.

Chapter 1327: Rescue Mission

Not long after Han Li's departure, the Reincarnation Palace Master suddenly appeared beside Gan Jiuzhen, but it was only a projection of him.

Gan Jiuzhen wasn't surprised to see this, and the Reincarnation Palace Master asked, "What do you think of him right now?"

"He feels completely unfathomable to me right now. I've only ever felt an aura so vast whenever I've been in your presence. How has he become so powerful in such a short time?" Gan Jiuzhen asked.

"He must've already severed his kind corpse soul, which means that his powers won't be inferior by much even compared with my own," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied with a smile.

"You're saying he's already progressed to the late-Great Encompassment Stage in such a short time? How?" Gan Jiuzhen exclaimed.

"I don't know how he did it, but one thing you have to remember is that the three paramount laws are referred to as such because they are closer to the essence of the Heavenly Dao than all other laws. Once a cultivator of one of the three paramount laws has severed their wicked and kind corpse souls, they will begin to be able to draw upon the power of the Heavenly Dao, granting them power on par with or even superior to that of the average Dao Ancestor.

“As a cultivator of reincarnation law powers, that's something that you can also look forward to upon reaching the late-Great Encompassment Stage," the Reincarnation Palace Master explained.

"Looks like I need to work even harder in my cultivation," Gan Jiuzhen said as she clenched her fists with a look of resolve in her eyes.

"Cultivating the paramount laws comes with significant benefits over cultivating other law powers, but it's a very difficult path to pursue, and it becomes even more difficult at the Great Encompassment Stage.

“There are countless cultivators across the True Immortal Realm who have attempted to walk such a path, but very few succeed. It's extremely important not to become overly ambitious and bite off more than you can chew," the Reincarnation Palace Master cautioned.

"Yes, Father," Gan Jiuzhen replied in a sheepish manner.

"If you wish to further your cultivation, I suggest you go and travel through some mortal realms for inspiration," the Reincarnation Palace Master said.

"How is that going to help?" Gan Jiuzhen asked in a puzzled manner.

"One of the keys to severing one's kind corpse soul is to understand the true meaning of kindness. Unfortunately, many cultivators lose sight of the meaning and importance of kindness over the course of their long cultivation journeys, and it's often the case that traveling through the mortal realms can allow one to reawaken the kindness in their heart," the Reincarnation Palace Master explained.

A thoughtful look appeared on Gan Jiuzhen's face upon hearing this.

"Those who live pure and kind lives are blessed with positive reciprocation when their souls enter the cycle of reincarnation. Even though I am able to control the six paths of reincarnation, it's not easy for me to alter the fates of those who've led lives of great kindness," the Reincarnation Palace Master continued.

"I see. Are you really going to do as Gu Huojin says, Father?" Gan Jiuzhen asked.

"A battle between our Reincarnation Palace and the Heavenly Court is inevitable. Your mother has already been captured, so you must remain safe no matter what, Jiuzhen," the Reincarnation Palace Master said in a gentle voice.

"I want to go and rescue Mother with you," Gan Jiuzhen said.

"No! You are to stay here and not stray a single step from this island!" the Reincarnation Palace Master said in a stern manner.

This was the first time that she had seen the Reincarnation Palace Master with such a stern expression, and she shuddered slightly in response, but her resolve didn't waver.

"Only when you're safe can I focus fully on dealing with the Heavenly Court. Leave your mother to me and Han Li," the Reincarnation Palace Master sighed as he patted Gan Jiuzhen on the shoulder, then vanished into thin air.

In the wake of his departure, Gan Jiuzhen remained rooted to the spot in a slight daze for quite some time before making her way deeper into the palace.

......

Dragon Abyss Immortal Region, Sky Sea Continent, Mist Dragon City.

The Dragon Abyss Immortal Region was extremely abundant with water sources. In fact, over 80% of the entire immortal region was ocean, and the land only consisted of sparse islands dotted throughout the sea.

The largest of those islands was the Sky Sea Continent, while Mist Dragon City was the largest city on the Sky Sea Continent.

Mist Dragon City was a coastal city that had been strategically constructed at the junction of several continents, and it was vastly renowned across the entire immortal region.

However, what was even more renowned was the Mist Dragon Sect that was situated outside Mist Dragon City.

The Mist Dragon Sect was a sect that had been around for countless years, and it had always been the number one sect in the entire immortal region.

The most renowned cultivator in the history of the sect by a huge margin was none other than Feng Qingshui, whose Dao Ancestor status only further cemented the sect's status as the dominant force in the immortal region.

At the center of Mist Dragon City was a plaza that was several dozen kilometers in size, and it was being patrolled by groups of blue-robed guards.

All of these guards were outer sect disciples of the Mist Dragon Sect, and they were responsible for maintaining order in Mist Dragon City.

Not only was Mist Dragon City under the jurisdiction of the Mist Dragon Sect, the same applies to the entire Sky Sea Continent, making it very difficult even for the Dragon Abyss Immortal Palace to have much sway over the continent.

At the center of the plaza was a huge, blue archway that reached all the way up to the clouds like a blue mountain.

The archway was riddled with countless array patterns that extended down to the plaza below, forming over a thousand teleportation arrays of different sizes, all of which were currently flashing.

These teleportation arrays were connected to many different immortal regions, and countless people came and went through them every single day.

Right at this moment, a group of six figures emerged from one of the teleportation arrays.

Five of them were chatting amicably with one another, while the sixth figure, an azure-robed man, appeared to have been a little distant from the group.

Among the five cultivators, a blue-robed young woman took a deep breath, then exclaimed, "So this is Mist Dragon City! It's so majestic, and the world's origin qi here is so abundant as well! It's way better than our Eternal Sky Immortal Region!"

"Of course. The Dragon Abyss Immortal Region is one of the thirty-six large immortal regions, so it's naturally much better than our Eternal Heaven Immortal Region. It looks like we made the right decision to pool together all of our funds to purchase a teleportation token to this place," a black-robed elderly man said.

As a Golden Immortal, he possessed the loftiest cultivation base of the five, and it was clear that he was the leader of the group.

"Of course, we also have to thank Fellow Daoist Han for chipping in. Otherwise, we would've still been short on funds," the elderly man said as he turned to the azure-robed man with a smile.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Huo. This was a mutually beneficial deal for all of us. The teleportation array is able to teleport six people at once, so I also saved a lot of Immortal Origin Stones by traveling with your group," the azure-robed man replied with a smile of his own.

The black-robed elderly man turned his gaze back to his companions as he said, "Right now, we barely have any Immortal Origin Stones between us, so there will undoubtedly be some hard times to come. Let's all work hard so that we can establish a foothold here as soon as possible."

His four companions gave a collective, affirmative response.

"Fellow Daoist Han, you're also a vagrant cultivator, so how about you join us as well? There's always more strength in numbers," the black-robed elderly man offered.

"I have some private matters to attend to, so I'm afraid this is where we'll have to part ways. Good luck with your cultivation, fellow daoists," the azure-robed man said as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

The black-robed elderly man was rather disappointed to hear this, but he didn't say anything further as he departed with his four companions.

Meanwhile, the azure-robed man remained on the plaza as he began to inspect his surroundings.

"Oi, you over there! Don't loiter on the teleportation plaza! This isn't your backyard!" a nearby guard yelled, but the azure-robed man simply ignored him.

A furious look instantly appeared on the guard's face upon seeing this, and he was just about to detain the azure-robed man to administer a stern punishment when he suddenly stopped cold in his tracks.

Even though the azure-robed man was merely standing still on the spot, the guard's soul had suddenly begun to tremble in his presence, leading him to reflexively stop in his tracks.

The azure-robed man was none other than Han Li, and at this moment, he was scouring the surrounding area with his spiritual sense.

The Dragon Abyss Immortal Region was far more massive than the Crane Ridge Immortal Region, so his spiritual sense was only able to encompass a small section of it.

However, the entire Sky Sea Continent had still fallen within his spiritual sensory range, as was the entirety of the Mist Dragon Sect.

The only problem was that he wasn't able to detect the auras of either Nangong Wan or Feng Qingshui.

Even though Feng Qingshui was a Dao Ancestor, surely there was no way that he should've been able to remain hidden from his spiritual sense, given that he had now mastered all seven levels of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Could it be that I've been fed false information?

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li turned to the nearby guard, and a layer of murky light appeared in his eyes.

The guard's eyes instantly became glazed over, and countless memories began flashing through his pupils in rapid succession, laying out his entire life for Han Li to see.

Given Han Li's current mastery over the Spirit Refinement Technique, he was now able to examine a High Zenith cultivator's memories with ease, as opposed to having to use intrusive soul search techniques.

Through the guard's memories, Han Li was able to glean some information about Mist Dragon Sect, and with that, he instantly vanished from the spot.

The dazed look in the guard's eyes instantly faded away, and he shuddered as he snapped back to his senses.

"What the hell just happened?" the guard murmured to himself, and he felt as if there were a small gap in his memory.

He looked around momentarily in a perplexed manner, then scratched his own head as he returned to his patrol duties.

Chapter 1328: Abduction

All of a sudden, Han Li appeared outside a peaceful palace in the Mist Dragon Sect without any warning.

There were two guards clad in suits of blue armor stationed on either side of the palace entrance, and both of them were at the late-High Zenith Stage.

Both of them were naturally very alarmed by Han Li's abrupt arrival, but before they had a chance to do anything, a faint glimmer of light flashed through Han Li's eyes, and they were instantly rooted to the spot in a statuesque manner.

Han Li turned his gaze to the palace gates, which were tightly shut, with a layer of hazy, blue light flashing over their surface, clearly indicating the presence of some formidable restriction.

After examining the palace gates briefly, Han Li turned his gaze to the distance as he swept a sleeve through the air, and seventy-two tiny arcs of lightning sprang out of his sleeve before vanishing into the nearby space.

In the next instant, seventy-two golden lightning swords emerged around the entire Sky Sea continent to form an enormous encirclement.

Arcs of golden lightning sprang out of the lightning swords, then intertwined with one another to form a dome-shaped lightning net that encompassed the entire continent.

However, the lightning net was only visible for an instant before vanishing into thin air, immediately following which a blanket of dark clouds suddenly began to gather over the continent.

The cultivators all over the continent quickly noticed what was happening in the sky, but they didn't think much of it. Given the climate and water-rich environment of the Dragon Abyss Immortal Region, storms were a very common sight.

After doing all of that, Han Li flew into the palace gates as a streak of golden light, and the restrictions on the gates instantly began glowing radiantly as it attempted to keep him at bay.

However, the streak of golden light was able to pass through the restrictions and the gates without pause, and inside the palace was a thin elderly man seated on a cushion with his legs crossed.

There was a projection of a blue flower that was around ten feet in size hovering above the elderly man's head, and the petals of the flower were drifting through the palace while giving off a unique fragrance.

All of a sudden, the elderly man's eyes sprang open, yet before he even had a chance to stand up, Han Li had already appeared in the palace.

The elderly man reacted extremely quickly, and a burst of radiant, blue light erupted out of his body alongside a peak-Great Encompassment Stage aura.

A loud roar rang out from within his body, immediately following which a projection of a blue dragon that was ten thousand feet in size appeared around him.

As soon as the dragon projection appeared, the elderly man's wizened body was instantly rejuvenated. His white hair turned an exuberant black, his skin became as fair as jade, and it was as if he had aged fifty years in reverse, while his aura had also become as violent and tumultuous as that of a combative dragon.

The elderly man threw a punch at Han Li, and the blue dragon projection around him sprang forward with his fist.

Countless cracks appeared throughout the space in the palace, but it didn't completely explode. It resembled a shattered piece of porcelain, but it was somehow able to hold itself together.

At the same time, all of the restrictions throughout the Mist Dragon Sect sprang into action, and the entire sect was basked in a sea of radiant, blue light.

All of the world's origin qi within a radius of millions of kilometers converged from all directions before surging into the sea of blue light, following which it was then funneled into the palace.

The walls of the palace began radiating dazzling, blue light, which converged toward Han Li like a turbulent wave, and it was more formidable an attack than the punch thrown by the elderly man.

All of a sudden, everything in the palace had become incredibly heavy, as if it had suddenly been teleported to the seabed, millions of kilometers beneath the surface.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, but Han Li remained unfazed as he casually thrust a fist forward, and a giant, golden fist projection took shape before hurtling directly toward the elderly man.

The fist projection appeared to have been completely unremarkable, and it wasn't even giving off any energy fluctuations, yet it was able to tear through the oncoming dragon projection and waves of blue light with ease.

A stunned look appeared on the elderly man's face upon seeing this, and he immediately turned to flee, only for the golden fist projection to instantly appear above him before unfurling into a palm and swooping down upon him.

The elderly man let loose a desperate roar as he thrust both palms up toward the heavens.

A resounding boom rang out as the entire palace trembled violently, and half of the elderly man's body had been smashed into the ground. He had reverted back to his elderly appearance, and blood was gushing out of his mouth in a frenzy.

A finger appeared before him without any warning, then gently pressed itself against his forehead, and several translucent chains shot out of the fingertip before vanishing into his glabella.

The elderly man instantly stiffened as his eyes glazed over, and he was hoisted out of the ground by Han Li, following which both of them vanished from the spot.

The waves of blue light in the palace slowly dissipated, while the cracked space gradually healed.

Right at this moment, three streaks of light landed outside the palace, containing a tall middle-aged man, a blue-robed young woman, and a child that was only around three feet tall.

The middle-aged man and the blue-robed woman were both at the mid-Great Encompassment Stage, while the child was a late-Great Encompassment cultivator.

The two armorclad guards stationed outside the palace were laying on the ground in an unconscious state, and that was certainly not an encouraging sight for the three figures.

The three of them exchanged a glance with one another, following which the middle-aged man called out, "What's going on in there, Sect Leader?"

There was no response.

"Something must've happened. Let's go in," the blue-robed woman said, and the three of them promptly undid the restrictions on the palace gates before stepping inside.

The interior of the palace was in a state of chaotic disarray, and all that remained of the sect leader was a puddle of blood on the ground.

"It looks like our sect leader may have been abducted," the middle-aged man remarked with a grim expression, one that was mirrored on the faces of his two companions.

"But Sect Leader Yang Shan is a peak-Great Encompassment cultivator, who could've possibly managed to abduct him in such a short time? Unless..."

The blue-robed woman's voice trailed off into a grim silence as a harrowing possibility dawned upon her.

"It had to have been a Dao Ancestor," the child said, and even though his voice was very tender and childlike, it somehow sounded as if it belonged to someone with a much older appearance.

"Surely not! Why would a Dao Ancestor stoop to abducting a Great Encompassment cultivator?" the middle-aged man exclaimed.

"Right now, the True Immortal Realm is in a very chaotic state, and there are many things happening that are out of the ordinary," the child mused.

"What should we do, Elder Ji?" the middle-aged man asked as he turned to the child, as did the blue-robed woman.

"Seeing as this matter most likely concerns a Dao Ancestor, it's no longer something that we can take care of, so we'll have to notify our patriarch," the child replied.

The middle-aged man and the blue-robed woman exchanged a glance with one another before nodding in agreement.

......

Somewhere out in the boundless expanse of space was a ball of golden light that was around an acre in size, resembling a giant egg.

However, the space within the ball of golden light was far larger than an acre in area, spanning dozens of kilometers in size, and it was complete with mountains, valleys, and forests.

Sect Leader Yang Shan had been set down onto the ground, and Han Li had pressed a palm down onto his head, attempting to search his soul.

However, to his surprise and dismay, Sect Leader Yang Shan seemed to have cultivated some type of secret technique that combined all of his memories to form a strange, impermeable seal.

This seal was closely connected to his soul, and it was extremely unstable, so if he were to try and search his soul by force, then his soul would instantly self-detonate.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li withdrew his palm before pressing several key points on Sect Leader Yang Shan's body to seal away his cultivation base, then tapped a finger against his glabella to withdraw the spiritual sense chains within.

His eyes quickly came into focus, and as his gaze fell upon Han Li, he asked, "May I ask which Dao Ancestor you are, Senior? And why have you abducted me?"

"There's no need to be so apprehensive, Sect Leader Yang Shan. I've only brought you here because I want to ask you some questions, and you'll be free to leave once my questions have been answered," Han Li said with a reassuring smile.

Sect Leader Yang Shan raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, then closed his eyes in a stoic manner.

"Does this mean you're refusing to cooperate?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. I don't know who you are, but you're not getting any information about our patriarch from me! If you wish to kill me, then do as you please!" Sect Leader Yang Shan declared.

"I appreciate loyal people like you, but my questions are very important and must be answered, so I'm afraid that I'll have to subject you to a bit of suffering," Han Li said, and he wasn't irked at all by Sect Leader Yang Shan's refusal to cooperate.

"If you want to search my soul, then go ahead. Even if you're a Dao Ancestor, you won't be able to bypass the Nine Dragon Seal that our patriarch planted in my soul," Sect Leader Yang Shan sneered.

"So that seal was personally placed upon you by Feng Qingshui. It would indeed be able to prevent the majority of Dao Ancestors from searching your soul, but unfortunately for you, that doesn't apply to me," Han Li said with a faint smile.

Chapter 1329: Confrontation

A derisive sneer appeared on Sect Leader Yang Shan's face upon hearing this, and it was clear that he was of the opinion that Han Li was merely bluffing.

"This Nine Dragon Seal is closely connected to your soul, and it contains nine different types of power. As soon as it's infiltrated by any external power, it'll immediately detonate. How troublesome," Han Li mused with a faint smile.

Sect Leader Yang Shan closed his eyes once again as a cold sneer appeared on his face.

"However, this Nine Dragon Seal is supported by the power of your soul, so if your soul is weakened, then the seal will also become weaker. If your soul is reduced to the Golden Immortal Stage, then even if this seal is to explode, I'll be able to easily suppress the explosion," Han Li continued.

Sect Leader Yang Shan's eyes instantly sprang open upon hearing this, and a look of unease appeared on his face.

Before he had a chance to do anything, Han Li raised a hand before spreading his fingers apart,and five bursts of golden light shot out of his fingertips.

One was as explosive as fire, one was as gentle as water, one was as dense as earth, one was as exuberate as wood, and the final one was as sharp as metal.

Each burst of golden light was giving off a completely different type of time law powers, and

The five bursts of golden light descended around Sect Leader Yang Shan, then intertwined with one another to form a golden light barrier.

The five bursts of time law powers came together in a seamless manner, and the nearby spirit domain began to flash with golden light.

The flow of time around Sect Leader Yang Shan was undergoing a drastic change, and he let loose a pained cry as his aura began to rapidly decline.

In the blink of an eye, he had been reduced from the peak-Great Encompassment Stage to the Golden Immortal Stage, and this was no illusion. His law powers, number of immortal acupoints and soul power had all dropped to the Golden Immortal Stage, which meant that he would have to begin cultivating anew from the Golden Immortal Stage if he wanted to return to his former cultivation base.

"What did you do to me?" Sect Leader Yang Shan yelled frantically as he hurriedly attempted to detonate his own soul, but Han Li was able to easily subdue him.

At his current cultivation base, it had become far easier for Han Li to channel his Five Elemental Illusory World ability, and now that Sect Leader Yang Shan's soul power had fallen to the Golden Immortal Stage, the Nine Dragon Seal was powerless to stop Han Li from searching his soul.

With the Nine Dragon Seal easily bypassed, Sect Leader Yang Shan's memories were all laid bare to Han Li.

"So he's in the Mist Dragon Secret Area. You should've just told me that and spared yourself all this suffering," Han Li sneered as he withdrew his hand, and Sect Leader Yang Shan immediately fell unconscious.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of golden light, which swept over Sect Leader Yang Shan, and he instantly vanished from the spot, following which Han Li also departed.

......

Inside a valley deep within the Mist Dragon Sect, three streaks of light descended from the heavens, and they were none other than the three Great Encompassment cultivators from before.

At the end of the valley was an ordinary-looking stone door, and the three of them fell to their knees outside, following which Elder Ji pulled out a stick of incense before lighting it.

A plume of blue smoke came wafting out of the lit stick of incense, then slowly seeped through the stone door.

Beyond the stone door was a vast, bottomless sea, hanging over which was a radiant, blue sun.

All of a sudden, a layer of blue mist rose up over the surface of the sea, as if the water were being evaporated by the sunlight.

Occasionally, a huge wave would sweep over the surface, revealing a giant tail or a massive claw.

On the seabed was a massive cave that was filled with countless strange rocks, forming a vast stone forest.

Laying within the stone forest were countless massive skeletons ranging from thousands of feet to over a hundred thousand feet in size, and even though they were only sets of remains, they were still giving off an incredibly arrogant aura, as if they were looking down on all of the living beings under the heavens.

These were all dragon skeletons, so it seemed that this place was a tomb for dragons.

Seated on a large, blue rock in the cave was none other than Feng Qingshui, and he was staring off into space, seemingly contemplating something.

Some time later, he reached out with one hand to make a grabbing motion, and a vortex of blue mist quickly took shape in front of him.

"What's brought all three of you here to see me at once?" Feng Qingshui asked.

The voice of Elder Ji rang out from within the blue vortex, explaining, "Sorry to interrupt your seclusion, esteemed patriarch, but Sect Leader Yang Shan seems to have been abducted by someone we strongly suspect to be a Dao Ancestor."

"Oh? How did it happen? Give me more details," Feng Qingshui instructed.

Elder Ji duly obliged, giving Feng Qingshui a detailed recount of events.

"If they were able to abduct Yang Shan in such a short time even after he activated the Four Seas Crashing Waves Array, then they most likely were indeed a Dao Ancestor," Feng Qingshui mused.

What was even more concerning to him was that he had completely failed to detect anything.

While it was true that he was in the Mist Dragon Secret Area, and his mind had been on other things just now, surely he should've still been able to sense the presence of a hostile Dao Ancestor in his sect.

After a brief silence, Feng Qingshui said, "Alright, I'll look into the matter..."

Before he had a chance to finish, a booming voice suddenly rang out to cut him off.

"There's no need to look into anything, I have your sect leader right here!"

At the same time, the entire secret area suddenly began to tremble violently, and a thick pillar of golden light descended from the heavens to pulverize the vortex of blue mist in front of Feng Qingshui, thereby cutting off communication between him and the three elders outside.

An alarmed look appeared on Feng Qingshui's face as he sprang back in retreat, and at the same time, plumes of white mist surged out of his body, instantly giving him an indistinct and illusory appearance.

The pillar of golden light faded to reveal none other than Han Li, and Feng Qingshui was struck by a sense of familiarity at the sight of the intruder.

At his cultivation base, seeing through disguises was a simple feat, and he could tell that the intruder was not concealing his true appearance.

Han Li paid no heed to Feng Qingshui as he released his spiritual sense to encompass the entirety of the Mist Dragon Sect Area.

Swimming within the boundless sea in the secret area were countless dragons of extremely pure bloodlines, and there were close to twenty Great Encompassment Stage dragons among them, while the cave was littered with countless dragon skeletons.

However, Han Li had no interest in these dragons as he was searching for something else, and judging from the look that had appeared on his face, his search had clearly proved to be a fruitless one.

"It's you!" Feng Qingshui suddenly exclaimed as a look of recognition appeared in his eyes.

He had finally recalled that Han Li had been one of the intruders that had snuck into Asura City while he had been in the Gray Realm, attempting to recruit Yin Chengquan as an ally.

However, he recalled that at the time, Han Li had only been at the peak-Golden Immortal Stage, so the fact that he had managed to reach the peak-Great Encompassment Stage in such a short time since then was nothing short of astonishing.

Could it be that he concealed his true power back then? That's a very strong possibility. I recall he and a devilish companion of his had vanished under very mysterious circumstances back then. I had thought at the time that they had been saved by some powerful ally of theirs, but perhaps it was him all along, Feng Qingshui thought to himself.

"Were you the one who captured Wan'er?" Han Li asked as he cast a cold gaze toward Feng Qingshui.

"I don't know who you're referring to. Why have you captured the leader of my sect?" Feng Qingshui countered.

"Don't try to play dumb with me," Han Li sneered as he conjured up a ball of golden light, contained within which was the visage of Nangong Wan.

A faint smile appeared on Feng Qingshui's face, but he offered no response.

"Hand her over right now and I'll release your sect leader and leave. Otherwise, I'm going to have to get a little rough with you," Han Li harrumphed coldly.

"I can't even recall how many years it's been since someone has dared to speak to me like this. I can tell you that I was indeed the one who captured that woman, but it was under the orders of the Heavenly Court, and she has already been sent there," Feng Qingshui declared.

Han Li was already mentally prepared for this outcome, but his face still paled slightly upon hearing this.

"Why does the Heavenly Court want to capture her?" Han Li asked in a cold voice.

"I don't know, I was only following orders, and the Heavenly Court didn't feel the need to tell me their reasons," Feng Qingshui replied.

Chapter 1330: Battle of the Great Daos

"In that case, it's time for you to pay for what you've done!" Han Li declared in a cold voice as his robes began flapping audibly around him, despite the lack of wind.

A burst of dazzling, golden light erupted out of his body alongside tremendous time law powers, and an astonished look appeared on Feng Qingshui's face as he exclaimed, "You're a cultivator of time law powers!"

At the same time, he sprang back in retreat while sweeping both sleeves through the air, and countless strands of blue light appeared out of thin air before sweeping toward Han Li like a blue sea.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face as he transformed into a streak of golden light that raced through the air at an incredible speed, leaving a trail of afterimages in its wake.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li appeared behind Feng Qingshui without any warning, and all of the strands of blue light in the air had already been severed, while Feng Qingshui's body had been split into two from head to toe by a line that ran down the center.

However, even as his body split into two, not a single drop of blood appeared, and all of a sudden, the two halves of his body exploded into two clouds of blue mist that darted away into the distance before fusing back together to reform him.

In the wake of the ordeal that he had just suffered, he was looking a little pale, but he quickly recovered, and he exclaimed, "Those time law powers... There's no mistaking it, you must be a disciple of the True Mantra Sect!"

"You're a smart man, but people who are too smart tend to not live very long," Han Li harrumphed coldly as his spirit domain erupted out of his body.

Within the spirit domain, Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis emerged before transforming into a bright, golden moon that began rapidly revolving while releasing countless golden ripples.

As soon as these golden ripples swept over Feng Qingshui's body, he was instantly immobilized, resembling a snapshot in time.

Han Li pounced on this opportunity to throw an almighty punch, and five bursts of time law powers erupted out of his fist before combining as one.

However, instead of forming his Five Elemental Illusory World, the five bursts of time law powers came together to form a golden fist that struck Feng Qingshui with the force of a hurtling asteroid.

The five bursts of time law powers within the golden fist clashed violently against one another, but didn't completely explode, and they were giving off terrifying power that seemed capable of destroying anything in its path.

This was an ability that Han Li had created, and he had named it "Great Five Elemental Annihilation Fist".

A loud thump rang out as Feng Qingshui's body exploded into countless scraps of blood and flesh, and on top of that, a giant, golden sun that was millions of kilometers in diameter appeared around him, with bursts of fearsome time law powers raging within it.

All space, matter, and even time within the golden sun was reduced to nothingness, and the scraps of Feng Qingshui's body were naturally no exception.

At the same time, astonishingly destructive shockwaves swept through the air in all directions, and huge cracks appeared all over the Mist Dragon Secret Area before it collapsed violently.

The space above the Mist Dragon Sect was pulverized as a boundless sea appeared out of thin air, encompassing the entire sect and close to half of the Sky Sea Continent.

The bright, blue sun in the secret area had also appeared, and it continued to give off rays of blue radiance, while all of the dragons in the sea were trembling and cowering in fear.

These dragons were extremely proud and looked down on all other living beings, but they still harbored nothing but awe and veneration toward Dao Ancestors.

The entire continent was about to be inundated by the vast sea crashing down from above, and all of the disciples of the Mist Dragon Sect erupted into a blind panic.

Elder Ji and his two companions were also looking up at the sky with stunned expressions, and the three of them hurriedly flew up into the air before collectively conjuring up a blue light barrier to oppose the falling seawater.

Meanwhile, all of the residents of the Sky Sea Continent could only pray that they would somehow survive this cataclysmic disaster.

Han Li had also appeared in the sky above the Mist Dragon Sect, and his brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the terrible fate that was about to befall the continent down below.

He raised a hand to the heavens, and the entire Dragon Abyss Immortal Region was instantly filled by boundless blue light, while all of the seawater and water-attribute spiritual qi in the air fell completely still.

The vast sea that had gushed out of the Mist Dragon Secret Area was also suspended in mid-air as a gargantuan ball of water, which then raced toward the sea at Han Li's behest.

The three Great Encompassment Stage Mist Dragon Sect elders were unable to get away in time before the unfathomably massive ball of water crashed into them, and blood came gushing out of their mouths as they were swept away into the distance.

The ball of water flew out of the Sky Sea Continent in the blink of an eye, where it was then released into the sea by Han Li, and with that, the crisis had been averted.

The ball of water crashed down into the sea below with an almighty splash, and countless, enormous waves were sent sweeping over the surface of the sea in all directions.

All of the dragons in the ball of water hurriedly fled in all directions, forced to swallow their pride as they frantically swam for their lives.

All the while, Han Li remained hovering high up in the sky with a contemplative look on his face.

While he was extremely confident in his own powers, it didn't make sense for a Dao Ancestor like Feng Qingshui to have met his demise so easily.

As the long-established Water Dao Ancestor, he stood at the very pinnacle of the entire True Immortal Realm, yet the Feng Qingshui that had been slain just now really had been a body of flesh and blood, rather than any illusion or avatar.

Unwilling to take any chances, Han Li released his unfathomable spiritual sense, and right at this moment, a cacophony of rumbling thunderclaps rang out as a section of the golden lightning net that had previously vanished into thin air around the Sky Sea Continent reappeared.

Han Li immediately turned to that direction, then vanished from the spot amid a flash of lightning.

At the same time, countless balls of golden lightning and lighting sword projections erupted out of the lighting net, and every single one of them was imbued with unfathomable lightning law powers.

A deafening boom rang out as all of the space within a radius of hundreds of thousand of kilometers was completely annihilated, and Feng Qingshui was sent flying out of thin air in an unsteady manner.

At the moment, his complexion was very pale, and his aura had also receded significantly.

In the next instant, Han Li appeared before him as he harrumphed coldly, "So you really did use an avatar. You did manage to fool me, but the entire continent has already been surrounded, so you're not going anywhere today!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, an enormous, golden spirit domain erupted out of his body, and this one was far more powerful than the one that he had conjured up earlier, warping all of the space encompassed within it.

Han Li made a hand seal, and a series of giant, golden gates appeared above the spirit domain, leading to various other immortal regions and even many lower realms.

Beyond the largest of the golden gates was a boundless space that was filled with golden light, and it contained the power of the laws of time within the Heavenly Dao.

All of the golden gates lit up at his behest, and bursts of time law powers funneled their way through them before fusing into the surrounding time spirit domain.

The time in those immortal regions and lower realms was instantly thrown into a state of disarray, while the world's origin qi within them also began churning violently in a doomsday-like scene.

All of the time law powers within the Dragon Abyss Immortal Region were also converging toward the golden spirit domain, altering the complexion of the entire immortal region drastically.

The gate that was connected to the Heavenly Dao also lit up as a thick pillar of golden light descended from it before fusing into the spirit domain, and it instantly swelled to several times its original size, while the golden light radiating from it became so bright that it completely outshone the light of the sun.

A stunned look appeared on Feng Qingshui's face upon seeing this, and he let loose a loud roar as a blue spirit domain erupted out his body as well.

The spirit domain was filled with blue mist that refracted the light in countless different angles, presenting a captivating yet confounding sight to behold.

A series of spatial gates also appeared within the blue spirit domain as it attempted to draw upon power from other immortal regions and realms, but right at this moment, a gargantuan, golden lightning net emerged over the Sky Sea Continent.

All of the space on the other side of the lightning net seemed to have been cut off, and as a result, the spatial gates within Feng Qingshui's water spirit domain were filled entirely with golden lightning.

An alarmed look appeared on Feng Qingshui's face upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to do anything, a burst of almighty power came crashing down upon him from Han Li's time spirit domain.

The constrictive force was so potent that Feng Qingshui was almost completely immobilized, and he let loose a loud roar as he threw a punch with great difficulty.

His blue spirit domain began to rumble as it drew upon some power from the sea down below to help it oppose Han Li's time spirit domain.

In the next instant, the two spirit domains clashed with an almighty boom, and this was the most formidable clash that had taken place between the two of them thus far.

This was not just a clash between laws, but also a battle between Great Daos!

However, as one of the three paramount laws, the laws of time were a fundamental part of the Heavenly Dao, one that the laws of water couldn't hope to oppose.

The entire Dragon Abyss Immortal Region had begun trembling violently, and the sky and the sea were collapsing in a cataclysmic fashion.

Several enormous spatial rifts had appeared in the center of the immortal region, and they were rapidly widening and elongating, threatening to tear the entire immortal region into pieces.

The seawater in the Dragon Abyss Immortal Region gushed into the spatial rifts, and some of the smaller fragments of the immortal region on the edges of the spatial rifts were sucked in before plummeting toward the lower realms.

Thankfully, the vast majority of the immortal region was comprised of ocean, so even in the face of such a calamitous disaster, there weren't too many casualties.

Before long, a series of massive cracks appeared over the surface of the blue spirit domain, and it was shattered into pieces by the might of Han Li's time spirit domain.

Chapter 1331: Intervention

Feng Qingshui shuddered violently, and his aura was significantly weakened with the destruction of his spirit domain.

However, he clearly wasn't going to simply resign himself to his fate, and his shattered spirit domain was still resisting against Han Li's time spirit domain, but as time passed, it was clear that the gold was overwhelming the blue.

Finally, as the last bits of blue were devoured, Feng Qingshui threw up a large mouthful of blood as he plummeted out of the sky like a meteorite.

Meanwhile, Han Li was also looking a little pale. After all, maintaining a spirit domain of this caliber for such a long time as a peak-Great Encompassment cultivator was quite a strenuous task.

However, this was a battle that he had to win, and he couldn't afford to ease up the pressure even for a moment.

As Feng Qingshui came falling out of the sky, he threw an almighty punch in his direction, and five bursts of bright, golden light shot out of his spirit domain, then intertwined to form another Great Five Elemental Annihilation Fist.

The golden fist raced toward Feng Qingshui with unmatched speed and power, and in response, Feng Qingshui hurriedly expelled a mouthful of blood essence, before casting a rapid string of incantation seals into it.

A streak of radiant, blue light shot out from within, and it was none other than the blue sun from the Mist Dragon Secret Area, currently in the form of a blue halberd that was around a thousand feet in size.

The halberd was giving off incredibly fearsome law powers that were around twice as formidable as Feng Qingshui's own law powers, and it was clear that this was his trump card.

That's a second tier immortal treasure!

The blue halberd hurtled through the air as a streak of dazzling, blue light at Feng Qingshui's behest, and it pierced its way into the giant, golden fist, shattering it into countless specks of golden light.

The blue halberd sped through the specks of golden light, leaving a blue trail in its wake as it hurtled directly toward Han Li with astonishing speed.

"You were a fool to think that a mere Great Encompassment cultivator like yourself could challenge a Dao Ancestor!" Feng Qingshui declared as a hint of insanity flashed through his eyes.

Han Li remained completely unfazed by the oncoming blue halberd, and a sense of foreboding welled up in Feng Qingshui's heart at the sight of his composed reaction.

Right as the halberd was no more than a thousand feet away from Han Li, his time spirit domain abruptly shuddered, and the blue halberd was stopped cold in its tracks.

Immediately thereafter, a layer of golden light appeared over its surface, and it exploded into countless pieces right before Feng Qingshui's astonished eyes.

A horrified look appeared on his face upon seeing this, and he frantically pulled out a blue tablet before crushing it in his hand.

At the same time, he drew up all of his remaining power, and a vast expanse of misty, blue light began to proliferate outward from his body.

In the blink of an eye, he had conjured up hundreds of identical avatars to himself, all of which fled in different directions at an incredible speed.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and countless arcs of golden lightning erupted out of the lightning net around the Sky Sea Continent at his behest.

The arcs of lightning converged toward the fleeing avatars from all directions at an even more astonishing speed, and in the blink of an eye, all of the avatars were destroyed, leaving only Feng Qingshui left.

Countless arcs of golden lightning had converged around him as well to form a lightning cocoon, and he was completely immobilized as his entire body spasmed uncontrollably.

"Let this serve as a warning to Gu Huojin. If he doesn't release my dao partner, the Heavenly Court will meet the same fate that will befall you now!" Han Li declared as he unleashed yet another Great Five Elemental Annihilation Fist, this one even more massive than the previous two, and it sped toward Feng Qingshui with unfathomable destructive might.

Right at this moment, the entire Dragon Abyss Immortal Region suddenly began to tremble violently, and a burst of tremendous power came crashing down upon the golden lightning net from the outside.

This burst of power was ten times more formidable than what Feng Qingshui was able to muster, and the lightning net immediately began to twist and warp, following a huge gash was torn into its surface.

At the same time, a turbulent vortex appeared on the surface of the sea below Feng Qingshui, and he was sucked into it along with the lightning cocoon around him.

As a result, Han Li's Great Five Elemental Annihilation Fist struck nothing but thin air, while Feng Qingshui was engulfed into the sea.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as a golden sun that was millions of kilometers in size emerged, decimating everything within it, but Han Li paid no heed to it as he cast a grim gaze out of the lightning net.

All of a sudden, the burst of fearsome power had vanished, as if it had gone into hiding, and Feng Qingshui's aura was also nowhere to be detected.

Han Li harrumphed coldly as he made a rapid string of hand seals, and the golden lightning net instantly reverted back into seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that raced away in different directions.

As a set of third tier immortal treasures, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were extraordinarily fast, and they instantly flew to all corners of the immortal region, following which arcs of golden lightning began to fan out from them, as if they were searching for something.

In the next instant, Han Li's eyes suddenly lit up as he vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning, then instantly reappeared beside an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword that was hovering above a sea on the edge of the Dragon Abyss Immortal Region.

This was one of the new abilities attained by his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords upon their evolution into third tier immortal treasures. Regardless of where they were, Han Li would be able to instantly teleport to whichever Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword that he pleased through their spiritual connection.

From there, he released his spiritual sense, and at the same time, his time spirit domain erupted out of his body before pouncing down on the sea below like a giant, golden beast.

The seawater down below instantly evaporated, revealing Feng Qingshui enveloped in a ball of blue light on the seabed.

Caught within Han Li's spirit domain, the ball of blue light had been stopped cold in its tracks.

Right at this moment, the same burst of fearsome power from before reappeared, and an incredibly pure, blue spirit domain flew out of the nearby sea to encompass Feng Qingshui.

The spirit domain was filled with all types of water-based entities, such as rivers, clouds, glaciers, and ripples, and it was as if were the origin of all water under the heavens.

The spirit domain clashed violently with Han Li's time spirit domain, and Han Li felt as if his spirit domain had crashed into a soft, yet extremely resilient wall.

A deep indentation had appeared on the blue spirit domain, but it refused to shatter.

It was as if all of the unfathomable power in Han Li's time spirit domain had plunged into a bottomless sea, and it was completely nullified.

However, the blue spirit domain was clearly struggling immensely as well, and it looked as if it were on the verge of being overwhelmed.

"Who's there?" Han Li yelled as he conjured up the golden spatial gates within his time spirit domain once again, preparing to draw upon the power of other realms and immortal regions to crush the opposing spirit domain.

This spirit domain was far more powerful than Feng Qingshui's, but Han Li was confident that he would be able to crush it.

Right at this moment, a voice rang out from within the blue spirit domain.

"Hold on a second, Fellow Daoist Han, I am not your enemy. I've come here to return Fellow Daoist Nangong Wan to you!"

As soon as the voice trailed off, a ball of blue light shot out from within the blue spirit domain, and it contained none other than Nangong Wan.

"Wan'er!"

Han Li yelled in an ecstatic manner as he hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of golden light to catch her.

Through the power of his spirit domain, Han Li was able to verify that this was truly Nangong Wan and not some trick.

However, she was currently in an unconscious state, and it seemed as if her soul had been sealed away.

Han Li rested a fingertip against her glabella, injecting a burst of soul power into her consciousness.

In doing so, he discovered that the seal in her consciousness was a very unremarkable one that he could break with ease, but he didn't dare to do so with these two formidable adversaries before him.

With another sweep of his sleeve, he sent Nangong Wan into the Flower Branch domain, then withdrew his spirit domain until it had shrunk down to only several dozen kilometers in size, but didn't withdraw it entirely.

The opposing, blue spirit domain also shrank down significantly before retreating to a safe distance away, and Han Li made no effort to pursue it.

"You must be Han Li, right? I can see that you've fully harnessed the inheritance of the True Mantra Sect. Congratulations!"

A delicate young woman with a head of blue hair emerged from the blue spirit domain.

She had a pair of sparkling eyes, a delicate nose, a pair of small, cherry lips, and her blue hair was arranged into many little braids, giving her the appearance of a mischievous young girl.

She was wearing a blue dress that left her arms and calves exposed, and there were no shoes on her feet. There was an intricate, blue band around each of her ankles and wrists, hanging from which were some tiny bells that produced a tinkling chime with her movements.

However, her most eye-catching trait was the pair of delicate dragon horns on her forehead, as well as the faint, true spirit bloodline aura swirling around her.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Even though he was on the Heavenly Court's wanted list, his cultivation base had been too lowly to attract the attention of the Dao Ancestors, and that was why Feng Qingshui had failed to recognize him.

However, this woman, who was clearly a more powerful Dao Ancestor than Feng Qingshui, was somehow aware of exactly who he was.

Chapter 1332: All-Encompassing Tribulation

"Who are you?" Han Li asked in a wary manner.

At the same time, he made a beckoning motion, and all of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords scattered throughout the Dragon Abyss Immortal Region immediately returned to him before flying up his sleeve.

"My name is Chen Ruyan, and I am the Essential Water Dao Ancestor. You can call me Ruyan," the young woman replied with a wide grin.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon hearing this.

Chen Ruyan's lips puckered slightly as she put on a pitiable display and continued, "I only captured your dao partner under the orders of the Heavenly Court, and I've already returned her to you, so surely there's no need to look at me with so much animosity."

"You serve the Heavenly Court as well?" Han Li asked.

"I haven't joined the Heavenly Court, but I occasionally do things for them, even though I may not necessarily like it. Gu Huojin is too powerful for me to oppose, so I have no choice but to conform," Chen Ruyan replied.

"Didn't Feng Qingshui say that Wan'er had already been sent to the Heavenly Court? Why was she with you?" Han Li asked.

Chen Ruyan merely smiled and offered no response.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and right at this moment, Feng Qingshui suddenly flew out of her blue spirit domain.

All of his injuries had been healed, and his aura had also recovered significantly.

"Please accept my sincerest apologies for my incompetence, Mistress Ruyan," Feng Qingshui said with a guilty expression, and Han Li wasn't surprised to see this display of subordination from him.

Chen Ruyan was the Essential Water Dao Ancestor, while Feng Qingshui was the Water Dao Ancestor, so the latter was naturally bound to be below the former on the pecking order.

This type of relationship was not rare among Dao Ancestors, and almost every Essential Dao Ancestor had a corresponding, subordinate Dao Ancestor.

"It's fine. Even I wouldn't be able to defeat Fellow Daoist Han in battle, so there's no need to feel so bad about your defeat," Chen Ruyan said in an indifferent manner, displaying a completely different attitude than when speaking to Han Li.

Feng Qingshui nodded in response as he took a glum glance at Han Li.

"While it's true that Feng Qingshui was the one who captured your dao partner, he was only acting under the orders of the Heavenly Court, so please let him off the hook now that Fellow Daoist Nangong has been returned to you. Feng Qingshui and I occasionally do some favors for the Heavenly Court, but we are not Gu Huojin's allies, and we have no intention of opposing the Reincarnation Palace," Chen Ruyan said.

A look of realization flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

These two captured Wan'er at Gu Huojin's behest, but now that the Reincarnation Palace has made its move against the Heavenly Court, they're unsure of which side will come out on top, so they decided to keep Wan'er and wait for the situation unfold before making a decision.

Feng Qingshui most likely lied about having already sent Wan'er to the Heavenly Court in order to intentionally goad me into a rage so that I would display my full power. Now that they've witnessed my power, they're even more unwilling to oppose the Reincarnation Palace, and that's why they've returned Wan'er to me.

With that in mind, Han Li cast his gaze toward Feng Qingshui as he said, "In that case, I'll spare you this time, but you won't be so fortunate if you dare to go after anyone close to me again."

After that, he promptly withdrew his time spirit domain before vanishing from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning.

"The Reincarnation Palace really has managed to recruit a very powerful ally. The outcome of the conflict between the Reincarnation Palace and the Heavenly Court is only becoming more and more difficult to predict," Chen Ruyan mused with a faint smile.

"Mistress Ruyan, how are we going to answer to Gu Huojin now that you've returned Nangong Wan to Han Li?" Feng Qingshui asked with a concerned expression.

"It's fine. Just say that you were about to send her to the Heavenly Court when cultivators from the Reincarnation Palace intervened and rescued her. Right now, the Heavenly Court is facing a full-frontal assault from the Reincarnation Palace, so they won't dare to do anything to us," Chen Ruyan replied.

The concern on Feng Qingshui's face eased slightly upon hearing this, but he then began in a hesitant manner, "By the way, about that Han Li..."

"If you have something to say, then spit it out," Chen Ruyan said.

"I met him once in the Gray Realm around two thousand years ago, and since then, I've been notified that one of his companions at the time is a prince of the Devil Realm, so I suspect that he may have some ties with the Devil Realm," Feng Qingshui said.

"Oh? Tell me what happened," Chen Ruyan instructed as she raised an eyebrow, and Feng Qingshui promptly delivered a detailed recount of everything that took place in the Gray Realm at the time.

After hearing his story, Chen Ruyan's eyes narrowed slightly as she mused, "There's no way he could've gone from the peak-Golden Immortal Stage to the peak-Great Encompassment Stage in just two thousand years, so he must've hidden his true power back then. As for how they were teleported out of the Gray Realm, perhaps he wasn't the one to do it, but it definitely would've had something to do with him.

“That really complicates things. Could it be that the Reincarnation Palace is colluding with the Devil Realm? Also, did the Reincarnation Palace orchestrate Liu Qi's escape from the Gray Realm as well?"

"Hasn't it already been confirmed that ties exist between the Devil Realm and the Reincarnation Palace? The ability of the Reincarnation Palace masks to teleport items from wearer to wearer indicates a very advanced incorporation of spatial law powers, and only the cultivators of the Devil Realm could be so proficient in manipulating spatial laws," Feng Qingshui said.

However, Chen Ruyan shook her head as she said, "There are other details involved that you're not aware of."

Feng Qingshui was rather intrigued to hear this, but he could tell from Chen Ruyan's expression that she didn't want him asking questions.

"If Liu Qi was also rescued by the Reincarnation Palace, then there's a chance that the primordial land has also forged an alliance with the Reincarnation Palace! They really are everywhere!" Feng Qingshui exclaimed with a stunned expression.

"How else do you think the Reincarnation Palace was able to oppose the Heavenly Court for so long?" Chen Ruyan harrumphed, and Feng Qingshui fell into a sheepish silence.

"It looks like a major tribulation is about to sweep over the True Immortal Realm. I wonder if we'll be able to safely weather the storm," Chen Ruyan sighed.

"Aren't you thinking too much, Mistress Ruyan? We are Dao Ancestors, so we should be safe as long as we don't get involved in the conflict between the Heavenly Court and the Reincarnation Palace," Feng Qingshui said in a dismissive manner.

"No one is guaranteed to be safe in the face of an all-encompassing tribulation. In fact, you would've most likely already perished by now had I not intervened," Chen Ruyan said, and Feng Qingshui lowered his head upon hearing this.

"In any case, there's no point in thinking excessively about such matters. We'll just have to take things one step at a time," Chen Ruyan said, then vanished from the spot.

Feng Qingshui remained where he was for a moment, then flew back to the Mist Dragon Sect as a streak of blue light.

The shattered space in the Dragon Abyss Immortal Region had already returned to normal, and the unrest in the world's origin qi had also subsided.

Meanwhile, Han Li appeared in the air above a small and secluded island amid a flash of golden lightning.

He briefly examined the surrounding area with his spiritual sense to ensure that there wasn't anything amiss, then set up several layers of restrictions over the entire island.

From the outside, it appeared as if the island had vanished into thin air.

After that, he consumed a pair of blue pills, then pulled out two high-grade Immortal Origin Stones to assist in the recovery of his immortal spiritual power.

He had obtained the blue pills from Shui Changtian's storage tool, and they were a type of recovery pill that were quite potent even for late-Great Encompassment cultivators, and coupled with the two high-grade Immortal Origin Stones, it wasn't long before he had recovered close to half of his energy reserves.

As opposed to continuing to rest and recuperate, he immediately rose to his feet before entering the Flower Branch domain, where Nangong Wan was hovering in mid-air in a peaceful slumber.

Laying on the ground not far away was Sect Leader Yang Shan, who Han Li had tossed into the Flower Branch domain after the soul search.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of golden light, carefully wiping away the residual effects of the time law powers in his body, then cast him out of the Flower Branch domain, but only after he had confiscated all of his storage tools.

He had originally planned to use Sect Leader Yang Shan as leverage in exchange for some information about Nangong Wan's whereabouts, but now that she had been returned to him, there was no point in keeping Sect Leader Yang Shan.

With Sect Leader Yang Shan out of the way, Han Li carried Nangong Wan into the bamboo pavilion, then carefully set her down onto the bed inside.

Looking at her sleeping features, he couldn't help but allow himself a faint smile.

He had thought of her on countless occasions since his ascension to the True Immortal Realm, and even though they had been reunited earlier than this, she had been without her memories, so this was their first true reunion.

Han Li took a deep breath to compose himself, then gently pressed a finger against Nangong Wan's glabella, and a series of blue lines instantly emerged beneath his fingertip to form a simple seal.

The seal was no match for Han Li's power, and it flickered momentarily before quickly dissipating, following which Nangong Wan's eyelashes fluttered slightly as she opened her eyes.

Chapter 1333: Reunion

"Wan'er," Han Li called out in a gentle voice as he leaned down slightly with a gentle look in his eyes.

Nangong Wan was still looking rather dazed, seemingly yet to completely recover.

Han Li cast an incantation seal into her glabella upon seeing this, and a cool and refreshing sensation spread through her consciousness, instantly returning her fully to her senses.

She sat up on the bed, only to turn to Han Li in an expressionless manner.

Han Li's heart sank slightly upon seeing this. Could it be that he had been deceived, and Nangong Wan hadn't actually recovered her memories from this lifetime?

Despite his concerns, he reached out for her hand as he asked, "What's wrong, Wan'er? It's me."

Nangong Wan pulled back her hand so that it was out of Han Li's reach, then flew out of the bed with a wary look on her face.

"Who are you?"

"I am your dao partner, Han Li," Han Li replied.

"How can you prove your identity to me?" Nangong Wan asked in a cold manner.

A sense of relief welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this. It seemed that Nangong Wan had recovered her memories, she simply had reservations about his identity.

"Do you still remember the first time we met, Wan'er? It was during the Trial of Blood and Fire. At the time, you concealed yourself among us Qi Condensation Stage disciples to pick spirit medicines from all over the secret area. I have to say, that wasn't your finest moment," Han Li chuckled. [1]

A reminiscent look flashed through Nangong Wan's eyes upon hearing this, but it was only there for a moment before reverting back to the same apprehensive expression from before.

"After that, we worked together to defeat that flood dragon from what had seemed like a dire situation, and that was the beginning of our entwined fates..."

Han Li began to tell their story from the beginning, and even though countless years had passed since those events, they still remained fresh in his memory, as if they had taken place just yesterday.

"... We were separated after I ascended to the True Immortal Realm, and I had thought that perhaps that would've been a permanent separation, but fate has brought us back together," Han Li concluded.

Nangong Wan listened in silence the entire time, and it was clear from her expression that she wasn't swayed.

"These are all of our past experiences together, Wan'er. I'm sure no one else aside from the two of us is privy to this information," Han Li said with a hopeful look in his eyes.

"That doesn't prove anything. I can't tell what your current cultivation base is, but it's definitely above my own, so you could've easily searched my soul if you wanted to," Nangong Wan objected.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then sighed, "I suppose you're right. In that case, how would you like me to prove my identity to you?"

A contemplative look appeared on Nangong Wan's face as she considered the question.

All of a sudden, Han Li's expression changed slightly as he noticed that she was only giving off a True Immortal Stage aura.

He had been so caught up in the joy of their reunion that he had failed to notice this.

It seemed that with her memories recovered, the cultivation base that had belonged to Gan Rushuang and been bestowed upon her by the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate had been lost.

"I can see that your cultivation base has been regressed to the True Immortal Stage by the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate, but I've examined your condition, and this regression won't affect your future cultivation," Han Li assured.

"The Six Paths Reincarnation Plate... That's that underworld treasure in the Reincarnation Palace Master's possession, right? Do you know of that man's daughter?" Nangong Wan asked.

"I do. Her name is Gan Jiuzhen, and she was your daughter in your past life. If you have any other questions, then feel free to raise them," Han Li replied with a calm nod.

"How does that work? Also, why does the Reincarnation Palace Master look exactly like you?" Nangong Wan asked.

Han Li heaved a faint, internal sigh, then told Nangong Wan about his ties with the Reincarnation Palace Master, as well as how the latter had attempted to reawaken her memories of her past life using the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate.

Nangong Wan took some time to process this new information, then asked him a few more questions about the underworld, all of which he was able to answer.

"Surely you believe me now," Han Li said.

"That still doesn't prove it," Nangong Wan replied with a stubborn shake of her head.

A resigned look appeared on Han Li's face, but an idea then occurred to him.

With a sweep of his sleeve, he summoned his seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and the lightning flashing over them faded away to reveal the swords underneath.

"These Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords have always been my bonded treasure, even from back when we were together. I've refined them many times over the years, but the natural aura of the Golden Lightning Bamboo has been retained," Han Li said.

Nangong Wan stared blankly at the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords for a moment before turning her gaze back to Han Li, and her expressionless facade was finally beginning to crack.

"Oh, and there's also this. I've refined this treasure on multiple occasions as well, but it still retains some of its old traits," Han Li said as he summoned his Integrated Five Extremes Mountain.

Nangong Wan shuddered slightly at the sight of the mountain, and her resolve was clearly wavering as she turned back to Han Li.

"I've discarded all of my other treasures that you would be familiar with over the years, but I can still display some cultivation arts and abilities that you would've seen in the past, such as my Holy Nirvana Physique, and..."

Before he had a chance to finish, Nangong Wan had already dove into his arms, and she was embracing him with all her might as she murmured, "It's enough, I believe you."

After recovering her memories in the underworld, Nangong Wan had suffered a steep decline in her cultivation base, and everyone around her had been countless times more powerful than her, putting her in a constant state of unease.

Now that she was finally reunited with Han Li, she finally felt safe again, and she was gripping his arms with all her strength, as if she were afraid that he would disappear if she allowed her grip to relax even for a second.

Han Li returned her embrace with an affectionate and sympathetic look in his eyes.

He had been furious at the Reincarnation Palace Master's decision to awaken the memories of Nangong Wan's past life, but he had been powerless to oppose him at the time, so he was forced to leave her behind.

Now that Nangong Wan was finally back by his side, he felt as if a massive weight had been lifted from his chest.

His spiritual sense began to churn within his consciousness with this sudden and drastic change in his mental state, and he hurriedly closed his eyes to calm himself.

As he did so, he suddenly noticed that his nascent soul seemed to have undergone a curious change. It wasn't a significant change, and it would've completely escaped his notice had he not just so happened to have been inspecting his own internal condition.

It was this slight change that had resulted in an advancement in his cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique, and his spiritual sense had been significantly enhanced.

With his cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique, his spiritual sense had become more and more powerful, but it had never been a single, unified entity in his consciousness. Instead, it was as if it had been split up into individual bursts of power that refused to fuse with one another, resulting in a rather chaotic state.

He was able to unify his spiritual sense whenever he drew upon his Spirit Refinement Technique, but as soon as he stopped, his spiritual sense would return to its normal, chaotic state.

However, just now, his spiritual sense seemed to have found a point of unification.

It felt like a scattered and broken soul that had suddenly found a home, or a nascent soul that had returned to its host body after many years of roaming.

It was an indescribably blissful feeling, as if his nascent soul had been made whole, and what was even more of a pleasant surprise was that he had take a significant stride toward reaching full mastery of the seventh level of the Spirit Refinement Technique.

Upon sensing this change in Han Li's emotions, Nangong Wan gently pulled back to look at him as she asked, "What's wrong?"

"Nothing, I'm just really happy to have you back," Han Li replied in a gentle voice as he enveloped her in his embrace once again.

The two of them held each other in an intimate silence for a long time before releasing one another and exchanging a smile, and it was as if they had gone back in time to the days of old.

"I'm sorry for suspecting you just now," Nangong Wan said as an apologetic look appeared on her face.

"It's fine. In fact, it's very reassuring to see that you're so careful and cautious," Han Li said with a smile as he stowed his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and Integrated Five Extremes Mountain away, then sat down on the edge of the bed with Nangong Wan.

"What have you experienced during your time in the True Immortal Realm? I've heard some things about you from Gan Jiuzhen and the Reincarnation Palace Master, and they've mentioned some feats of yours that seem almost too extraordinary to be true," Nangong Wan said.

"I don't have any significant feats to my name. All I've been doing is running away from all types of adversaries over the years," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"I know you like to keep a low profile, but you don't have to be so modest when you're with me," Nangong Wan complained. "Let me ask you this: where do your powers rank in the True Immortal Realm right now?"

"At the moment, the most powerful cultivator in the entire True Immortal Realm has to be the Time Dao Ancestor, Gu Huojin. As for who's second, I don't think it's any of the other Dao Ancestors. Instead, I think it's the Reincarnation Palace Master. As for myself, I should be able to squeeze into the top ten," Han Li replied with a smile.

"I knew it! You're still the same dominant force that you were back in the Spirit Realm! Tell me everything that you've done during your time in the Immortal Realm, and don't try to keep any secrets! Also, I have a gift for you," Nangong Wan said as she pulled out half of a green jade pendant.

The jade pendant was as translucent as water, and there was an elegant figure etched onto its surface.

The figure was none other than Violet Spirit, while the jade slip that Violet Spirit had given to him had carried a visage of Nangong Wan.

"Alright, if you want to hear my story, then we'll have to start from the very beginning. After I ascended to the True Immortal Realm, I ended up in a secluded immortal region called the Northern Glacial Immortal Region..."

With that, Han Li commenced his tale, detailing his journey through the True Immortal Realm.

He glossed over some parts that contained sensitive information or concerned Violet Spirit, but he was very candid about everything else, even fully revealing the role that the Heaven Controlling Vial had played in his cultivation, something that he had never revealed to anyone else before.

Nangong Wan quickly became fully absorbed in his story, and her emotions fluctuated wildly with each twist and turn that was unveiled.

Her brows would furrow tightly whenever she heard about the people who had attempted to harm Han Li in the past, and she would heave a long sigh of relief upon learning how Han Li was able to save himself from his predicaments.

It was as if Han Li were a war veteran husband who had returned from the battlefield to tell his wife about his glorious feats.

As Nangong Wan listened to his story, her heart was filled with pride at his achievements, concern at the tribulations that he had been forced to endure, and elation at their long-awaited reunion.

Even though Han Li had discarded most of his attachments over the course of his cultivation journey, he retained a pure and earnest heart when it came to Nangong Wan, and it was only in her presence that he could truly be himself.

[1]. For more information on the Trial of Blood and Fire, please refer to https://a-record-of-a-mortal-is-journey-to-immortality.fandom.com/wiki/Trial_by_Blood_and_Fire

[Back]

Translator's Thoughts

Chapter 1334: Stories of the Past

"... After I learned that you had been captured by Feng Qingshui, I immediately traveled to the Dragon Abyss Immortal Region, where I battled him and Chen Ruyan. Thankfully, the heavens were on my side, and you were returned safely to me," Han Li recounted, marking a conclusion to his story.

"I've imagined to myself countless times what you would experience following your ascension, but the reality is far more extraordinary than anything I could've ever envisioned. The average person would've died countless times in your shoes, only you would be able to emerge in triumph from all of those perilous situations," Nangong Wan said with a hint of admiration in her voice.

"It's only thanks to a ridiculous amount of luck that I was able to make it to this point alive and well," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"And you also had the help of many powerful and beautiful women, didn't you? I've heard from Gan Jiuzhen that Weeping Soul and Jin Tong have already transformed into a pair of stunning beauties, and that's not even to mention Violet Spirit," Nangong Wan said with an amused smile.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he said, "Please don't make jokes at my expense. You know Weeping Soul, she's been with me ever since she was a little monkey back in the mortal realm. Speaking of Jin Tong, I never imagined that she would have such an extraordinary origin story. As for Violet Spirit..."

A slightly awkward look had appeared on his face at the mention of Violet Spirit, but before he had a chance to explain, Nangong Wan pinched his lips between her fingers to cut him off.

"I'm not going to get jealous over something like this. All of these things are pre-ordained by fate, just like our meeting," Nangong Wan said in a gentle voice.

Han Li nodded in response, then changed the subject as he said, "That's enough about me. How was life in the Spirit Realm for you before you ascended?"

"My time in the Spirit Realm was far less eventful than your time in the Immortal Realm. Following your ascension, I remained in the Azure Origin Palace to cultivate, and thanks to the resources that you left me and some opportunities that I encountered, I was able to reach the Grand Ascension Stage.

“After that, it took me several thousand more years to reach the pinnacle of the Grand Ascension Stage, at which point I attempted to transcend my heavenly tribulation so that I could be reunited with you in the True Immortal Realm," Nangong Wan recounted.

"How did your heavenly tribulation go?" Han Li asked.

"I thought I had prepared sufficiently to transcend my tribulation, but as things turned out, I was clearly too ambitious. In the end, I was overwhelmed, and in my final moments, I yelled to the heavens, hoping that you would be able to hear me," Nangong Wan replied with a wry smile.

Even though Han Li knew that Nangong Wan had clearly gone on to survive the ordeal, he still couldn't help but reach out to stroke her cheek in concern.

"I thought I was dead, but I woke up in a dark world, and by then, my magic power had already been converted into immortal spiritual power. On top of that, I was surrounded by True Immortals that were all far more powerful than Ma Liang had been," Nangong Wan continued. [1]

"A dark world? Was it the underworld?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. The Reincarnation Palace Master saved me, but he sealed away my memories, and my consciousness fell into a deep slumber, only reawakening recently," Nangong Wan replied.

"You must've suffered a lot of hardship over the years without me by your side," Han Li sighed as he latched onto her hand. "Why did you leave the Reincarnation Palace in the end?"

"The Reincarnation Palace Master was very respectful to me, and he didn't restrict my freedom, either, but my intuition told me that it was best for me to stay away from him. On top of that, I really wanted to see you, so I escaped in secret, but it seems like all I've done is cause you trouble," Nangong Wan replied as she lowered her head in a guilty display.

"Not at all," Han Li said with a smile. "I didn't want to leave you at the Reincarnation Palace, but I had no choice at the time. If you hadn't escaped from the underworld, who knows when our reunion would've come?"

A bright smile appeared on Nangong Wan's face upon hearing this, and he latched onto Han Li's hand with both of her own.

"Speaking of which, how is the human race doing in the Spirit Realm? And how is everyone in the Azure Origin Palace?" Han Li asked.

"The human race is doing very well, thanks to the foundation that you left behind, and everyone in the Azure Origin Palace had been progressing very smoothly in their cultivation while I was there. At the time of my tribulation transcendence, Qi Lingzi and Hai Yuetian had both reached the pinnacle of the Body Integration Stage, while Bai Guo'er had reached the Grand Ascension Stage. [2] Fellow Daoist Ice Phoenix and Sister Silvermoon reached the Grand Ascension Stage even earlier than I did, [3] but they wanted to prepare more extensively for their tribulation transcendences," Nangong Wan replied.

Han Li was overcome by a wave of nostalgia upon hearing all of these familiar names, and he was very happy to hear that all of them were doing well.

However, at the same time, he couldn't help but be struck by a sense of sorrow, not knowing if he would be able to see them ever again.

The path of cultivation was one that was inherently fraught with loneliness, and he should already count himself very fortunate that fate had brought Nangong Wan back to his side.

"By the way, how is Yuan Yao doing right now?" Han Li asked. [4]

A hint of dejection appeared in Nangong Wan's eyes at this question.

"Did something happen to her?" Han Li asked as a sense of foreboding welled up in his heart.

"Sister Yuan Yao was also able to reach the Grand Ascension Stage. She received Senior Qing Yuanzi's inheritance, allowing her to progress rapidly in her cultivation, and she attempted her tribulation transcendence even earlier than I did, but unfortunately, she was unable to make it," Nangong Wan replied as she lowered her gaze in a display of sorrow.

Han Li was completely blindsided by this news, and a sense of grief welled up in his heart.

"Don't be saddened by her passing. Sister Yuan Yao and I chatted for an entire night before her tribulation transcendence, and she told me that she had lived a spectacular life, and that she had no regrets regardless of whether she succeeded in her tribulation transcendence or not," Nangong Wan said.

"I'm fine, Wan'er, don't worry about me. It's just that I was a little caught off guard by this news," Han Li reassured with a slightly forced smile.

"I heard from the Reincarnation Palace Master that the Six Paths Reincarnation Plate governs the reincarnation of all living beings. Perhaps we can use it to find Sister Yuan Yao's current incarnation if the opportunity arises," Nangong Wan suggested.

"Yuan Yao perished to the might of the Heavenly Dao, so it's unclear whether her soul even survived, and even if we find her current incarnation, it'll no longer be her. Are we supposed to forcibly awaken the memories of her past life like the Reincarnation Palace Master did to you? If we were to do that, we would essentially be killing the Yuan Yao of this lifetime," Han Li said with a shake of his head, and Nangong Wan fell silent upon hearing this.

"If we manage to return to the Spirit Realm someday, you can take me to visit her grave," Han Li sighed.

As a peak-Great Encompassment cultivator, he had become very sensitive to the disparities between realms, and he knew that if he were to enter the Spirit Realm, it would most likely completely collapse in the face of his power.

Nangong Wan nodded in response, then suddenly gave Han Li an indignant look as she changed the subject and complained, "I can't believe you stumbled upon a treasure as extraordinary as the Heaven Controlling Vial so early in your cultivation journey! No wonder you progressed so rapidly in your cultivation in the mortal realm and the Spirit Realm. How could you have kept such a big secret from me for so long?"

"If that secret had been leaked, then I would've had countless people coming after me, so I couldn't tell anyone. If it makes you feel any better, you are the first person that I've revealed the full extent of the Heaven Controlling Vial's power to," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"It's fine, I don't blame you for your decision. Given the Heaven Controlling Vial's extraordinary powers, it's only right that you kept it a secret from everyone. Now that the Heavenly Court is aware that it's in your possession, won't they send people after you for it?" Nangong Wan asked in a concerned manner.

"That's not a concern. The Heavenly Court currently has its hands full dealing with the Reincarnation Palace, and with my current powers, I'm fairly confident in my ability to fend for myself. Outside of three people, I should be able to keep the Heaven Controlling Vial safe from everyone else in the entire True Immortal Realm," Han Li replied.

"I have full faith in you, but I'm afraid that I won't be of much help to you, given my current cultivation base," Nangong Wan sighed.

An intrigued look then appeared on her face as she mused, "It's incredible to think that there exists a treasure capable of space-time transmigration."

"I can take you on a trip if you're interested," Han Li offered as he pulled out his Heaven Controlling Vial.

"Don't do that. Each time you use that ability, it temporarily costs you the power of all of your Time Dao Runes, and that would leave you in a far too vulnerable state," Nangong Wan immediately refused with a shake of her head.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this. Now that he had reached the peak-Great Encompassment Stage, he was able to draw upon the power of the Heaven Controlling Vial to support the Heaven Controlling Vial's space-time transmigration ability, so the cost of using the ability was nowhere near as steep as before.

Having said that, he was very touched that Nangong Wan was so considerate of his safety.

"Alright, we'll leave it for another time then," Han Li said.

"What are your plans from here?" Nangong Wan asked.

"Truth be told, I was so focused on saving you that I haven't even considered my future plans. However, it's probably best to leave this place, given that my battle against Feng Qingshui and Chen Ruyan has most likely already caught the attention of certain unsavory individuals," Han Li replied, and Nangong Wan naturally raised no objections to this.

[1]. Ma Liang was essentially the final boss of the first instalment of RMJI, a True Immortal that had been sent down to the Spirit Realm for a mission. For more information on him, refer to https://a-record-of-a-mortal-is-journey-to-immortality.fandom.com/wiki/Ma_Liang

[Back]

[2]. Qi Lingzi, Hai Yuetian, and Bai Guo'er are all disciples of Han Li's from the Spirit Realm.

[Back]

[3]. Ice Phoenix and Silvermoon are both spouses of Han Li's from the Spirit Realm.

[Back]

[4]. Yuan Yao was a close friend of Han Li's from the Spirit Realm. They were referred to as soulmates, but there was no romantic development between them.

[Back]

Chapter 1335: Through Thick and Thin

In an unknown space.

The Reincarnation Palace Master was standing atop a cliff, and there was an ordinary-looking copper mirror hovering before him.

There was an image displayed on the surface of the mirror, and it depicted none other than Han Li and Nangong Wan.

There were also seven or eight figures standing not far behind him, and they were led by none other than the Heavenmend Sect cultivator, Yuan Chunfeng.

Right at this moment, Yuan Chunfeng approached the Reincarnation Palace Master with a puzzled expression as he said, "I already predicted through my divination that Nangong Wan would sneak out of the underworld to be captured by the Heavenly Court, so why did you not make an effort to prevent it from happening?"

"Nangong Wan's personality is just like Rushuang's, and now that she also has some of Rushuang's memories, she's only become even more wilful and stubborn. With her mind already made up, there's no way we could've kept her unless it was by force," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"Even then, we could've easily intervened before she was captured," Yuan Chunfeng said.

"I did this to show Han Li that the Heavenly Court is willing to stoop to anything to get what they want. This time, she was captured because of her ties with me, but in the future, her safety could very likely come under threat due to her ties with him," the Reincarnation Palace Master explained.

"A confrontation between him and Gu Huojin is inevitable at some point, and given the way Gu Huojin likes to do things, he won't spare anyone close to Han Li," Yuan Chunfeng agreed.

"Additionally, I also did this to trick the Heavenly Court. They've searched for me for countless millennia for no avail, and in the wake of Nangong Wan's capture, it seems like I finally panicked and made an irrational decision to come out of hiding," the Reincarnation Palace Master revealed.

"Even so, that was a little too risky, was it not? If Nangong Wan really had been sent to the Heavenly Court, then things would've been a lot more troublesome," Yuan Chunfeng said.

"Feng Qingshui isn't all that bright, but the one above him is very smart. Even your Heavenmend Sect knew the importance of hedging your bets, there's no way she would've done something that would've made her a sworn enemy of our Reincarnation Palace, so she would've never allowed Feng Qingshui to send Nangong Wan to the Heavenly Court," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied.

"But what if a mishap had occurred during Nangong Wan's capture?" Yuan Chunfeng asked.

"You already saw the outcome of her capture through your divination, so if some mishap had taken place, wouldn't you have been the one to blame?" the Reincarnation Palace Master asked.

Yuan Chunfeng instantly stiffened upon hearing this, and he felt a chill run down his own spine.

The Reincarnation Palace Master allowed the tension to build in the air for a while, then suddenly smiled as he broke the silence and continued, "Besides, I was constantly watching from the shadows, so no harm could've befallen her."

"Of course," Yuan Chunfeng replied with a nod.

The Reincarnation Palace Master turned his gaze back to the scene in the mirror.

"Will this really be enough to convince Han Li to side with us and oppose the Heavenly Court together?" Yuan Chunfeng asked as his gaze also fell upon Han Li.

"I know him better than anyone else in this world. There are certain things that he absolutely won't make any concessions on, and Nangong Wan is one of them. Now that he's reached the peak-Great Encompassment Stage, he's definitely not going to let this matter slide..."

Right at this moment, his voice abruptly cut off as Han Li suddenly turned to look directly at him through the mirror.

In the next instant, the copper mirror abruptly exploded, startling everyone present.

"What happened?" Yuan Chunfeng exclaimed.

"Don't worry, he simply noticed that he was being spied on. In fact, even the reincarnation mark that I planted on Nangong Wan has been removed," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied with a faint smile.

"In that case, won't he be able to guess that you allowed all of this to happen and develop a grudge against you?" Yuan Chunfeng asked.

"Perhaps, but it's not like that's going to change the final outcome," the Reincarnation Palace Master replied with an unconcerned smile.

......

Somewhere in the Dragon Abyss Immortal Region was an ancient forest, within which Han Li and Nangong Wan were standing together at the foot of a huge parasol tree.

"What's wrong?" Nangong Wan asked.

The two of them had agreed to travel to the Azure Abyss Continent so that they could use the teleportation array there to travel to the Middle Earth Immortal Region, but for some reason, Han Li had suddenly descended into this forest along the way.

As opposed to answering her question, Han Li carefully inspected his surroundings for a moment, following which his gaze settled upon a gray rock nearby.

A moth was resting on the rock, and upon catching sight of it, Han Li harrumphed coldly, "First, it was a blade of grass, then a fish, then a sparrow, and now a moth. Are you not tired of spying on us?"

In the next instant, a streak of translucent light shot out of his eye, and the moth instantly exploded into a puff of dust.

A surprised and perplexed look appeared on Nangong Wan's face as she asked, "Why do I sense reincarnation law power fluctuations from that moth?"

"You should ask the Reincarnation Palace Master that," Han Li harrumphed coldly, then carefully inspected Nangong Wan's body for a moment before reaching out for the back of her neck.

Nangong Wan leaned into his hand, and a burst of faint, golden light flashed over his palm.

Nangong Wan felt a slight, burning pain, but only for a fleeting moment before it subsided.

"Did he plant a mark on me?" she asked as her brows furrowed slightly.

"Just like that moth from before, these were most likely all measures taken by the Reincarnation Palace Master to protect you. I presume that if Feng Qingshui had tried to harm you in any way, he would've been able to instantly teleport to your side and intervene. However, such measures are no longer necessary now that I'm with you," Han Li replied with a smile.

A surge of warmth welled up in Nangong Wan's heart upon hearing this, and she replied with an affectionate smile, "What's in the past can all be left behind. What's important now is that we're together."

"Unfortunately, some people refuse to leave us in peace," Han Li sighed.

"Then let's leave this place. Let's go back to the Spirit Realm, or the mortal realm, or anywhere else," Nangong Wan said as she latched onto Han Li's hand.

"It's no use. Over the years, I always thought that I had been living according to my own wishes, that I was the master of my fate, that no matter how difficult things became, at least I had my free will. However, I've since then come to realize that the influence of fate is truly ever-present," Han Li said with a wry smile.

"I don't believe in fate. If it does exist, then I have to thank it for reuniting us," Nangong Wan replied.

"That's certainly something to be thankful for," Han Li mused with a warm smile, one that was returned by Nangong Wan.

"Now that I'm at the peak-Great Encompassment Stage, I'm becoming more and more able to sense the conflicting Great Daos of myself and Gu Huojin. I'm beginning to be able to see the river of time, and he's like the deity that rules over the river, while I'm like a sneaky thief trying to dig out a channel to redirect the river elsewhere," Han Li said.

"If you can sense him, then surely he's also aware of you," Nangong Wan said in a concerned manner.

"That's definitely true. It appears that there are countless paths that can be taken in one's cultivation, but ultimately, all of those paths narrow to a single one. If you're lucky, there will be no one else at the end of the path, but if you're unlucky, then a showdown will be inevitable," Han Li mused.

Nangong Wan could see that his mind was already made up, so she didn't try to sway him any further.

"I won't be able to help you much, but I'll remain by your side through thick and thin," Nangong Wan declared with a resolute look in her eyes.

"No. My trip to the Heavenly Court is bound to be one that's fraught with peril, I can't let you take the risk with me," Han Li immediately refused with a firm shake of his head.

"In Gan Rushuang's memories, she stood against Gu Huojin with the Reincarnation Palace Master, and even though she ultimately met her demise, she had no regrets. This time, I'm also going to stand by your side. If we lose, then I'll be there with you to the bitter end, and if we win, then I want to see your triumph with my own eyes!" Nangong Wan insisted in a determined manner.

Looking into Nangong Wan's determined eyes, Han Li didn't have the heart to turn her down again.

In the end, he sighed as he acquiesced, "After this close call, I feel like I won't be able to leave you anywhere without being constantly worried."

"Perhaps the most dangerous place is the safest place. Only when I'm by your side can you avoid distractions and focus on the task at hand," Nangong Wan said with a smile.

"If you insist on coming with me, then once we enter the Middle Earth Immortal Region, you have to stay in the Flower Branch domain at all times unless it's absolutely necessary for you to come out," Han Li said in a serious manner.

"Alright, I can do that," Nangong Wan replied with a firm nod.

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he laid his hands on Nangong Wan's shoulders as he carefully inspected her gorgeous features with eyes that were brimming with affection.

"What are you looking at?" Nangong Wan asked in a low voice as she averted her gaze with a faint blush on her face.

Chapter 1336: Exhaustive Mobilization

"You're still just as captivating to me as when I first saw you," Han Li said with a smile.

"I don't recall you being captivated by me when we first met. When we were facing that flood dragon..."

Nangong Wan's voice abruptly cut off here as she realized that she had misspoken, and the flush in her cheekers became even more pronounced.

Han Li enveloped her in a gentle embrace as a reminiscent look appeared in his eyes, and he said, "Come to think of it, I have to thank that flood dragon. If it wasn't for that thing, you and I wouldn't have..."

"Shush!" Nangong Wan hurriedly interjected as she pressed a finger against Han Li's lips to silence him.

Even though they were already dao partners, she still felt extremely embarrassed whenever she thought back to those events of the past.

The light of the sun filtered through the forest, basking the two of them in a warm and pleasant sensation. The occasional bird chirp rang out within the trees, and the mountain breeze resembled gentle hands caressing over their bodies.

The two of them enjoyed this rare moment of peace in silence, immersed in each other's warm embrace.

......

Half a month flew by in a flash.

The mortal realm under the Southern Forest Immortal region was the smallest and most infertile of all of the mortal realms.

The realm was almost entirely inhabited by mortals with no cultivation base to speak of, and even those who were born with any amount of cultivation aptitude were extremely rare.

Due to the severe lack of the world's origin qi in the realm, there were barely any spirit plants or cultivation resources to be found. As a result, even Core Formation cultivators were considered to be extraordinary cultivation prodigies here, while Nascent Soul cultivators were seen as god-like beings.

In this mortal realm, battles against cultivators were extremely rare. After all, it was extremely difficult just to cultivate at all here, so the few cultivators that did exist were very averse to any risk.

However, on this day, the number one immortal sect of the realm's Northern Origin Nation, the Hidden Mountain Sect, came under the attack of a sworn enemy.

The enemy in question was only a mid-Core Formation cultivator, while the leader of the Hidden Mountain Sect had already reached the late-Core Formation Stage several decades ago, so this should've been a complete suicide mission.

However, the intruder was able to kill all of the disciples of the sect using a bone flute, with which he was controlling a large swarm of powerful insects, the most prominent of which were twenty-eight infantile Gold Devouring Beetles.

Before long, all that was left of the Hidden Mountain Sect were its leader and several severely wounded elders, all of whom were ordered to make their way to the sect's ancestral hall by the intruder.

The leader of the Hidden Mountain Sect was a short man with a childlike appearance, and his entire right arm was missing, having been devoured by the twenty-eight Gold Devouring Beetles.

"I'll admit that it was an oversight on our part that resulted in your failed breakthrough, but you didn't have to go this far!" the sect leader yelled as he turned to the man with the bone flute with a furious expression.

The man stopped playing the flute, and the swarm of insects under his control temporarily drew to a halt.

"Given how sparse the world's origin qi in this realm is, you've most likely robbed me of my only chance of reaching the Nascent Soul Tier in this lifetime! Am I supposed to just let that slide?" the man asked in a cold voice.

"Even so, you've already completely destroyed my sect, so surely you've done enough," the sect leader pleaded.

"It's still not enough. You have to die for your Hidden Mountain Sect to be truly ruined," the man with the bone flute said in a cold voice, then began blowing on his flute again, and the surrounding swarm of insects instantly began converging toward the remaining Hidden Mountain Sect cultivators at his behest.

Right at this moment, a burst of faint rumbling rang out for a moment before fading away, and no one paid it any notice.

However, all of a sudden, a disturbance suddenly ran through the swarm of insects, and the entire swarm erupted into a chaotic frenzy.

The man with the bone flute was very alarmed to see this, and he hurriedly channeled his spiritual power to try and regain control over his spirit insects.

However, that only seemed to make matters worse, and all of a sudden, all of the spirit insects turned on him, led by the twenty-eight Gold Devouring Beetles.

A blood-curdling howl rang out, but it was quickly silenced, and within mere moments, there was nothing left of the man, with his entire body devoured down to the very last strand of hair.

All of the Hidden Mountain Sect cultivators were stunned to see this, but fortunately for them, the spirit insects displayed no intention of attacking them, and they quickly flew away into the distance.

Having just inexplicably survived what they had thought would've surely been their final moments, the Hidden Mountain Sect cultivators were left staring at one another with flabbergasted looks on their faces.

Meanwhile, a spatial rift that was several hundred feet in length had been torn open above a majestic mountain in the mortal realm, and swarms of spirit insects of all descriptions were converging from all directions before flying into it.

However, almost all of them were instantly torn to shreds by the spatial power within the rift, and only the several dozen Gold Devouring Beetles remained unscathed.

......

High Flourish Immortal Region, Bollworm Sect.

A belly of an entire mountain range that was enshrouded in a vast cloud of miasma had been virtually completely dug out, and there were countless maze-like passageways within, leading to thousands of palaces.

At this moment, there were countless creatures with human bodies and ant heads rushing through the passageways in a busy manner.

In a massive underground palace in the deepest part of the maze-like system laid an enormous, white ant queen. Its lower body was rotund and white like a silkworm, yet its upper body was no different from that of a human, complete with a stunningly beautiful female face.

Right at this moment, a burst of faint tremors suddenly swept through heaven and earth, and the ant queen's eyes abruptly sprang open as a look of incredulity and elation surfaced in her eyes.

"Could it be... It has to be!" she yelled in a frantic manner, then abruptly took on a fully human form.

In this form, she was a young woman in a white sheer dress, and her aura indicated that she was at the late-Great Encompassment Stage.

"Guards!" she yelled in an authoritative voice, and a group of eight figures instantly rushed to the palace before each falling to one knee.

"The day that we've been waiting for has finally arrived. Prepare for march!" the ant queen ordered.

The eight figures were ecstatic to hear this, and they quickly began mobilizing everyone in the giant ant colony.

On this day, the High Flourish Immortal Region witnessed the large insect tide in the history of its existence.

It was as if all of the spirit insects in the entire immortal region had suddenly decided to emerge, but as opposed to attacking any cities, all of them converged toward the peak of the tallest mountain in the immortal region, where a gargantuan spatial rift had appeared.

......

Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

The northernmost region of the Infernal Frost Continent was an inhospitable land that was enshrouded in ice and snow all year round, and the hostile conditions meant that there were barely any living beings residing here.

At this moment, a massive and indistinct blue shadow could be seen through a raging snowstorm on the summit of a tall, icy mountain.

All of a sudden, a faint crack rang out, and huge chunks of ice began tumbling down from the mountain to reveal a giant cocoon that was tens of thousands of feet tall.

A faint tearing sound rang out as the cocoon abruptly burst open, and a vast expanse of glacial qi erupted out of it, freezing the entire surrounding snowstorm solid.

A white-haired man with a pair of long feelers extending out of his forehead flew out from within the cocoon.

It was a thin and handsome man with a pair of eyes that glowed like sapphires, giving off a unique sense of allure.

The man was clad in a suit of blue leather armor, and there were four wings of blue light on his back.

Most astonishing of all was his aura, which was at the peak-Great Encompassment Stage, and he looked up into the heavens as he murmured to himself, "My queen, have you finally returned?"

In the next instant, he vanished from the spot with a flap of his wings.

......

Somewhere in the Heavenly Court.

Inside a giant palace that looked as if it had been carved out a single, enormous piece of green jade was a tall and imposing man. He had a head of short hair, a set of intimidating facial features, and his dark green robe was bulging over his incredibly muscular build. At this moment, the man was pacing back and forth in front of a jade throne with a grim look on his face.

Standing before him were several divine officials of the Heavenly Court, all of which were Great Encompassment cultivators, but at this moment, they were all displaying respectful expressions that were tinged with a hint of fear.

The man pacing before them was Xuanyuan Jie, the Essential Earth Dao Ancestor and one of the Seven Heavenly Dao Lords.

"You're telling me even Tong Qiu was assassinated along with Immortal Lord Hu Liang?" Xuanyuan Jie asked in a cold voice.

"All eight Reincarnation Envoys have been deployed in groups of two to hunt down all of the powerful cultivators traveling to attend the Bodhi Banquet, and both of them were targeted," one of the divine officials hurriedly replied as he fell to his knees, while his companions lowered their heads in a tense and fearful silence.

The demise of Immortal Lord Hu Liang wasn't of much concern to Xuanyuan Jie, but Tong Qiu was the son of one of his acquaintances.

Chapter 1337: Almighty Insect Tide

"Have you found out which two of the Reincarnation Envoys did it?" Xuanyuan Jie asked.

"It was Yan Zhuo and Xuan Yu. They made no attempt to hide their identities, and they even demolished the ancestral hall of Tong Qiu's sect, so it looks like they don't fear retaliation from the Heavenly Court," the divine official replied.

"Find out where they are, kill them, and bring their souls to me," Xuanyuan Jie ordered.

The divine officials were just about to respond when Xuanyuan Jie's expression suddenly changed slightly, and all of them instantly fell silent as their hearts leaped into their throats.

All of a sudden, Xuanyuan Jie burst into laughter.

"I didn't think you would be able to make it back to this point. Let met see how you're going to get away this time!"

The divine officials had no idea what was happening, so they remained in a fearful silence.

"Lu Qingshan, Zhao Yao, go and find out Yan Zhuo and Xuan Yu's whereabouts. Everyone else, come with me," Xuanyuan Jie ordered, and the divine officials immediately gave a collective affirmative response.

......

Dragon Abyss Immortal Region, Azure Abyss Continent.

There was not a single cloud anywhere in sight in the clear, blue sky, and the sea down below was just as clear and vibrant.

Two streaks of light were racing through the air, leaving a long, golden trail in their wake.

Within the streaks of light were none other than Han Li and Nangong Wan, and the former had disguised himself as a man with bushy eyebrows and a large beard, while Nangong Wan remained without a disguise.

"Once we get to the Azure Abyss Continent, you'll enter the Flower Branch domain, while I go into the teleportation pagoda on my own to travel to the Middle Earth Immortal Region," Han Li said.

"Isn't it going to be too dangerous for you to travel to the Middle Earth Immortal Region using the Heavenly Court's teleportation array?" Nangong Wan asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"It'll be fine. I have a Bodhi Token in my possession, so they won't scrutinize me too closely. On top of that, I'm sure they would've never expected that I would dare to do this," Han Li reassured.

"I suppose," Nangong Wan replied with a nod, but it was clear that her concerns hadn't entirely abated.

Shortly thereafter, the coastline of the Azure Abyss Continent came into view on the horizon, and right at this moment, a burst of peculiar energy fluctuations swept through the air from up ahead.

Han Li immediately stopped in his tracks and positioned himself in front of Nangong Wan as he cast his gaze forward.

In the sky above the coastline was a vast expanse of black light, within which was a chaotic gathering of spirit insects.

A perplexed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Within mere moments, the expanse of black light had already flown several hundred kilometers closer to them, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

The entire expanse of black light was crammed full of spirit insects of all descriptions ranging from several inches to thousands of feet in size.

An insect tide of just a single species wouldn't have been much cause for interest, but there were millions of spirit insects of all types of species intermingled together here, and that was very strange.

"Something's not right," Han Li murmured.

"What's wrong? It's just an insect tide, is it not?" Nangong Wan asked.

"Normally, insect tides only contain a single species of spirit insects. However, there are countless species here, some of which are natural enemies of one another that would've normally been sure to fight to the death on sight, so it's very strange that they're coexisting so peacefully together," Han Li explained.

All of a sudden, the swarm of insects parted as a giant, golden beetle flew out from within their ranks, and it was a Gold Devouring Immortal that was close to the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage.

"Wait here for me for a second," Han Li said with slightly furrowed brows, and before she had a chance to reply, he had already vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, he appeared directly before the swarm of insects, and it looked as if he were about to be inundated.

However, a golden spirit domain then erupted out of his body, encompassing the entire surrounding area within a radius of close to a hundred thousand kilometers.

All of the spirit insects were instantly immobilized within the time spirit domain, while even the sea down below had fallen completely still.

Han Li made his way through the insect tide, quickly arriving in front of the Gold Devouring Immortal, then pressed a finger against its glabella to send a streak of translucent light vanishing into its head.

After taking a moment to examine the Gold Devouring Immortals memories, his eyes sprang open as he exclaimed, "How could she have not told me about this! She's always so reckless!"

Immediately thereafter, he returned to Nangong Wan's side in a flash.

"What's wrong?" Nangong Wan asked.

"It looks like Jin Tong is about to make a breakthrough, and these spirit insects are traveling to her side," Han Li replied.

"Is she about to reach the late-Great Encompassment Stage?" Nangong Wan asked.

"No, she's going to attempt a breakthrough to become a Dao Ancestor," Han Li replied with a shake of his head, and Nangong Wan was stunned into silence upon hearing this.

"Jin Tong was split off from a Dao Ancestor to begin with, so she's able to progress in her cultivation simply by devouring her brethren. As a result, she doesn't need to sever any corpse souls, and the speed of her progression depends solely on how quickly she's able to encounter and devour other Gold Devouring Immortals," Han Li explained.

"Isn't that a good thing? Why do you look so worried?" Nangong Wan asked.

"Similar insect tides to this one are most likely arising across all of the immortal regions, and that's inevitably going to attract the attention of the Heavenly Court," Han Li mused.

"What are you planning to do then?" Nangong Wan asked as a look of concern appeared in her eyes as well.

"I have to go help her," Han Li said.

"I agree, but do you know where she is right now?" Nangong Wan asked.

"I don't have to, I can simply follow this insect tide," Han Li replied.

"That's a good idea. I'm sure it'll make for a spectacular sight once all of the insects tides from all of the immortal regions combine into one," Nangong Wan said.

"Let's go. Time is of the essence," Han Li said, then latched onto Nangong Wan's hand before flying onto the Gold Devouring Immortal's back.

After that, he withdrew his time spirit domain, and the insect tide was instantly able to advance as normal again.

......

Somewhere in the Extraheavensphere.

There was an incredibly dark and pure expanse of space that was filled with spatial storms, which would occasionally clash against one another to produce spectacular light displays.

On the edge of a massive spatial storm was an even more enormous black cloud that was moving as if it were a living creature, and beams of light were shining out of it in all directions as if it were a light tower.

The black cloud was formed by Extrarealm Heavenly Devils, but for some reason, it was currently pressed tightly against the spatial storm, unwilling to stray even a single inch from it.

Hovering in the boundless space several hundred thousand kilometers away was a golden beetle that was hundreds of thousands of feet in size, and it was giving off an unfathomably powerful aura alongside a vast expanse of dazzling, golden light.

Any asteroids that dared to stray too close to it were instantly wiped out of existence by its aura even tens of thousands of kilometers away, and laid out around the golden beetle were numerous spatial rifts that resembled windows in a dark room.

The smallest of those rifts were hundreds of feet in size, while the largest were thousands of times more massive, and they were connected to countless immortal regions.

At the moment, there were countless spirit insects surging into the Extraheavensphere through most of the spatial rifts, but the spatial pressure in the Extraheavensphere was so immense that most of the spirit insects were completely pulverized as soon as they arrived.

Even so, countless more spirit insects continued to fly in without any regard for their own safety.

There were some powerful beings among them that were able to withstand the spatial pressure, and they flew over to the golden beetle's side, where they were able to enjoy the protection of the golden light radiating from its body.

There were also many Gold Devouring Beetles interspersed among them, and they instantly disintegrated into bursts of pure power that surged into the giant golden beetle's body after flying into the golden light.

As more and more spirit insects flew into the Extraheavensphere, the swarm of insects around the golden beetle grew larger and larger, forming an asteroid-belt-like structure around it.